<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Amiga CD32</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game id="33575" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./AlienBreedTowerAssault_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Alien Breed : Tower Assault</name>
		<desc>In the depths of space a holocaust has occured. Intelligent and hostile alien life-forms have taken over the Military Research Unit in the planet Azarin 2E. Chaos and destruction have been wrought on the innocent colonists.
Now it's your job to reclaim the station for humankind. Travel through the tractless voids of space, then endure over 65 levels of Alien blasting mayhem. Watch your ammunition and energy levels in preparation for the showdown with the Alien Queen.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Team 17</publisher>
		<hash>384C2BA9</hash>
		<image>./media/images/AlienBreedTowerAssault_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/AlienBreedTowerAssault_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33316" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ArabianNights_v1.4_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Arabian Nights</name>
		<desc>In Arabian Nights, you play Sinbad Jr., a gardener at the royal palace who loves to sneak a peek at the princess every now and again. One day, Sinbad looks up and sees a huge demon kidnapping the princess. He dashes to save the princess, only to be caught by the palace guards and thrown in the dungeon. 

There are nine levels in the game. In several levels, there are various gameplay elements which include flying on the magic carpet and racing against your opponent in a mine cart. You will also meet some characters, which if you give them an item they want, they will give you something in return.
 
In other levels, you have to do things yourself. For example, obtain a snake that will set a prisoner free, or using a blow torch to open some frozen doors.

Arabian Nights comes on two floppy disks, but a CD32 version is also available on 1 CD.
</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19930512T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krisalis Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Krisalis Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>AF9F005B</hash>
		<image>./media/images/ArabianNights_v1.4_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/ArabianNights_v1.4_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="172988" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ArcadePool_v3.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Arcade Pool</name>
		<desc>Arcade Pool is an overhead viewed pool game designed to be easy to control. The game includes the most standard games of pool (UK and US 8-ball and the fast-paced 9-ball game), each with customisable rules, computer players of variable difficulties, and two-player options. There's also a Survivor mode, which is similar to the early Pool arcade game, in that you're playing alone and have to clear the table without missing more than three times. Speed Pool involved clearing the table as quickly as you can - two minutes can be considered a good time.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Team 17</publisher>
		<hash>0C4B1A7C</hash>
		<image>./media/images/ArcadePool_v3.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/ArcadePool_v3.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="89741" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Banshee_v3.3_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Banshee</name>
		<desc>A vertically-scrolling shoot 'em up from the old school, with similarities to games like 1942 and SWIV. There are lots of big, brash enemy vehicles to take on, plus individual soldiers (these often lie in a pool of blood afterwards, a gruesome sight making full use of AGA graphics) and civilians. Many of the enemies have good hiding places and can emerge surprisingly, Commando-style.

There are four large levels, which also scroll a small amount horizontally, the idea being that you can evade some opposition. There's a special loop-the-loop type feature available, which can double as an attack or an evasive move.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>8DB86779</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Banshee_v3.3_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Banshee_v3.3_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="172989" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./BaseJumpers_v2.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Base Jumpers</name>
		<desc>Base Jumpers was the second release by Aaron and Adam Fothergill's Shadow Software outfit for publisher Rasputin and was very simple in concept. In a 2D platform gaming style, players run up to the top of towers, trying to combine 3 letter pickups to collect plain daft bonuses (there were something like 500 different 3 letter combinations) and then jump off the building and base jump down the outside. The last player to avoid the sticky out bits of the building and successfully open their parachute before becoming pavement art wins the round.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shadowsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Shadowsoft</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>2CAECF47</hash>
		<image>./media/images/BaseJumpers_v2.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/BaseJumpers_v2.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33213" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Battletoads_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Battletoads</name>
		<desc>The Dark Queen has attacked and kidnapped (toadnapped?) your best buddy.. To make matters worse, she nabbed the best looking girl around! So, what will you do? Cry? Whimper? Hide? Call the Starcops? NO! Cause you're a Battletoad! Battletoads don't cry, hide or call for help! And they certainly don't whimper! They get MAD then they get EVEN! So grab your blaster, hop on the Toadster and go get 'em!

You will control a battletoad through various levels. Some are side-scrolling beat-em-ups, other are vertical drops down a shaft, fighting as you go, others have you riding a rocket or surfboard, shooting or avoiding enemies. At the end of each area, there is a boss. In some areas, about half-way through, you may have a mini-boss.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>B513A050</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Battletoads_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Battletoads_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33756" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Benefactor_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Benefactor</name>
		<desc>As Ben E Factor himself, you must travel through the six moons of Minniat, on which the peaceful and good-natured people of Lullyat have been kidnapped. These Merry Men each have their own potential skill once rescued, so releasing them in the right order is often essential for completing a level. Some Merry Men have grey suits - this marks them out as joyless and awkward characters which must be guided through a coloring machine.

The Miniation people have loaded the 60 levels with various nasties, ranging from slugs (slow, but must be jumped), Rock Men (those with sharp backs are more dangerous, but both are quite nippy), spiked teeth emerging from manholes, and so on. A large map is provided, and at any point you can pause the game and scroll around the map, which makes the forward planning easier.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940702T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Illusions</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4FB8FE33</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Benefactor_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Benefactor_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="104977" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./BlackViper_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Black Viper</name>
		<desc>Black Viper takes inspiration from games such as Fire and Forget and Chase H.Q., replacing the fast car with an armed motorcycle. As usual, this game takes place after a terrible nuclear war, with you playing as the son of a lost freedom fighter. 

The freedom fighters try to recapture the remaining cities from the mercenaries acting on behalf of the underground people who instigated the war in the first place. To do this, you must travel from city to city on the open roads, arriving within a given time frame. This is difficult due to the crowded roads, but luckily you can blow up most other vehicles with your gun. As the game progresses, enemy vehicles become harder, requiring more shots to be taken out. Luckily, your bike may be upgraded in the shop between levels.

Black Viper has a certain arcade-ish look to its graphics, a jukebox for choosing soundtracks, and comes in both OCS and AGA versions.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Light Shock Software</developer>
		<publisher>neo Software Produktions</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>98F4C274</hash>
		<image>./media/images/BlackViper_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/BlackViper_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33892" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./BrutalPawsOfFury_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Brutal : Paws of Fury</name>
		<desc>Brutal : Paws of fury est un jeu de combat sur Amiga. Le Dalaï-Lama, plus grand guerrier du Monde, a convié tous les animaux maîtres dans leur discipline. Un rat boxeur, un singe maître de kung-fu ou encore un crocodile karatéka, voilà les combattants qui se défient pour avoir l'honneur d'affronter le Dalaï-Lama. Le style loufoque des personnages et les animations ne manqueront par d'ajouter une bonne dose de rire dans toute cette violence.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GameTek</developer>
		<publisher>GameTek</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<hash>F36D5417</hash>
		<image>./media/images/BrutalPawsOfFury_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/BrutalPawsOfFury_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="172998" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./BubbaNStix_v3.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Bubba 'n' Stix</name>
		<desc>Bubba and his sidekick Stix are an interesting pair, Bubba is a happy-go-lucky animal delivery guy for the local Zoo here on Earth . One day while going about his daily routine, Bubba is abducted by an alien that plans on delivering him along with several other aliens in their zoo. On the way back to his home planet, the alien spacecraft loses control and crashes, Bubba, the other aliens and Stix (a sentient twig like alien) are able to escape. Bubba and Stix become friends and start on their journey home, They're now on an alien planet, things are a little bit different than they are on Earth. Take control of Bubba as he wields Stix as various puzzle solving tools (including a weapon), as they try to find a way back home. You'll have to solve mind-boggling puzzles and fight all kinds of wacky aliens if you're planning to return to Earth, so you'll have to have fast reflexes and be able to think fast and sometimes sideways.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B45D02A7</hash>
		<image>./media/images/BubbaNStix_v3.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/BubbaNStix_v3.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="89997" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./BubbleAndSqueak_v2.1-B_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Bubble And Squeak</name>
		<desc>Bubble and Squeak starts off similarly to many other platform games. Controlling a bald child, you move through a scrolling array of ledges, avoiding contact with nasties who release coins when shot. There are hidden areas to find as well.

Halfway through the first of the 30 levels, you meet Squeak and the full nature of the game starts. Squeak is a blue alien, who must also be guided through the levels. As he can't jump as high as you, he must sometimes be instructed to wait while you flick a switch or otherwise solve the puzzle of how to guide him through. If you stand on top of Squeak you can be launched into an extra-high jump.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Fox Williams</developer>
		<publisher>Audiogenic</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0D00FF1B</hash>
		<image>./media/images/BubbleAndSqueak_v2.1-B_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="34009" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./BumpNBurn_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Bump 'n' Burn</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart is taken one step further in this racer. The computer racers include Loretta LAmour, the Buck-Toothed Beavers, and the uncompromising Colonel Carnage, each of which have individual looking cars, varied weapons, and some attempts at humour and pathos.

The courses are quite lengthy, and are laden with hazards and power-ups such as oil slicks and homing missiles. The computer cars appear to be faster when behind you than when in front  strange.

The handling is deliberately arcadey, with fast acceleration and braking as well as the chance to brake and steer at the same time. The graphics are third-person, with a split-screen option, in the grand Mario Kart / OutRun tradition.
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Grandslam Entertainments Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Grandslam Entertainments Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>77559978</hash>
		<image>./media/images/BumpNBurn_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/BumpNBurn_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33333" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./CannonFodder_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Cannon Fodder</name>
		<desc>Guide a team of up to four soldiers through 72 levels of combat in this innovative top-down action/strategy hybrid, best thought of as Lemmings crossed with Commando crossed with Dune 2. The characters are controlled indirectly using the mouse, as you activate each soldier or group of them by highlighting them, click the left button to move them to a particular spot, and the right button for them to fire guns at an enemy. You can also pick up grenades, which can be used to destroy groups of enemies or buildings (by pressing both buttons at once). 

Each mission has a specific objective, and some feature vehicles such as tanks to make things easier. Your troops can cross water but can't shoot within it, so finding and controlling bridges is often crucial. You can use the arrangement of trees to find hiding places to shoot from, and should watch out for CPU soldiers also doing so.
</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sensible Software</developer>
		<publisher>Avalon Interactive</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C61ADD27</hash>
		<image>./media/images/CannonFodder_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/CannonFodder_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="90061" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./CapitalPunishment_v1.1a_AGA_CD.lha</path>
		<name>Capital Punishment</name>
		<desc>You choose one of four warriors (Corben Wedge, Wakantanka, Sarmon or the topless Demona) and try to battle your way through a series of baddies ('Street Fighter' style) until you reach the final boss: Qwesul! On the way you get the chance to 'Rescue' the other fighters you could have chosen after you beat them in a fight. After that you get to choose which fighter to take with you into the next arena, depending on who you think will work best for that fight.
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>PXL</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>FA8B511A</hash>
		<image>./media/images/CapitalPunishment_v1.1a_AGA_CD.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/CapitalPunishment_v1.1a_AGA_CD.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173002" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cedric_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Cedric</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>9F296BFF</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Cedric_v1.1_CD32_Fast.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="173005" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ChuckRock2_v2.4_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Chuck Rock 2</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>04F35EBC</hash>
		<image>./media/images/ChuckRock2_v2.4_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="33331" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ChuckRock_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Chuck Rock</name>
		<desc>Chuck Rock is your typical average cave man.  He likes to spend his Sunday afternoons watching football and drinking beer.  Unfortunately, his peaceful existence is interrupted one day when his wife, Ophelia Rock, is kidnapped by the village wierdo, Gary Gritter.  So, Chuck is rather upset about this whole situation and you have to help him make things right.

The game is a side-scrolling platformer.  Chuck fights of a variety of dinosaurs using his belly-buster attack and a jump kick.  Occasionally he has to pick up and throw rocks to defeat enemies and allow him to jump to greater heights.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8AA48895</hash>
		<image>./media/images/ChuckRock_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/ChuckRock_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33294" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Civilization_v1.1_CD.lha</path>
		<name>Civilization</name>
		<desc>This is it - the game that you've decided is the best Amiga game ever, and I must say it caught me by surprise. Sid Meier's conquest game is intriguing and addictive; challenging the player to evolve with their charge through the ages, from primitive man to present day and beyond. Hugely absorbing, the game sucks in the player and has been responsible for many late nights and bleary eyes. The recent re-issue on CD should ensure Civ stays at the top of the AR100 for a while yet.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>29006138</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Civilization_v1.1_CD.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Civilization_v1.1_CD.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="34276" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Clockwiser_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Clockwiser</name>
		<desc>On each of Clockwiser's levels, you are presented with a level layout, and a target layout, with the aim being to transform the former to match the target. The levels consist of a collection of cogs, which can be rotated either clockwise or anti-clockwise to achieve this goal. There are lots of special blocks to help out, including bombs, diamond-producers and anti-gravity blocks. Each level has its own time limit, ranging from seconds to minutes - this doesn't start until you make your first move, and you can look around the level at your leisure before making a stab at it. Each level has its own password, which makes progression a little easier.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Hoi</developer>
		<publisher>Rasputin Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>417C3B65</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Clockwiser_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Clockwiser_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="90373" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./DGeneration_v2.4_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>D/generation</name>
		<desc>Something has gone horribly wrong at Genoq Biolabs, Singapore. You're just a courier, sent to the building to deliver a package. Now you're trapped inside, the security system has gone crazy, genetically engineered organisms are on the rampage and things look like they could get even worse...

Make your way through 10 floors of isometric action and puzzles, trying to stay alive and discover what's going on. Talk to and rescue survivors, pick up armaments and log into computer terminals. What caused the Genoq disaster? What's inside the
vital package you've got to deliver? What is the D/Generation? And what is really waiting for you on the top floor of the building?
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Abersoft</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>37F9AF06</hash>
		<image>./media/images/DGeneration_v2.4_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/DGeneration_v2.4_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="78424" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./DarkSeed_v1.03_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Darkseed</name>
		<desc>Dark Seed is an adventure game which capitalizes on the drawings of famous horror designer H. R. Giger as a source of background artwork and inspiration.

You play Mike Dawson, an ad company manager who, in pursuit of his goal in life to become a writer, purchases a solitary mansion in a small town called Woodland Hills. Although the low cost and hush-hush transactions when purchasing the house do raise your suspicion, the solitary environment and sheer beauty of the house crush common sense and you decide to buy the house. That's when trouble begin. Upon reaching the house, you suddenly feel tired. You find a bed and fall asleep...

... and wake up from a terrible dream, only to find out that your life has just become a worse nightmare: an unknown source has implanted a seed of darkness in your mind, and you only have three days to find a way to stop it.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incentive Software</developer>
		<publisher>Cinemaware</publisher>
		<hash>8E7E49F0</hash>
		<image>./media/images/DarkSeed_v1.03_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/DarkSeed_v1.03_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33357" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./DefenderOfTheCrown_v3.1_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Defender of the Crown</name>
		<desc>Defender of the Crown puts you in the role of one of four Saxon knights in medieval England, in a time where the land is in turmoil as the King is dead and his crown was stolen. The Saxons and the Normans blame each other and fight for control of England.

After a short introduction by Robin of Locksley himself, you start the game with a single castle and 10 soldiers at your command. From there, you have to build your army, take control of additional territories and fight the three Norman lords - and sometimes your Saxon friends as well.

The game has several different styles: You may either engage in a jousting contest where you have to knock your opponent off his horse using a lance, you can go raid a castle for loot or you can attack another territory/castle.

The game was originally created on the Amiga platform in 1986 by Cinemaware with wonderful graphics by James D. Sachs and great music by Jim Cuomo, then ported to the PC whilst keeping its original appeal and quality.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Master Designer Software</developer>
		<publisher>Cinemaware</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7F5F51BA</hash>
		<image>./media/images/DefenderOfTheCrown_v3.1_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/DefenderOfTheCrown_v3.1_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="90457" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dennis_v1.5.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Dennis</name>
		<desc>This game brings the US cartoon character Dennis the Menace's menacing treatment of poor old Mr. Wilson to the computer screen, around the time of the film also released in 1993. 

Dennis is a platform game across settings such as Sewers, the Park, and Mr. Wilsons house, each of which has an end-of-level bad guy. The in-level opposition follows standard attack patterns and can usually be avoided. The enemies regenerate as you move on, although you generally only progress from bottom-left to top-right anyway. 

Some of the holes in the ground are deadly while others lead to secret rooms. Fortunately, you are given up to 9 lives at the start, and lots of extra lives are on offer throughout the game, so these are well worth checking out. A choice between music and sound effects is offered.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Citizen Software</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A609A8BA</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Dennis_v1.5.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Dennis_v1.5.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="34029" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./DisposableHero_v1.5_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Disposable Hero</name>
		<desc>This horizontally scrolling R-Type-influenced shoot 'em up features 5 levels to blast through, with bosses at the end of each level as well as tough mini-bosses as you go through it. There are four difficulty levels, with the easiest acting as a trainer, as you can't reach the final level or complete the game properly with it. You can customize exactly how loud the music and sound effects are relative to each other, and there lots of subtle visual effects, such as a smoke haze coming off your ship as it incurs gradual damage.

The game's power-up system is worthy of note. Rather than simply picking up new weapons, or all-purpose tokens which can be traded in at the press of a button, you collect blueprints for a total of 32 different weapons as well as upgrades to the maximum amount of power your ship can unleash at a time. Once you reach a power-up bay (which are depicted as blue domes at the base of the level), you can add or remove weapons so as to maximize your attack capabilities.
</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1C963248</hash>
		<image>./media/images/DisposableHero_v1.5_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/DisposableHero_v1.5_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173020" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragonstone_V1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Dragonstone</name>
		<desc>The pseudo-sequel to Darkmere, Dragonstone has a look and feel influenced by Zelda, making it stand out from the Dungeon Master-influenced bulk of role-playing games for the Amiga.

Agon is the villain whose hordes you must destroy. The game is split across 7 multi-directional levels, taking in forests and caves in a fantasy setting. You are armed with a sword and a special energy-bolt attack, which can be charged up. Some vanquished enemies discard food or gold; there are shops in which to spend this.
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A273BB6D</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Dragonstone_V1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Dragonstone_V1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="120376" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./EmeraldMines_v1.0_CD.lha</path>
		<name>Emerald Mines</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>6C8D3274</hash>
		<image>./media/images/EmeraldMines_v1.0_CD.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="173022" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ExtractorPreview_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Extractors Preview</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>18D5280E</hash>
		<image>./media/images/ExtractorPreview_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="103138" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./FantasticVoyage_v1.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Fantastic Voyage</name>
		<desc>Fantastic Voyage is a side-scrolling shooter based on the 1966 movie of the same name. The scientist Jan Benes is near death because of a clot of blood in his brain. A submarine, controlled by the player, is shrunk and needs to reach the brain through three levels. The enemies, which lower the energy bar when touched, are the human defense systems like antibody cells.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Centaur</publisher>
		<hash>77D9185D</hash>
		<image>./media/images/FantasticVoyage_v1.0_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/FantasticVoyage_v1.0_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="90802" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fears_v4.0.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Fears</name>
		<desc>One of the numerous Doom style games for the Amiga in the mid 90s. Like Gloom, it was published by Guildhall Leisure, who gave the Amiga a lot of time in that era.

Fears took the approach of having full-screen, though relatively low-resolution, graphics. The level landscapes feature lots of stairways and lifts, giving it a psuedo-3D feel. The game is played across 30 levels., with a level designer also included. The one-player game has 3 difficulty levels, while multi-player action is available via a null-modem cable.
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Manyk</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>1D2988FB</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Fears_v4.0.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Fears_v4.0.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="172431" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fire&amp;Ice_v2.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Fire And Ice</name>
		<desc>Fire And Ice sur Amiga est un jeu d'action vous permettant de jouer un drôle de coyote qui se bat en lançant des glaçons sur ses adversaires pour ensuite les casser ! Il doit récupérer toutes les parties de clés qu'ils laissent tomber afin de passer au niveau suivant.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renegade Software</developer>
		<publisher>Graftgold</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4F8D927A</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Fire&amp;Ice_v2.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Fire&amp;Ice_v2.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33920" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./FireForce_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Fire Force</name>
		<desc>This shoot 'em up scrolls horizontally with gameplay on a number of different levels, similarly to Green Beret. You play an elite soldier dropped behind enemy lines who must take out the enemy forces. You can choose your weapons and ammunition before starting, including a wide range of guns as well as grenades and a trusty pocket-knife. You'll have to avoid land mines and destroy bridges along the way. Defeated enemies release further weapons.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICE</developer>
		<publisher>ICE</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A5E9F065</hash>
		<image>./media/images/FireForce_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/FireForce_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173028" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Flink_v2.4_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Flink</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>1B24CE29</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Flink_v2.4_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="33922" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./FlyHarder_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Fly Harder</name>
		<desc>Your homeland's precious limited energy is being taken advantage of by the evil Thargoid Empire, and you and your spaceship must do something about it. There are 8 bases to enter, with the aim of using energy pods to cause the reactors to overload and thus malfunction.

The game is viewed side-on, resembling the ST classic Oids quite strongly; which is to say that gravity and motion physics dictate the ship's motion strongly. The 8 levels all have plenty of enemies on offer, both wall-mountings and actual ships, as well as enhanced weapons and extra fuel and shield energy. The ship can take some damage, and repairs itself over time (for no logical reason), which is one of the few things that gives you a hope of getting anywhere early on. Losing a life causes all the enemy turrets to replenish, emphasizing the restart points and making things more maze-based and methodical.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Simulation</developer>
		<publisher>Action</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>456611A8</hash>
		<image>./media/images/FlyHarder_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/FlyHarder_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173030" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Frontier_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Frontier</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>300D2F34</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Frontier_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="33282" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./FuryOfTheFurries_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Fury of the Furries</name>
		<desc>In Fury of the Furries, you control a cute, round creature called Tiny, who must defeat "the wicked one" who has captured the King, and turned all the Tinies into mindless monsters. Fortunately your Tiny has special powers. It can transform himself into a swimmer, rock eater, fireball spitter, or rope swinger during its quest.

The game takes place on a huge island separated into eight regions: Desert, Lagoon, Forest, Pyramids, Mountains, Factory, Village, and finally the Castle.

For the US release, the title was changed to 'Pac-In-Time'. It's exactly the same game. Only the characters were changed : the not-so-known European Tinies (from the Skweek, Super Skweek, Tiny Skweeks/Brainies/Tinies games) were replaced by the widely known Pac-Man.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mindscape</developer>
		<publisher>Kalisto</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2FD377F1</hash>
		<image>./media/images/FuryOfTheFurries_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/FuryOfTheFurries_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="91161" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gunship2000_v3.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Gunship 2000</name>
		<desc>Gunship 2000 is a game which achieves the tricky task of balancing technical accuracy with playability. It doesn't bog the player down with endless pages of numbers and statistics, and you can happily bounce your helicopter off the ground without worrying about falling out. It has lots of scope, starting the player off on simple fly-about missions, and giving the opportunity to retire and play general by directing others about. The kind of game that could keep the occasional player going for months.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CE665CF2</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Gunship2000_v3.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Gunship2000_v3.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="103132" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./GuySpy_v1.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Guy Spy and the Crystals of Armageddon</name>
		<desc>Guy Spy is quite easily one of the most eagerly awaited games of the year. From its initiation early on in January, and our special In Development article six months ago, interest has snowballed Ã¢â¬â the question on everyoneÃ¢â¬â¢s lips was: can real gameplay be added to ReadysoftÃ¢â¬â¢s stunning cartoon-quality graphics? Now, more than eighteen months on, the finished product is poised to hit the shelves and revolutionize the world of interactive gaming.

Guy Spy is presented as a cartoon adventure in much the same way as the DragonÃ¢â¬â¢s Lair series before it. In fact, the whole thing has been produced in more or less the same vein as Space Ace but features longer, more playable sections, with the player actually controlling Guy rather than guiding him when necessary. The term Ã¢â¬ËInteractiveÃ¢â¬â¢ when used to describe Guy Spy is still slightly misleading, though, as itÃ¢â¬â¢s more interactive than most games. Although you do exercise control over the character, itÃ¢â¬â¢s still never more than walk left, step right, punch or whatever.

Of the thirteen levels itÃ¢â¬â¢s fair to say that most are enjoyable, but thereÃ¢â¬â¢s only a handful youÃ¢â¬â¢ll want to play again. The best levels have been sensibly placed sporadically to keep the interest up, though, and there are enough of them to keep you coming back for more. Couple these with the fine and other humorous link animations and three difficulty settings, and the game goes a long way to restore credibility to Readysoft gaming.

This is the closest anyone has come to a fully animated and playable adventure and the Canadian-base company deserve enormous credit. ItÃ¢â¬â¢s still not the perfect cartoon-quality game, but I seriously doubt whether a floppy-based Amiga would ever be able to house such a project anyway. That said, though, what Readysoft have achieved here is admirable and itÃ¢â¬â¢s a hefty step in the right direction and one that deserves praise. ItÃ¢â¬â¢s by no means perfect, but give it a whirl regardless.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>ReadySoft</publisher>
		<hash>9856AB35</hash>
		<image>./media/images/GuySpy_v1.0_CDTV.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="91216" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Heimdall2_v1.6_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Heimdall 2 - Into The Hall Of Worlds</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>997053A5</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Heimdall2_v1.6_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="173033" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./IK+_v1.8_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>International Karate</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>88FAB96E</hash>
		<image>./media/images/IK+_v1.8_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="91439" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./JamesPond2_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>James Pond 2 - Codename Robocod</name>
		<desc>In his second adventure James Pond must retrieve the toys Dr Maybe has stolen. Pond has been armed with an Inspector Gadget-style stretch device, which he can use to view higher areas or claw onto ceilings so as to slide across them.

The gameplay takes place across worlds themed around particular types of toys, such as sporting goods, candy and aircraft. The levels scroll sideways, although a small amount of vertical movement is included. On each level Pond must collect 2 penguins and reach the exit, although there are usually multiple exits and lots of secret areas to explore. After completing each pair of two worlds (each of which has three sub levels), a boss must be faced.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vectordean</developer>
		<publisher>Millennium</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>84CB3ADB</hash>
		<image>./media/images/JamesPond2_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/JamesPond2_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="172548" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./JamesPond3_V1.02_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>James Pond 3 - Operation Starfish</name>
		<desc>Unlike the first game of the series, that was a mission-based game, and the second one, where your character had unique abilities such as observing the whole level and growing to unlimited height, James Pond 3 is a standard jump and run platform game. Pond can run very quickly (by holding down the A button) through large levels, which often contain steep mountain sides and other tricky areas. Once again, he has to oppose the evil scientist Maybe and his minions.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Millennium</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B67EA318</hash>
		<image>./media/images/JamesPond3_V1.02_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/JamesPond3_V1.02_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="34165" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./JungleStrike_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Jungle Strike</name>
		<desc>Some time after Operation Desert Strike, Ibn Kilbaba, son of Kilbaba S.R, threatens to annihilate America. After his father was killed, the people who were under his control, sent his son running off, along with his father's money and nuclear weapons program. Kilbaba, more ruthless than his father, longs for revenge of his father's death and decides to shed the blood of those who killed him, the Americans. Already armed, Kilbaba hires Carlos Ortega to help him set up his Nuclear Weapons program, deep in South America. Carlos Ortega, the world's most notorious druglord, also yearns to seek revenge. With his own private army, armed with the most hi-tech weapons, he's ready to fight America at all costs. 

Because of this threat, you're hired again to battle these two characters, following their paths in the jungles of South America. Armed with the Commache, numerous other vehicles, and destructive weapons, you must take out their private army. Blow up the enemy with your hellfires, hydras, chain guns. Use the watercraft to launch mines at enemy ships. Pull off a drive-by on the enemy with guns on the side. Take out the evil duo and forever rid this threat.....in the jungle!
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>03C17503</hash>
		<image>./media/images/JungleStrike_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/JungleStrike_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="34166" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./KidChaos_v1.1b_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Kid Chaos</name>
		<desc>Kid Chaos is transported from the stone age into an unknown world by evil scientists from the future. Now he must fight his way through artificial environments such as the Secret Garden, Toxic Wasteland, Toy Factory, Techno Fortress, and the Ruined City to reach the time machine that can transport him back home.

Kid does this by running through the level, destroying all wildlife and several destruction targets, then leave the level by the exit door, which remain closed until Kid has destroyed all destruction targets. He destroys by swinging his club in the air and hitting them. He can also whiz if he's running fast, which enable him to discover hidden passages through walls that usually contain apples and power-ups. These are also found if Kid manages to jump really high in the air and lands on a platform that usually lead to secret passages.

There are five levels and four sections to complete in all of them (a total of twenty levels) and Kid start each level with three lives. During the level, if he loses health just by touching wildlife, or if the time expires, he is warped out of the level, loses a life, and has to restart the level at the checkpoints he passes through. His health can be restored either by waiting for the health meter to reach 99 (the boring way) or collecting apples (the smart way), but as Kid progresses further throughout the game, these apples become rare as well as his destruction targets. 

Once he leaves a level, Kid is given a statistics screen, telling him the percentage of destruction he has caused, how much wildlife he has killed, how many apples he collected, and other extras. These "extras" probably include how much more of his destruction targets he broke beyond the requirement.

As mentioned earlier, if Kid jumps really high to reach a platform, he can get power-ups, giving him such wonderful things like extra lives, extra time, or extra health. He can also collect a life token. If he manages to find three life tokens within the same section, then he is awarded an extra life as well.

Every fourth level, Kid will be faced with a challenge, and the object of these is usually to kill something, but there's always a catch for these challenges. For example, in Toy Factory, he has to shoot teddy bears at least ten times to blow them up, while avoiding shooting at ducks; and in Techno Fortress, he's presented with a game similar to Space Invaders, but only this time, there are no barriers. 

Kid Chaos starts off easily, but the further he progresses in the game, the higher the damage factor. Early in the game, he is allowed to hit so much wildlife before he loses a life, but as he progresses through each level, he can't afford to be hit not even once. Some levels in the game are quite tricky. Some levels require him to race through the level under a very strict time limit, while others contain a huge destruction target and he can't afford to miss any of these targets.

The game uses a password system, that allows you to resume at the start of each level. In terms of the gameplay, one of the cheats say it all.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magnetic Fields</developer>
		<publisher>Magnetic Fields</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F065DF9E</hash>
		<image>./media/images/KidChaos_v1.1b_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/KidChaos_v1.1b_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="89105" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kingpin_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Kingpin : Arcade Sports Bowling</name>
		<desc>Kingpin: Arcade Sports Bowling is a bowling game with support for up to 6 players, who can be human or CPU-controlled. Player statistics can be built up as you play.

On the bottom right of the bowling alley screen there is a power gauge that can be altered pressing the Up and Down keyboard arrow keys / joypad buttons. Pressing the Left and Right keys changes the position of your avatar, and hitting Enter / fire makes a small moving arrow appear in the bowling lane. It shows the direction your character will throw the ball when you hit Enter / fire again.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Team 17</publisher>
		<hash>F92C3DCC</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Kingpin_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="91659" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Legends_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Legends</name>
		<desc>The premise of the Zelda style game is that a hero with a mission (rescue princess, free lands, destroy evil - that sort of thing) sets off on a voyage of discovery through different 'lands' or 'zones'. Picking up weapons along the way it ends up being a cross between a Commando style game and an adventure. Yes, you have to shoot or beat things roundly about the head with swords and like, but you also have to collect an inventory, talk to people and solve puzzles. Legends fits all of the above criteria. Give someone an object for a favour? Yes. this game is all about trading too.

Life is a precious thing in Legends. You have a certain number of continues, but there is no facility to save a game in the middle of a level, which is frustrating. One of Legends' great advantages is that you have four worlds to explore: North American, Egypt, Mediaeval, China and an additional Space Ship level. This provides major variety in terms of gameplay but it also means that once you're used to the enemies in one world everything changes in the next one and you start getting killed too easily.

Another annoying point about Legends is that the weapons are a bit weedy and the enemies are too persistent at times. This means that you can spend far too long high-tailing it out of situations without having enough chance to stand and fight, which I always find most enjoyable.

This is a step above Speris, and those who have boon searching for Zelda on an A1200 or A4000 need look no further. With various sub games, mazes and the like there is a lot of gameplay in here, and even though the various attempts at humour seem to fall flat (on me at least) it's still a fun adventure.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Guildhall</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A506CA55</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Legends_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Legends_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33248" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lemmings_v1.2_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Lemmings</name>
		<desc>Your task is to rescue the Lemmings across 120 levels of fast-paced puzzling. These creatures simply walk blindly through the world in the hope of reaching safety at the end of the level - unfortunately these levels include steep drops, gaps in the ground, barriers and rivers amongst other hazards.

You are in control not of any individual Lemming, but of a cross-hair, which can be moved over any of the Lemmings. Along the bottom are a selection of functions which can be assigned to a Lemming, including climbing, floating and bashing. You must click to select the appropriate function, then click on the Lemming to activate it. Each level has a different range of skills on offer, a different amount of Lemmings, and a different percentage target in order to progress.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>DBCCCCD8</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Lemmings_v1.2_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Lemmings_v1.2_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173038" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./LostVikings_v2.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Lost Vikings</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>492DB217</hash>
		<image>./media/images/LostVikings_v2.0_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="173039" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lotus_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Lotus</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>5E61CC52</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Lotus_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="173040" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./LunarC_v1.0b_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Lunar C</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>62F41A25</hash>
		<image>./media/images/LunarC_v1.0b_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="91826" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./MarvinsMarvellousAdventure_v1.01_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Marvin's Marvellous Adventure</name>
		<desc>One of the most console-style platformers ever seen on the Amiga, Marvin has approximately 60 levels to battle through. There are stars to collect, extra lives on offer, slides, tubes, ladders, caterpillars to move across, and bonus fruit to collect.

The levels are inhabited by typical enemies, some of which are killed by jumping on their heads, while others must be kicked or shot (once you collect a weapon).

Many of the annoyances which plague platform games, such as blind jumps and spikes appearing at random, are deliberately absent from this. The graphics are intentionally cute, using the AGA chip-set for 256 colours.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<publisher>20th Century Fox</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C8C39ACB</hash>
		<image>./media/images/MarvinsMarvellousAdventure_v1.01_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="34310" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./MeanArenas_v1.0b_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Mean Arenas</name>
		<desc>You have entered a game show where you need to collect all gold coins scattered throughout the 22 arenas in order to enter the next one. There are four types of arenas: "Robo Zones", "Dungeon Zones", "Rainbow Zones", and "Starship Zones". Besides the gold coins, each arena is filled with monsters, hazards, and weapons which you must look out for. Use the map to help you locate these.

As you progress through the arenas, there are new challenges which you must face such as multi-level arenas, locked doors and passages, slippery surfaces, and much more. Also scattered throughout the arenas is the letter "B", which when collected will award you a letter that make up the word CREDIT. When you have formed the word, you will be awarded an extra credit. Besides the standard arenas, there are also speed arenas, which are more difficult than the others. The object of these arenas is to get past more obstacles and gather as many coins as you can before the time expires.

In each arena, you will receive messages from time to time, as well as a password, which you can enter to resume that game from that arena.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nite Time Games</developer>
		<publisher>ICE</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>4177CF06</hash>
		<image>./media/images/MeanArenas_v1.0b_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/MeanArenas_v1.0b_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="91998" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Morph_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Morph</name>
		<desc>Young Morris Rolph has been trapped in limbo due to a malfunction on Dr Krankenpot's new teleport machine (how come characters with German-sounding names in computer games and films are always evil or stupid? Even Darth Vader sounds German.). Now he's been split into his 4 component parts, represented by liquid, gas, a hard ball and a bouncy ball, and he must get through 24 levels (36 on the special A1200 version - mirroring the game's plot-line of improved technology causing more problems for Morris) to retrieve the parts of the machine so it can be rebuilt to bring him back to life.

The gameplay is vaguely influenced by Lemmings, as the levels are populated by lots of points which can't be crossed in all forms - walls, fires, gaps, thornbushes and suchlike. You get a set number of transformations on each level, although extra ones can be picked up at times, and there are heaters and freezers dotted around which cause transformations in some states. All this is done against a time limit. Like Lemmings 2, you can take on the next level in each of the worlds at any time, so you have to be stuck 4 times before you can't progress.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Millenium Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Millenium Interactive</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>863E2DF3</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Morph_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Morph_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173044" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Myth_v1.3a_System3_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Myth System 3</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>031A3863</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Myth_v1.3a_System3_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="34075" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./NaughtyOnes_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Naughty Ones</name>
		<desc>The Naughty Ones come under your control in this old-fashioned platform game. Each screen is separate from the others, and involves trying to collect a key and then progress through the exit. Enemies are best dealt with by shooting one of your longer-range weapons towards them and waiting for it to hit them - this will release at least one coin, for points. Improved weapons can be collected, each of which functions for a limited number of shots.  Bonus items are often located in the more precarious parts of the level, leading you to choose whether to risk losing a life, and going back to the start of the screen (although previously killed creatures remain dead when you lose a life)
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Melon Dezign</developer>
		<publisher>Interactivision</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D1EE94EA</hash>
		<image>./media/images/NaughtyOnes_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/NaughtyOnes_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="172540" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./NickFaldosChampionshipGolf_v2.1b_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Nick Faldo's Championship Golf</name>
		<desc>Arc Developments created a 3D game world called Reality3 for this simulation, licensed around one of Britain's top players. There are two courses, plus a hidden 9-hole course on Mars with reduced gravity, with match play and stroke play options against one of 8 varied-difficulty computer players.

The control system is quite unusual, as the strength of the shot is chosen before you start the swing, but you have to click within a range to activate the shot, and this range is narrower if your shot is intended to be more powerful. An extra click can be made to add wrist snap, which increases the shot's power. The wind calculation is more complicated than most games of the era, and the rough is harder to play out of than usual, as you can't make slight stance adjustments easily.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sport</developer>
		<publisher>Sport</publisher>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<hash>07D19048</hash>
		<image>./media/images/NickFaldosChampionshipGolf_v2.1b_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="92176" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Oscar_v1.8_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Oscar</name>
		<desc>Your name is Oscar. You have to run and jump through 7 Levels in Hollywood-style (Science Fiction, Western, Horror, Cartoons, Dino, Detective and Gameshow) to find Oscars (yes  the Academy Award!). 

If you have enough Oscars you solve the level. You can choose the levels in every order you want. In the levels you must jump on platforms to discover the level. 

You kill the enemies by jumping on them. Some of them lose a power up like invulnerable or a superjump. You can also find a JoJo to break down walls or using as ladder. Two creatures are no opponents. First the white rabbit. He gives you a extra continue. Second a red elephant. Touch him for using as save point in level.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flair Software</developer>
		<publisher>Flair Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>93F06E8A</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Oscar_v1.8_CD32_NTSC.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Oscar_v1.8_CD32_NTSC.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="34243" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./PGAEuropeanTour_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>PGA European Tour</name>
		<desc>European Tour is best thought of as a remake of the original game, rather than a sequel as such. It features 5 courses from across Europe, and 60 top European pros, rather than the US-leaned lineup of the original. The graphics are much more detailed and colorful, as you'd expect considering the intervening years of advances in programming skill.

The control system is the standard three-click method used in most golf games, but you can now define intended draw/fade levels in advance of playing the shot, so that a perfect aim leads to a measured effect, and an imperfect one exaggerating the effect.

As well as the Stroke Play games of the original (where you count the total score across the whole round of 18 holes, and compare this to your opponent), there are also Match Play (where the aim is to win as many individual holes as possible) and Skins (the same, but with money) modes as well.
</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8DD9B422</hash>
		<image>./media/images/PGAEuropeanTour_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/PGAEuropeanTour_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="92290" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./PierreLeChefIsOutToLunch_v2.3_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Pierre Le Chef Is... Out To Lunch</name>
		<desc>Pierre Le Chef is famed worldwide for his mouth-watering recipes involving the freshest ingredients. So, when the vegetables start attempting to run away from him, he has no choice but to chase after them.

Out to Lunch is a platform game set across 6 countries, starting off in Switzerland and finishing in Paris. To recollect the vegetables he must first stun them, either by firing at them or jumping on them, then walk over them, in a manner similar to Fire &amp; Ice. Unusually, the game was converted from the SNES to the Amiga, not the other way around.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>EA5A3A45</hash>
		<image>./media/images/PierreLeChefIsOutToLunch_v2.3_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/PierreLeChefIsOutToLunch_v2.3_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="92293" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./PinballFantasies_v2.7_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Pinball Fantasies</name>
		<desc>After the success of Pinball Dreams on several systems, a sequel featuring four new tables was created. The gameplay is much the same as the first game, with realistic physics, multi-player options and a high score table to aim for. The tables are Partyland, Speed Devils, Billion Dollar Gameshow and Stones 'n' Bones, taking in a funfair, racing cars, a tacky game-show, and a graveyard. Each one has a range of ramps, combos, light sequences and targets to shoot, as well as general themes which are less influenced by real tables than those in Pinball Dreams.
</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>20th Century Fox</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Illusions</publisher>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<hash>D2F6B93F</hash>
		<image>./media/images/PinballFantasies_v2.7_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/PinballFantasies_v2.7_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="92297" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./PinballIllusions_v2.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Pinball Illusions</name>
		<desc>Pinball Illusions is the successor to the Pinball Fantasies, using an upgraded game engine. The tables are Babewatch, Law &amp; Justice, Extreme Sports and (on PC CD versions) The Vikings. These contain ramps, bonus areas and combo sequences to set up. All the artwork were produced in true 256 colors from the ground up for AGA Amigas and the PC, rather than originating in 32 colors on older Amigas.

New to this version is multiball: Pinball Illusions supports up to six balls simultaneously, in which case it switches to high resolution mode. CD versions use CD audio for music.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>20th Century Fox</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Illusions</publisher>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<hash>619C2281</hash>
		<image>./media/images/PinballIllusions_v2.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/PinballIllusions_v2.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="172656" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./PiratesGold_v2.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Pirates! Gold</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>1D1A88D5</hash>
		<image>./media/images/PiratesGold_v2.2_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="105179" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./PowerPinball_v1.1_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Power Pinball</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>KarmaSoft</publisher>
		<hash>39C5E815</hash>
		<image>./media/images/PowerPinball_v1.1_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/PowerPinball_v1.1_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33511" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Prehistorik_v2.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Prehistorik</name>
		<desc>Prehistorik is a side-view platform game with superficial similarity to Chuck Rock, although the games were developed simultaneously in different countries. You control a neanderthal who must march through hostile pre-historic environments seeking food and keeping himself safe. Some food can be found in caves, but it mainly exists in living animal forms.

These include fire-breathing Pyro-Tax dragons, the Turtosaurus, and the Bad Bat. Each of these must be clubbed to death, some taking up to 5 hits, and then walked over. Some other enemies are indestructible, with the monkeys who throw coconuts at you particularly fiendish.

You will have to complete the level within the time limit, and avoid contact with these foes. However, bombs and improved weapons can be collected, as can extra lives, time bonuses and an improved jump.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titus</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>471EF4D5</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Prehistorik_v2.0_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Prehistorik_v2.0_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173049" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Premiere_v2.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Premiere</name>
		<desc>Six film reels have been stolen from your film studios by a rival company. In this platform game, your mission is to rescue from within the sets and backstage rooms they have been hidden in. Backstage sections are entered through doors, and weapons can often be collected in these.

The sets are themed around six different genres of film, and the backdrops, weapons and enemies fit these sections. There is a slapstick comedy played out in black and white (complete with greyscale background) a cartoon  with lots of Road Runnering and goofy facial expressions, a Wild West romp, Sci-Fi complete with aliens, and so on. After each platform level you will have to pass through a film scene - piloting a runaway mine-cart, navigating a scrolling shoot 'em up level, or similar.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The 8th Day</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>BF8E4DCA</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Premiere_v2.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Premiere_v2.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173051" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ProjectXSE_v1.5_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Project Xse</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>D70BB451</hash>
		<image>./media/images/ProjectXSE_v1.5_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="190752" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./PsychoKiller_v1.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Psycho Killer</name>
		<desc>Psycho Killer is an adventure game with the interaction restricted to "jumping" from picture to picture, occasionally clicking on the screen in order to find objects that are possible to interact with. As in other interactive movies, some parts presented as video sequences, during which the player has to make the correct action quickly in order to succeed.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Delta 4 Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>On-Line Interactive</publisher>
		<hash>37BFDCE8</hash>
		<image>./media/images/PsychoKiller_v1.0_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/PsychoKiller_v1.0_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="34344" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./QuikTheThunderRabbit_v1.2a_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Quik : The Thunder Rabbit</name>
		<desc>This platform game has much in common with console games of the era. There are 4 worlds including ice, desert and fields, and have multiple routes through. The bad guys are cutesy. You get past them by spinning at them, although jumping over them is often sufficient. Power-ups on offer include speed ups, energy, food and water (Quiks thirst and hunger are measured separately). The bonus levels involve jumping through time, by finding the right doors.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CB3049B1</hash>
		<image>./media/images/QuikTheThunderRabbit_v1.2a_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/QuikTheThunderRabbit_v1.2a_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173053" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Qwak_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Qwak</name>
		<desc>In this game, you play a duck and the object of the game is to get the highest score without losing all your lives. This can be achieved by getting all the fruit and gems in the level, or killing off enemies. There are 80 levels to complete and once you complete all of them, the levels are repeated. 

You exit each level by collecting all the gold keys then entering through the door that opens. You have a certain amount of time to complete the level before spikes fall down the level. There are eight areas, all consisting of ten levels. At the end of each area, there is a guardian waiting for you, and again, you have a certain amount of time to defeat them.

You kill enemies by throwing orange-colored eggs at them, and in the earlier levels, they go down in one or two shots, but in later levels, you'll find out that all of them take more than two shots to bring down, so your orange balls would be useless here. The solution is to get a special power-up that will give you chocolate eggs.

Besides gold keys, you can also collect silver keys. This lets you unlock a gate, giving you access to more shots or power-ups. There are also booby traps in the level, such as spikes, and some parts of a level are blocked off by spikes. Get a mushroom and they turn into flowers that you can pick up. Beware, getting another mushroom will make them turn into spikes again. 

Apart from the normal levels, there are challenges where you have to complete a level and get all the fruit as you can under a 20-second time limit. Depending on gameplay, there are  also tricks where the last key you have to get flies away and you have to catch it. Other tricks include turning on the lights to see enemies, and running away from the "happy ghost". You'll receive bonus points at the end of the level if you manage to collect every gem in the level.

Qwak can be played as either a one or two player game. The game was released at budget price, and later on a CD double pack with Alien Breed '92.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Team 17</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>1A797885</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Qwak_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Qwak_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94337" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Raffles_v1.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Raffles</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Edge, The</publisher>
		<hash>C3838456</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Raffles_v1.0_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Raffles_v1.0_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33466" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./RiseOfTheRobots_v1.3_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Rise of the Robots</name>
		<desc>Rise of the Robots emerges from the hype and reveals itself as a good-looking but rather unwieldy beat-em-up. The game, in all of the currently available versions, is just not that good.

In terms of pure beat-em-up action, Rise of the Robots is outclassed by the barely-better-than-16-bit BODY BLOWS games. ROTR is quite poor in the "special moves" area of beat-em-up gaming. The graphics? Well... the animations are good. The characters, when still, look very good too. When moving they are anything but realistic looking. Their movements are jerky and very repetitive. What's different in each version? Not a lot. All of them suffer from the poor control and jerky animation.

The non-AGA version takes less time to install on the hard drive than the AGA version because some of the Ã¢â¬ÅcinematicsÃ¢â¬Â have been taken out. They're not much of a loss really. This version also looks pretty good considering the number of colors onscreen. It seems to play a tad faster too.

Disappointment is the key word here. The game promised so much and delivered so little. I guess one good thing is that, for once, the PC suffers from the exact same problems.</desc>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Time Warner Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Mirage - Time Warner</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D3D6315E</hash>
		<image>./media/images/RiseOfTheRobots_v1.3_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/RiseOfTheRobots_v1.3_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="102741" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SabreTeam_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Sabre Team</name>
		<desc>A Sabre Team is a squad of four elite soldiers charged with some of the toughest hostage-rescue, building-storming and the like that Western forces have ever attempted. In this turn-based strategic simulation you must choose a team of four of these from the 8 available, and take them to victory in five increasingly tough missions. Even before you get into the main gameplay, there is a lot of strategy involved in choosing weaponry, as they make different amounts of noise when used (reducing the stealth potential) and their ammunition is of varying weight.

In each turn you have limited action points per soldier, which must be used for all movement, firing and reloading moves. The maps are viewed isometrically, with a compass used to indicate the directions of movement, and where the incoming fire emanated from.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krisalis Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Krisalis Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<hash>0BDD2A07</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SabreTeam_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/SabreTeam_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33524" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SensibleSoccerInternationalEdition_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Sensible Soccer : International Edition, World Cha</name>
		<desc>Sensible World of Soccer sur Amiga est une version améliorée du jeu de football. Celle-ci comprend a peu près toutes les divisions et clubs de tous les pays pour la saison 95. Tout y est authentique grâce à tous les noms officiels. Vous pouvez aussi gérer plusieurs équipes pour les mener à la victoire.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renegade Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sensible Software</publisher>
		<hash>5E91C818</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SensibleSoccerInternationalEdition_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/SensibleSoccerInternationalEdition_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33423" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ShadowFighter_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Shadow Fighter</name>
		<desc>Shadow Fighter was one of the few Mortal Kombat influenced beat 'em ups released for the Amiga. There are 16 fighters, each with their own home country and arena, plus Pupazz, a puppet you could repeatedly attack to practice moves. The usual sequence of best-of-3 fights is on offer, with variable difficulty and optional blood. The control system is designed around a one-button controller, but still offers 25 moves for each player, with special moves executed by spinning the joystick round 180 degrees. Each arena features multi-layer parallax, with up to 80 colors.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beat'em All</developer>
		<publisher>Beat'em All</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3FCC0871</hash>
		<image>./media/images/ShadowFighter_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/ShadowFighter_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33264" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SimCity_v1.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>SimCity</name>
		<desc>SimCity sets you as the mayor of a new municipality, with the responsibility of building and maintaining a place where citizens can move to and work and be happy. The first task is to place essentials such as housing, transport links, schools, factories and shops. There are 50 types of these, allowing for homes of all standards and different types of businesses. Make sure to consider which sites are effective for which tasks. Some power sources pollute, others don't but are more expensive. Taxes must be raised to ensure an income, and then portions allocated to public services such as policing and roads. Earthquakes, floods and fires are all emergency situations that must be dealt to contain any damage.

Successful mayoring will cause the small village to grow into a town, then a city and finally a metropolis. As the city's size grows so do it's needs. Commercial buildings may suddenly find that they need an airport to expand trade, or housing may find itself changing rapidly as vast amounts of people come and leave.

The game also includes 8 pre-defined time-limited scenarios, with specific challenges and targets. The environment varies in each game (especially if you have the Terrain Editor add on), and this should affect your choices.
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19891023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxis</developer>
		<publisher>Maxis</publisher>
		<hash>3E4B123C</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SimCity_v1.0_CDTV.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="92911" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SkeletonKrew_v2.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Skeleton Krew</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>3367E65E</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SkeletonKrew_v2.0_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="34519" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SuperSkidmarks_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Skidmarks Racer Issue 1</name>
		<desc>A vague descendant of Super Sprint with a mass of features, and one of the last multi-format games to have roots on the Amiga.

A multitude of cars are available, ranging from F1 cars and Sportscars to Minis and VWs were on offer, with the option to have up to 8 of these on more powerful machines - with up to 3 different models of car. You could link 2 Amiga 1200s (or faster) and use them to display the track across 2 separate screens. There were two novelty options of sorts as well - motorized cows, and the chance to have the cars pulling caravans as you race - using the caravan to push an opponent off-line was a skill worth mastering. 

24 circuits are provided, all of them with walls around them to ensure crash-bang-wallop racing, and most of them have parts which cross with other parts, making collisions possible if you're much ahead of (or behind) other cars (fortunately there's no car damage). They can be raced forwards or backwards - perhaps the first game with this feature available. You could either run single races, or one of the in-built championships - one for each car, across a specially selected set of tracks.

The customizable nature of the game goes even further - the number of laps can be set, as can the colour and power of the cars. As you repeatedly race a track, the markings on the course are eroded by the cars running over them.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Guildhall Leisure Service</developer>
		<publisher>Acid</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>53920F93</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SuperSkidmarks_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/SuperSkidmarks_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33740" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SoccerKid_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Soccer Kid</name>
		<desc>Aliens attempting to steal the World Cup have crashed as they tried to flee, and the Cup has been broken, its pieces scattered around the globe. As Soccer Kid, you must retrieve it. During your journey you will visit Britain, Italy, Russia, Japan, and finally the States.

Soccer Kid is a platform game with some unique elements.  As the name implies, you have to kill your enemies with your ball. Football-style tricks of keeping the ball in the air and under control are especially useful - headers and overhead kicks can be played with practice. You gain access to the pieces by collecting 11 Player Cards across each world.

There is a saving feature that gives you the ability to save between each country (but not between individual levels).
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krisalis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Krisalis Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A45C1A62</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SoccerKid_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/SoccerKid_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="172426" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Speedball2_v2.3_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Speedball 2</name>
		<desc>Speedball 2 sur Amiga est un titre qui oppose deux équipes dans un sport futuriste mélangeant football américain et handball. Les joueurs doivent faire entrer une boule en fer dans le but adverse par tous les moyens. Il est autorisé de frapper les adversaires pour se saisir de la balle, et les faire sortir sur blessure rapporte autant de points qu'un but.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imageworks</developer>
		<publisher>The Bitmap Brothers</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>08D8E161</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Speedball2_v2.3_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Speedball2_v2.3_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="93061" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SperisLegacy_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Speris Legacy, The</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Team 17</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>AA351238</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SperisLegacy_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="102704" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SphericalWorlds_v1.0.1_CD.lha</path>
		<name>Spherical Worlds</name>
		<desc>Spherical Worlds, as the name doesn't imply, is a two-dimensional adventure in which you take control of a spherical droid whose mission it is to roam the various sectors of a space station.

On loading the game, you are presented with just two options: Start Game or Enter Teleport Code. The game itself is fairly slow going - your spherical battle droid has to skid about a derelict space station, avoiding holes, sliding over ice, shooting other little robots and things, while searching for the exit to the next level. On level two, it gets harder...

There's not much in Spherical Worlds to get you hooked - yes, you can upgrade your weapons and you get to do all sorts of exciting things like use teleports and collect keys - but the graphics are small and uneventful, as is the gameplay. It's okay in a sub Alien Breed 1 and 2 sort of way, and there are a few marginally distracting moments, but it doesn't hold your attention for long.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>neo</publisher>
		<hash>44D94301</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SphericalWorlds_v1.0.1_CD.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="102807" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./StreetRacer_v1.5_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Street Racer</name>
		<desc>Street Racer is a go-kart racing game which combines racing with violence.

Characters can strike opponents with their fists and must avoid explosives littered around the track. The game's characters possess unique power-ups such as the Screaming Banshee, Batmobile, magic carpet and tri-plane.

The game features the ability to race various championships beginning with the Bronze Championship and moving on to progressively more difficult competitions. An alternative one-on-one mode is also available. The game awards points for final race positions, with bonus points given for accolades such as fastest lap. The competitor with the most points after all races wins the Championship. The game includes a "Rumble" mode in which players attempt to force opponents from an arena. The "Soccer" mode is a free-for-all football match with one goal and in which players tackle by colliding with the opponent.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>AA59D397</hash>
		<image>./media/images/StreetRacer_v1.5_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="105600" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./StripPot_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Strip Pot</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Fin Soft</publisher>
		<hash>ACC29AFC</hash>
		<image>./media/images/StripPot_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/StripPot_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="39339" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Subwar2050_v1.3_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>SubWar 2050</name>
		<desc>The year is 2050. Ocean is the next frontier, and war inevitably reached there. As an independent mercenary working for a corporate conglomerate, you are to pilot the latest fighter subs to protect the corporate interests, and rewarded with cold hard cash. With 5 different theater of operations (of varying difficulty) and an interesting mix of aerial and submarine tactics, this game can be described as Strike Commander under the sea, without the narrative.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Particle Systems Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>71E93A2F</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Subwar2050_v1.3_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="173060" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SuperPutty_v1.2a_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Super Putty</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>EFA6C872</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SuperPutty_v1.2a_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="93262" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SuperStreetFighter2Turbo_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II Turbo</name>
		<desc>Fighting game ported from the classic and wildly popular "Street Fighter 2" franchise.  Choose from a variety of characters and use their fighting skills to beat opponents and become the world champion fighter.

Advantages over the original Street Fighter 2 include faster fighting speed, 4 new characters, new locations, and more balanced/streamlined moves for the original characters.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GameTek</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>DEF81DD4</hash>
		<image>./media/images/SuperStreetFighter2Turbo_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/SuperStreetFighter2Turbo_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173062" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Superfrog_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Superfrog</name>
		<desc>Superfrog is a one of these rare traditional jump &amp; run games. Youre  surprise  a frog. Your enemies are all animals  like bees, hedgehogs or snails. You have no weapons. The only way to kill the enemies is to jump on them. Every stage has a timelimit. In this limit you have to collect a pretended number of coins.

Each of the 6 worlds has 4 stages. Every stage has a password. After all you can type your name into a hi score table.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Team 17</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FEA6F1E0</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Superfrog_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Superfrog_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173063" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Syndicate_v2.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Syndicate</name>
		<desc>In the future, the world is controlled by a handful of global corporations (syndicates).  You are the Marketing director (hit man) for one of these companies.  It is your job to take control away from the competitors.  The job is not one of diplomacy, but one of brute force and physical control.  Advance your way to the top of the corporation by successfully completing your missions and managing the money you make from your territories.

The gameplay is visually reminiscent of X-Com, with an angled top-down perspective, but it is real time rather than turn based. You have missions ranging from infiltrate and capture, to seek and destroy. In each of these you direct a team of four agents as they move through the world shooting at anything that gets in their way.

You can upgrade and modify your agents, as well as equip them with tools you have researched or liberated from opposing syndicates.  As you complete missions, you gain more funds to use for purchasing agents or researching upgrades and equipment.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B74C4DF5</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Syndicate_v2.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Syndicate_v2.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33262" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ChaosEngine_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>The Chaos Engine</name>
		<desc>Sixteen levels (in four groups of four) await you in this long-developed Bitmap Brothers title. The basic gameplay is similar to Gauntlet, but in an open air setting, with bridges across rivers and such in the maps. The visuals are in the 'metallic and blue' style the Bitmaps appeared to favor.

There were 6 characters available in the game, each with different strengths and weaknesses, and different starting prices. In 2-player mode you each chose a character and played co-operatively, but in one-player games you also choose a character for the computer to control, with its Artificial Intelligence allowing it to open doors, pick up power-ups and take on baddies away from the ones occupying your character.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Bitmap Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>The Bitmap Brothers</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>B09EDA52</hash>
		<image>./media/images/ChaosEngine_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/ChaosEngine_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="34022" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./CurseOfRa_v1.2_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>The Curse of RA</name>
		<desc>Curse of Ra est un puzzle-game sur Amiga. A l'intérieur d'une ancienne pyramide d'Egypte, vous subissez la colère de Ra et vous vous retrouvez transformé en scarabée. Votre seul espoir de retrouver votre forme initiale est de résoudre tous les puzzles et énigmes pour sortir de la pyramide vivant. Un total de 100 niveaux vous attendent ainsi que la possibilité de construire vos propres niveaux.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cybersoft</developer>
		<publisher>Cybersoft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D8E8B71E</hash>
		<image>./media/images/CurseOfRa_v1.2_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/CurseOfRa_v1.2_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="172613" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ThomasTheTankEnginePinball_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Thomas The Tank Engine And Friends - Pinball</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Spidersoft Software</developer>
		<publisher>Alternative Software</publisher>
		<hash>DA674060</hash>
		<image>./media/images/ThomasTheTankEnginePinball_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="34100" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./TinyTroops_v1.2_CD.lha</path>
		<name>Tiny Troops</name>
		<desc>On planet Agaris IV, two races fight for power on an endless war. When the Klutes and the Furfurians' dispute made their planet inhospitable, they needed a new battleground. Their troops where teleported to planet Earth, where everything, they discover, is 100 times bigger. Their battles are thus a small event there, taking place out of the attention of the humans.

Tiny Troops is a real-time strategy game, with gameplay similar to Cannon Fodder. It supports up to 2 players in split-screen mode, and mouse or joystick control. Before starting a level, a screen is shown where the player must select which units are going to be on his troop. There's several types of units (foot soldiers, grenadiers, etc). Clicking the general gives a hint and the main objective of the level (that usually is about killing the enemy and destroying their base). Most of the main game screen is occupied by a scrolling map of the level, with the bottom portion reserved for the control windows (one for the mini-map, other for game options like saving and restarting, a third for unit commands and a final one with unit information or a list of group formations). The player controls the soldiers by clicking on them and selecting orders icons from the command window:

- a fist icon is to attack;

- an upward arrow to select the route;

- a wrench to repair things;

- a shield to stand guard;

- a target to surround the unit.

The game has 65 levels spread on a variety of different terrains (garden, kitchen, etc).
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Vulcan</developer>
		<publisher>Vulcan</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A00AB71F</hash>
		<image>./media/images/TinyTroops_v1.2_CD.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/TinyTroops_v1.2_CD.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="93512" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./TopGear2_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Top Gear 2</name>
		<desc>This third-person racing game resembles Gremlin's earlier Lotus series, in terms of its general look and feel, right down to the text font used in the game. Your task is to race through 16 countries, each of which features four races, with many real-world circuits recreated in incongruous locations (such as the Monza layout in Ayers Rock, and the old Hockenheim in Vancouver). 

These four-race blocks each represent their own mini-championship, in which you race against 19 cars, needing to finish in the top 10 to continue, and with the top 6 scoring points 10-6-4-3-2-1, and the respective amount of money in thousands. This can be spent on various upgrades, ranging from engine to tires (wet and dry) and from shocks (front, side and rear) to gearboxes. The ideal approach is to buy the more expensive versions ASAP, as you get no saving when upgrading. If you win the four-race championship, you get the next password. 

You get a set amount of nitro boost to use during each race, although bonus nitros, money and instant speed-up token appear on many tracks. Hazards such as puddles, barriers and ramps are also frequent.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D3E143E4</hash>
		<image>./media/images/TopGear2_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/TopGear2_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173068" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./TreasureIslandDizzy_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Treasure Island Dizzy</name>
		<desc>This is Dizzy's second adventure. Dizzy is a cute little egg character who must explore the strange magic kingdom that is Treasure Island, solving problems and puzzles in order to escape from there. Dizzy must journey through haunted mines, tree villages, and underwater caverns in order to find hidden treasures. They will be used as bargain items to buy parts for the boat. The secondary goal is to collect 30 coins so he can pay the bribe in order to safely get off the island.



Unlike the other installments in the series the player has only one life without any energy bars to complete the game and is unable to select any particular item from the inventory for use. Items are rolled up through the inventory so the top one is used or dropped.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8E5368E1</hash>
		<image>./media/images/TreasureIslandDizzy_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/TreasureIslandDizzy_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="93590" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Trolls_v1.3_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Trolls</name>
		<desc>This platform game features the small blue-haired cutesy creatures that were popular around the time (although surely not with most computer game buyers?). You play a Troll roaming the levels in the hope of rescuing as many baby trolls as possible - each level gives you a set minimum to retrieve before you can leave via the Pigstop.

Initially you have no weapons, and contact with the nasties costs you energy, but a Yo-Yo can be collected, which can be used not only to kill enemies, but also to smash blocks away and open up paths, and even (with practice) tied to a ledge to allow you to swing across a gap. 

Throughout the levels you will find the letters B,O,N,U,S and G released from bonus balloons or on killing an enemy - if at the end of a level your letters spell out Bonus or Bogus you go to the appropriate extra level. The former has a chance to gain extra lives, the latter must be escaped quickly to avoid losing a life.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flair Software</developer>
		<publisher>Flair Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>26447CBB</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Trolls_v1.3_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Trolls_v1.3_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33509" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Turrican2_v1.4_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Turrican II : The Final Fight</name>
		<desc>Turrican II: The Final Fight is a platformer/shooter as typically seen on consoles, but designed for home computers from the ground up.

Its plot is - naturally - very simple: an evil mega-robot called The Machine attacks the United Planets Ship Avalon 1, slaughtering all who resist. All - except Bren McGuire, who manages to escape and slips into the experimental Turrican bionic armor. As Turrican, he strives to show The Machine who's the boss.

Unlike other games of its type, this game contains three levels of horizontal shooter action in the spirit of R-Type or the developers' own Katakis. Six large worlds are to be explored, where you are basically free to go everywhere you want, since there is no automatic scrolling and the levels are packed with hidden extra lives and weapons. All those levels are very different: the first one in the rock desert is pretty colorful with parallaxing rainbow background and happy music, while the following worlds get darker and darker.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbow Arts Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>09D8908F</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Turrican2_v1.4_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Turrican2_v1.4_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33464" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Turrican_v2.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Turrican</name>
		<desc>Three-headed demon Morgul has been influencing people's dreams to create nightmares, but more recently these nightmares have become real. Only Turrican can save them in this fast paced side scrolling shoot-em up. It features 5 worlds and 13 levels of challenging gameplay.

Gameplay is conceptually simple: just jump, shoot and explore. However, this game puts a lot of emphasis on finding and using the 10 different weapons Turrican can collect.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts Software</developer>
		<publisher>Factor 5</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>13531AAB</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Turrican_v2.0_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Turrican_v2.0_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="93642" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./UFOEnemyUnknown_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Ufo - Enemy Unknown</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3B0402B0</hash>
		<image>./media/images/UFOEnemyUnknown_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="190751" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./UltimateBodyBlows_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Ultimate Body Blows</name>
		<desc>A compilation of the original fighting game "Body Blows" and its sequel, available only for Amiga, "Body Blows Galactic". The game combines everything from its predecessors and adds more colors, improved graphics and music, more backgrounds and endings, giving the player a total of 22 characters (including the invincible Max and his true self, the Terminator T17) and many fixes.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team17 Software</developer>
		<publisher>Team17 Software</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>2AC59585</hash>
		<image>./media/images/UltimateBodyBlows_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/UltimateBodyBlows_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="190794" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./UltimateXTremeRacing_v1.1_AGA_CD.lha</path>
		<name>Ultimate Xtreme Racing</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silltunna</developer>
		<publisher>Alive</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>9C345B69</hash>
		<image>./media/images/UltimateXTremeRacing_v1.1_AGA_CD.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="173069" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Universe_v1.3_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Universe</name>
		<desc>You are Boris Verne, a normal guy who is been cast in a parallel universe because of your uncle's Virtual Dimension Inducer. There you'll have to find the fabled lost star as well as a way to defeat the Golden King...
This is a classic old-style adventure game with a point&amp;click interface. It uses the Rotoscope system to manage game characters and scores really beautiful 256-colour graphic.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1142E025</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Universe_v1.3_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Universe_v1.3_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="173071" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./VirtualKarting2_v1.1_AGA_CD.lha</path>
		<name>Virtual Karting 2</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<hash>90B70B7B</hash>
		<image>./media/images/VirtualKarting2_v1.1_AGA_CD.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="172933" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./WingCommander_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Wing Commander</name>
		<desc>The Confederation have been at war with the Kilrathi for the past 20 years, and you're just now joining the Vega campaign. You're a 2nd Lieutenant just out of the Academy, with some good work under your belt. You're posted to Tiger's Claw, the flagship of the Confederation Fleet.  Will you help the Confederation to victory, or go down in infamy? 

Wing Commander is a space combat simulator interspersed with shipboard dialogs. Onboard the ship, you can save/load game, visit the bar to get the latest gossip, or go on to the next mission briefing, and the 3D space combat part. 

The 3D space combat have you sitting in the cockpit, where you control the craft like roll, turn, up/down, afterburner, as well as fire guns and launch missiles. There are four different crafts on the Confed side, each with different flight characteristics and armament. You will have a wingman on each mission, and you should keep the wingman alive as the wingman will help you if you issue the right orders. You can also taunt the enemy. You'll be fighting several different types of enemy fighters and capital ships, and even combat a few Kilrathi aces. 

When the mission is complete, land back onboard the ship and get ready for the next one. The campaign tree have both winning and losing paths. 

Wing Commander featured a hybrid bitmap/3D graphics  engine that allowed even 286's to display detailed 3D graphics to an extent never before possible. With EMS available, it can display even more detailed graphics and in-cockpit animations.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mindscape</developer>
		<publisher>Origin Systems</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E73D19D0</hash>
		<image>./media/images/WingCommander_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="173072" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Worms_v1.0_CD32_1MB.lha</path>
		<name>Worms</name>
		<desc>Worms is a turn-based strategy game. It features up to 4 teams of 4 worms, aiming to destroy the others on a generated terrain. Each worm has 100 hit points, and dies when his hit points fall to 0. Upon death, a worm explodes, causing damage to everyone around.

Gameplay is turn-based. Each turn, the player can control one specific worm from his team. The worm can crawl left and right or jump. However, there is a time limit to make a move; also, if the worm falls from a great height, it loses health and the turn ends immediately; and if a worm falls into water or offscreen, it dies. Each turn, a worm can also make a single attack: the player can aim up and down, choose a weapon and then fire it. After attacking, the turn ends. 

There's a lot of weapons available - the standard ones as bazookas (which is affected by the (random) wind settings and gravity) and grenades. The others include a Fire Punch, dynamite, air strikes, and utilities such as ropes and girders.

There are 10 styles of terrain, ranging from forests and deserts to Candy land and the moon (complete with affected gravity). Shots leave craters in the ground, and complex tunnels can be formed.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Team 17</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>2EA7C0E3</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Worms_v1.0_CD32_2MB.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Worms_v1.0_CD32_2MB.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="102569" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./WrathOfTheDemon_v1.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Wrath of the Demon</name>
		<desc>The mighty wizard Anthrax, in an attempt to usurp authority over the kingdom, has summoned a horrifying Demon. The Demon makes good on his chartered task by summoning a horde of monsters to lay waste to the kingdom at large. Fortuitously, a random stranger is strolling nearby the kingdom and realizes that only he can beat back the foul creatures.

After some encouragement from the king, the adventurer begins the game on horseback, jumping over obstacles, beating flying creatures, and collecting potions on the ground. Afterward, the hero must proceed on foot through side-scrolling platforming levels, destroying creatures with his blade as well as collecting potions and additional weapons he will find on his deadly quest.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>ReadySoft</publisher>
		<hash>F875805E</hash>
		<image>./media/images/WrathOfTheDemon_v1.0_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/WrathOfTheDemon_v1.0_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="33381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Xenon2_v1.7_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Xenon 2 : Megablast</name>
		<desc>Xenon 2: Megablast is vertically scrolling space shooter, in which you have to pass several levels, filled with waves of enemies, that all end with a level boss creature. Each group of enemies you destroy grants you a cash reward and every once in a while you enter Colin's Bargain Basement, where you can use this cash to purchase upgrades for your ship like better weapons, speed &amp; health upgrades etc. Some upgrades can also be picked up during the levels.The first part of the game has an organic feel to it, while the second part of the game features mechanical enemies. As there are some maze-like sections with dead-ends in the game, your spaceship scrolls backwards when you keep pressing the down key.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bitmap Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Image Works</publisher>
		<hash>2E37F22A</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Xenon2_v1.7_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Xenon2_v1.7_CDTV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="93975" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Zool_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Zool - Ninja Of The 'nth' Dimension</name>
		<desc>His name is Zool. He is a Ninja in the 2345th dimension, 6 worlds each with 3 stages. 

In this platformer, you can run, jump, climb walls and shoot the enemies. In the levels are also some power-ups for Zool. There are life-spending hearts, smart bombs, shields, more powerful jump-skill and a twin Zool. This "twin" makes all your motions a few seconds after you do.

In the options you can change the difficulty and the game-speed two times, the continues and the background music (Rock or Funk).
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F1E2B138</hash>
		<image>./media/images/Zool_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Zool_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AlienBreed3D_v1.2_NoMusic_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Alien Breed 3D (No Music)</name>
		<desc>Team 17 were famed for pushing the Amiga to its limits, with a string of hits stretching back to 1991. The first major one was Alien Breed, a Gauntlet-style shoot 'em up which had already spawned three sequels, including a budget-priced Special Edition.

This release was in a similar vein, but set into a 3D context, making for the Amiga's first big Doom-style game. The 3D engine uses fairly small screen graphics, but these include full floors and ceilings with detailed shading, doors, vertical position variations, lifts and transporters. The CD version includes extra atmospheric sound, while fast processors and extra FastRAM are also supported.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/AlienBreed3D_v1.2_NoMusic_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/AlienBreed3D_v1.2_NoMusic_CD32.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Team 17 - Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BattleChess_v1.1_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Battle Chess (CD TV)</name>
		<desc>Battle Chess is a quite typical chess game, but it comes with a twist: all pieces are represented by small, realistic figures that walk around on the chessboard, and when one piece takes another, they both take part in an animated battle. There is a different animation for each permutation, depending on which pieces are capturing or being captured. You can also play in 2D without animation. 

The game's opening library includes 30,000 different moves, ensuring a variety of games will unfold across the 10 skill levels. 

Multi-player support can be extended to modem and/or serial port play.
</desc>
		<image>./media/images/BattleChess_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/BattleChess_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Civilization_v1.1_AGA_CD.lha</path>
		<name>Civilization (AGA)</name>
		<desc>This is it - the game that you've decided is the best Amiga game ever, and I must say it caught me by surprise. Sid Meier's conquest game is intriguing and addictive; challenging the player to evolve with their charge through the ages, from primitive man to present day and beyond. Hugely absorbing, the game sucks in the player and has been responsible for many late nights and bleary eyes. The recent re-issue on CD should ensure Civ stays at the top of the AR100 for a while yet.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Civilization_v1.1_AGA_CD.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Civilization_v1.1_AGA_CD.mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DefenderOfTheCrown2_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Defender of the Crown 2</name>
		<desc>Defender of the Crown puts the player in the role of one of four Saxon knights in medieval England, in a time where the land is in turmoil as the King is dead and his crown was stolen. The Saxons and the Normans blame each other and fight for control of England.

After a short introduction by Robin of Locksley himself, the game starts with a single castle and 10 soldiers at your command. From there, you have to build your army, take control of additional territories and fight and defeat the three Norman lords - and sometimes your Saxon friends as well.

In addition to the basic ' build your army and conquer your opponents' the game offers several events and options that can be used to fine tune your play style: You may engage in a jousting contest where you have to knock your opponent off his horse, gaining either fame or land, or you can go raid a castle for loot or the hand of a princess, joining your houses and territories.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/DefenderOfTheCrown2_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Master Designer Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Cinemaware</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DifensoreDellaCorona2_v1.1_CD32_It.lha</path>
		<name>Defender of the Crown 2 (IT)</name>
		<desc>Defender of the Crown puts the player in the role of one of four Saxon knights in medieval England, in a time where the land is in turmoil as the King is dead and his crown was stolen. The Saxons and the Normans blame each other and fight for control of England.

After a short introduction by Robin of Locksley himself, the game starts with a single castle and 10 soldiers at your command. From there, you have to build your army, take control of additional territories and fight and defeat the three Norman lords - and sometimes your Saxon friends as well.

In addition to the basic ' build your army and conquer your opponents' the game offers several events and options that can be used to fine tune your play style: You may engage in a jousting contest where you have to knock your opponent off his horse, gaining either fame or land, or you can go raid a castle for loot or the hand of a princess, joining your houses and territories.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/DefenderOfTheCrown2_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Master Designer Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Cinemaware</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zool_v1.2_CD32_NTSC.lha</path>
		<name>Zool - Ninja Of The 'nth' Dimension (NTSC)</name>
		<desc>His name is Zool. He is a Ninja in the 2345th dimension, 6 worlds each with 3 stages. 

In this platformer, you can run, jump, climb walls and shoot the enemies. In the levels are also some power-ups for Zool. There are life-spending hearts, smart bombs, shields, more powerful jump-skill and a twin Zool. This "twin" makes all your motions a few seconds after you do.

In the options you can change the difficulty and the game-speed two times, the continues and the background music (Rock or Funk).
</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Zool_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Zool_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BeneathASteelSky_v2.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Beneath a Steel Sky</name>
		<desc>Beneath a Steel Sky.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/BeneathASteelSky_v2.0_CD32.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BeneathASteelSky_v2.0_CD32_NoVoice.lha</path>
		<name>Beneath A Steel Sky (No Voice)</name>
		<image>./media/images/BeneathASteelSky_v2.0_CD32_NoVoice.png</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T000000</releasedate>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ChaosInAndromeda_v1.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Chaos in Andromeda</name>
		<desc>Chaos in Andromeda.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/ChaosInAndromeda_v1.0_CDTV.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Roadkill_v2.1b_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>RoadKill</name>
		<desc>RoadKill.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Roadkill_v2.1b_CD32.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TownWithNoName_v1.0_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Town with no Name</name>
		<desc>Town with no Name.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/NS.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher />
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms_v1.0_CD32_2MB.lha</path>
		<name>Worms (2 MB)</name>
		<desc>Worms is a turn-based strategy game. It features up to 4 teams of 4 worms, aiming to destroy the others on a generated terrain. Each worm has 100 hit points, and dies when his hit points fall to 0. Upon death, a worm explodes, causing damage to everyone around.

Gameplay is turn-based. Each turn, the player can control one specific worm from his team. The worm can crawl left and right or jump. However, there is a time limit to make a move; also, if the worm falls from a great height, it loses health and the turn ends immediately; and if a worm falls into water or offscreen, it dies. Each turn, a worm can also make a single attack: the player can aim up and down, choose a weapon and then fire it. After attacking, the turn ends. 

There's a lot of weapons available - the standard ones as bazookas (which is affected by the (random) wind settings and gravity) and grenades. The others include a Fire Punch, dynamite, air strikes, and utilities such as ropes and girders.

There are 10 styles of terrain, ranging from forests and deserts to Candy land and the moon (complete with affected gravity). Shots leave craters in the ground, and complex tunnels can be formed.
</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Worms_v1.0_CD32_2MB.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Worms_v1.0_CD32_2MB.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Team 17</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cedric_v1.1_CD32_Fast.lha</path>
		<name>Cedric (Fast)</name>
		<image>./media/images/Cedric_v1.1_CD32_Fast.png</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T000000</releasedate>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Logical_v1.1_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Log!cal</name>
		<desc>Logical is a bizarre puzzle game in which you have to arrange colored balls (green, purple, blue or yellow) to form quartets in any of several locations on the game board. These locations are, in fact, balls you can spin, then send any of the balls in them through the connection path (have a look at the screenshots).
</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Logical_v1.1_CDTV.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Logical_v1.1_CDTV.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts Software</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbow Arts Software</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BattleChess_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Battle Chess</name>
		<desc>Battle Chess is a quite typical chess game, but it comes with a twist: all pieces are represented by small, realistic figures that walk around on the chessboard, and when one piece takes another, they both take part in an animated battle. There is a different animation for each permutation, depending on which pieces are capturing or being captured. You can also play in 2D without animation. 

The game's opening library includes 30,000 different moves, ensuring a variety of games will unfold across the 10 skill levels. 

Multi-player support can be extended to modem and/or serial port play.
</desc>
		<image>./media/images/BattleChess_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/BattleChess_v1.1_CD32.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190728T155145</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battlestorm_v1.2_CDTV.lha</path>
		<name>Battlestorm</name>
		<desc>A top-down space shooter that was different from most others at the time in that it did not just scroll continuously in one direction, but could scroll at different speeds in all possible directions on the X and Y axis, on the player's whim.

The game takes place above the surface of a ruined, devastated planet: each level starts within a large area, in which your ship has free movement. Avoiding surface hazards, such as auto-aiming turrets, the goal is to destroy enemy spacecraft that hover around the large area in groups. Each wave of attacks is followed by a bomb-dropping mothership, which you must hurry up and destroy before it moves off the playfield, in order to proceed to the next wave; the last mothership gives way to the boss - a gigantic spacecraft that will chase you around the playfield. Beaten it? you are transported to a short section of standard shooter fare, where the screen auto-scrolls vertically, at the end of which you face a final monstrosity. This ends the level - on to the next one.

Absorbing enemy fire will deplete your power, while collecting power-ups and destroying turrets can bring it back up somewhat. At 0% power, the game is over - although you may get an option to continue, based on how far you got.
</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Battlestorm_v1.2_CDTV.png</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titus</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190729T005418</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LastNinja3_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Last Ninja 3</name>
		<image>./media/images/LastNinja3_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190906T155354</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oscar_v1.8_CD32_NTSC.lha</path>
		<name>Oscar (NTSC)</name>
		<desc>Your name is Oscar. You have to run and jump through 7 Levels in Hollywood-style (Science Fiction, Western, Horror, Cartoons, Dino, Detective and Gameshow) to find Oscars (yes  the Academy Award!). 

If you have enough Oscars you solve the level. You can choose the levels in every order you want. In the levels you must jump on platforms to discover the level. 

You kill the enemies by jumping on them. Some of them lose a power up like invulnerable or a superjump. You can also find a JoJo to break down walls or using as ladder. Two creatures are no opponents. First the white rabbit. He gives you a extra continue. Second a red elephant. Touch him for using as save point in level.
</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Oscar_v1.8_CD32_NTSC.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Oscar_v1.8_CD32_NTSC.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flair Software</developer>
		<publisher>Flair Software</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NigelMansellsWorldChampionship_v1.3_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Nigel Mansell's World Championship</name>
		<desc>Timing smiled on Gremlin with this licensed Formula 1 simulation, as Nigel's long quest for a championship had finally come good. The game was pitched somewhere in between a full-blown simulation like F1 GP and action games like Continental Circus. Only 12 cars were in each race, which could last from between 3 and 20 laps.

Before each race you can customize wing downforce, gear ratio, tyre selection and fuel load choices  pitstops are a standard feature of the longer races. The 16-bit versions include a unique 'Improve With Mansell' mode, in which a digitized version of Nigel's head appears in the top corner of the screen, offering instructions and praise.
</desc>
		<image>./media/images/NigelMansellsWorldChampionship_v1.3_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/NigelMansellsWorldChampionship_v1.3_CD32.mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20191002T004858</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castles2_v1.1_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Castles 2 - Siege And Conquest</name>
		<desc>Choisissez d'incarner un des cinq seigneurs luttant pour la couronne. Conquête, espionnage, sabotage, diplomatie, maintenez votre peuple heureux. Vous devez atteindre 7.000 points pour prétendre le au trône, et devrez maintenir ces points pendant 4-5 mois de jeu pour gagner. Cependant, vos adversaires ne vous laisseront pas tranquille...</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Castles2_v1.1_CD32.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Castles2_v1.1_CD32-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Castles2_v1.1_CD32-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quicksilva Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Stratégie</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SuperMethaneBros_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Super Methane Bros.</name>
		<desc>Ce jeu de plateforme est similaire à Bubble Bobble à plusieurs niveaux. Le jeu comporte 100 niveaux, aux formes différentes. Les niveaux sont remplis d'insectes méchants, mais vous disposez d'un pistolet de méthane pour leur tirer dessus.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/SuperMethaneBros_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/SuperMethaneBros_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SuperMethaneBros_v1.2_CD32-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SuperMethaneBros_v1.2_CD32-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apache</developer>
		<publisher>Apache</publisher>
		<genre>Plateforme</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Humans_v1.5_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Humans</name>
		<desc>Dans The Humans, vous devez guider une tribu d'hommes préhistoriques dans leur évolution. A chaque niveau, vous devez accomplir des tâches en un temps limité avec un certain nombre de membres de la tribu. Des animations humoristiques entrecoupent les passages entre les niveaux. Vous dirigez les hommes un par un et pouvez leur demander de faire plusieurs actions différentes en fonction des objets à disposition.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Humans_v1.5_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Humans_v1.5_CD32.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Humans_v1.5_CD32-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Humans_v1.5_CD32-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagitec Design</developer>
		<publisher>GameTek</publisher>
		<genre>Réflexion</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guardian_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Guardian</name>
		<desc>Ressemblant à Starfox à beaucoup de points de vue, Guardian est un Shoot'em up très rapide. Vous volez au ras de la surface d'une planète, abattant des ennemis le plus rapidement possible, dans le but de protéger le maximum d'installations possible - plus vous en sauvez, plus vous avez des vies supplémentaires.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Guardian_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Guardian_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Guardian_v1.0_CD32-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Guardian_v1.0_CD32-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acid</developer>
		<publisher>Acid</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BrutalFootball_v1.21_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Brutal Football</name>
		<desc>Semblable à Speedball 2, Brutal Football est un jeu de sport ultra-violent. Les matches durent 7 minutes, et le but est d'entrer la balle dans un but adverse. La balle peut être lancée ou donnée à coup de pied, et elle est ovale. Des bonus et des non-bonus apparaissent sur le terrain, des bombes pour jeter aux adversaires, des lapins pour accélérer le joueur, ou des tortues pour le ralentir...</desc>
		<image>./media/images/BrutalFootball_v1.21_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/BrutalFootball_v1.21_CD32.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/BrutalFootball_v1.21_CD32-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/BrutalFootball_v1.21_CD32-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Teque</developer>
		<publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FightinSpirit_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Fightin Spirit</name>
		<desc>Fightin' Spirit est un jeu de combat qui vous fait participer à un tournoi organisé par un gang afin de trouver de nouveaux champions. Dix combattants sont présents. Beaucoup de mouvements spéciaux comme le fait de pouvoir se transformer en animal - devenir un tigre ou encore un puma...</desc>
		<image>./media/images/FightinSpirit_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/FightinSpirit_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/FightinSpirit_v1.2_CD32-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/FightinSpirit_v1.2_CD32-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Combat</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20191031T144317</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gloom_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Gloom</name>
		<desc>Comme le titre le laisse penser, Gloom tente de recréer le jeu Doom sur Amiga. En 1995 c'était un vrai défi pour les programmeurs, on estimait alors que l'Amiga était capable de faire tourner un FPS...</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Gloom_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Gloom_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Gloom_v1.2_CD32-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Gloom_v1.2_CD32-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acid</developer>
		<publisher>Guildhall Leisure Services</publisher>
		<genre>Tir / 1ere Personne</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diggers_v1.0_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Diggers</name>
		<desc>Diggers est un puzzle-game inspiré de Lemmings où vous dirigez 5 mineurs aliens et de divers outils pour creuser afin de trouver un trésor. Le jeu est divisé en secteurs d'excavation. Chaque secteur a une somme d'argent à atteindre avant de passer au suivant. Pour se faire, vous devrez vendre vos trésors trouvés à la banque.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Diggers_v1.0_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Diggers_v1.0_CD32.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Diggers_v1.0_CD32-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Diggers_v1.0_CD32-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AlienBreed3D_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Alien Breed 3D</name>
		<desc>Team 17 were famed for pushing the Amiga to its limits, with a string of hits stretching back to 1991. The first major one was Alien Breed, a Gauntlet-style shoot 'em up which had already spawned three sequels, including a budget-priced Special Edition.

This release was in a similar vein, but set into a 3D context, making for the Amiga's first big Doom-style game. The 3D engine uses fairly small screen graphics, but these include full floors and ceilings with detailed shading, doors, vertical position variations, lifts and transporters. The CD version includes extra atmospheric sound, while fast processors and extra FastRAM are also supported.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/AlienBreed3D_v1.2_NoMusic_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/AlienBreed3D_v1.2_NoMusic_CD32.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Team 17 - Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20191112T143414</lastplayed>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AlfredChicken_v1.01_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Alfred Chicken</name>
		<desc>Alfred the chicken must rescue his friends and his bird (pardon the pun) Floella from the Meka Chickens. The result is a platform game across differently-themed levels, which are finished by either climbing to the top of the level or killing a boss. Bonus games and secret rooms have been included, and progression sometimes requires solving positional puzzles.

Alfred cannot fly, but he can use ramps to jump up and hit enemies with his bionic beak - this kills them, but any other contact will hurt Alfred. Watch out for spiked snails though. Other enemies include whales armed with guns, and stray bombs.
</desc>
		<image>./media/images/AlfredChicken_v1.01_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/AlfredChicken_v1.01_CD32.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Akira_v1.2_CD32.lha</path>
		<name>Akira</name>
		<desc>Un jeu adapté du film du même nom. Dans les premiers niveaux vous devrez guider Kaneda avec sa moto sur une route remplie d'obstacles. Les barrages peuvent être dégagés avec des grenades. Vous devez également traverser le niveau sans manquer de carburant. Après les niveaux à moto il y a cinq niveaux de plate-forme. Le but de ces niveaux est de tuer tous ceux que vous rencontrez.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Akira_v1.2_CD32.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/Akira_v1.2_CD32.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Akira_v1.2_CD32-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Akira_v1.2_CD32-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>International Computer Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>International Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<playcount>6</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20191012T133653</lastplayed>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BombPacCD32_v1.0_AGA.lha</path>
		<name>BombPac</name>
		<desc>In Bomberpac on Amiga CD32, you are the hero of a game which is a mixture of Pacman and Bomberman developed in freeware. You are Bombpac, paramilitary ancestor of hell, you must survive the ghosts and other enemies by finding all the pills and make your way through your bombs through the rooms of the castle.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/NS.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/BombPacCD32_v1.0_AGA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oliver Wagner</developer>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
