<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (France) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil Code: Vero</name>
		<desc>Three months after the events of Resident Evil 2, Claire Redfield is still looking for her brother Chris. She infiltrates Umbrella Corporation's headquarters in Paris, where she is captured and knocked out. When she comes to, she finds herself in a prison on a remote island. Freed by a friendly guard, Claire faces several problems. Not only is the island under attack by an unknown assailant, but there has been another outbreak of the T-Virus and the island is crawling with zombies and other mutated creatures. Claire not only has to face the undead, but also the commander of the base, a mad aristocrat with family ties to the origins of Umbrella Corporation and the T-Virus. And escaping from the island is only the beginning of Claire's ordeals.

Code: Veronica continues the survival horror gameplay of its predecessors: the protagonist explores the surroundings, fighting monsters and solving puzzles. However, Code: Veronica is the first game in the series to do away with pre-rendered backgrounds, using a fully polygonal 3D engine instead, which allows for features such as real-time lighting and camera movement. Still, such movements are only used sparingly, and the use of perspective is mostly unchanged from earlier installments: the camera automatically switches to different static angles, showing protagonist, monsters and rooms from different spooky viewpoints.

Most of the weapons from the earlier games make return appearances: knife, handguns, shotgun, grenade launcher and crossbow are all featured. There are also new weapons including a sniper rifle, an AK-47 and several guns only found in pairs, which can be used to target two enemies at the same time. Several weapons upgrades can also be found.

Similar to the earlier games, the player will not only control Claire, but also two other characters: Claire's fellow prisoner Steve, and her brother Chris.
</desc>
		<image>./images/Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (France) (Disc 1)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (France) (Disc 1)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (France) (Disc 1)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Striker 2.cdi</path>
		<name>Virtua Striker 2</name>
		<desc>It's here, Virtua Striker 2 V2000.1 has come to Dreamcast in all its arcade-perfect glory. Play any of the new modes - including 'Ranking' and 'Leagues' - or just sit back and enjoy the original arcade mode from the comfort of your armchair. You can save the best goal on your VM unit and use it when your competing in two-player mode. 

Football has never looked so good and felt so right... you can almost taste the pie and Bovril at half time.
</desc>
		<image>./images/Virtua Striker 2-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Virtua Striker 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Virtua Striker 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (France) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil Code: Vero</name>
		<desc>Three months after the events of Resident Evil 2, Claire Redfield is still looking for her brother Chris. She infiltrates Umbrella Corporation's headquarters in Paris, where she is captured and knocked out. When she comes to, she finds herself in a prison on a remote island. Freed by a friendly guard, Claire faces several problems. Not only is the island under attack by an unknown assailant, but there has been another outbreak of the T-Virus and the island is crawling with zombies and other mutated creatures. Claire not only has to face the undead, but also the commander of the base, a mad aristocrat with family ties to the origins of Umbrella Corporation and the T-Virus. And escaping from the island is only the beginning of Claire's ordeals.

Code: Veronica continues the survival horror gameplay of its predecessors: the protagonist explores the surroundings, fighting monsters and solving puzzles. However, Code: Veronica is the first game in the series to do away with pre-rendered backgrounds, using a fully polygonal 3D engine instead, which allows for features such as real-time lighting and camera movement. Still, such movements are only used sparingly, and the use of perspective is mostly unchanged from earlier installments: the camera automatically switches to different static angles, showing protagonist, monsters and rooms from different spooky viewpoints.

Most of the weapons from the earlier games make return appearances: knife, handguns, shotgun, grenade launcher and crossbow are all featured. There are also new weapons including a sniper rifle, an AK-47 and several guns only found in pairs, which can be used to target two enemies at the same time. Several weapons upgrades can also be found.

Similar to the earlier games, the player will not only control Claire, but also two other characters: Claire's fellow prisoner Steve, and her brother Chris.
</desc>
		<image>./images/Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (France) (Disc 2)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (France) (Disc 2)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (France) (Disc 2)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soulcalibur (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Soulcalibur</name>
		<desc>A fighting game to end all fighting games.  A sequel to Soul Blade, Soul Calibur takes place in a time inspired by a mixture of 16th-century ancient China and oriental medieval fantasies and legends.  

All characters have weapons and distinct fighting styles with over 100 individual moves per character.  In addition to high, mid, and low attacks, characters can hold/throw, block, and perform special attacks -- one or more of which is deemed "un-blockable" and must be avoided by ducking, jumping, or rotating around your attacker. 

In addition to several locales in which to fight and alternate models/costumes per character, the Dreamcast conversion of Soul Calibur contains many additional features over the arcade coin-op, including hidden characters and locales, a campaign mode, and tournament mode.  There is also a "museum" where you can view character profiles and view motion-captured martial arts demonstrations.</desc>
		<image>./images/Soulcalibur (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Soulcalibur (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Soulcalibur (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>es,fr,de</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shenmue disc4.cdi</path>
		<name>Shenmue</name>
		<desc>That day in November when the snow turned to rain. Ryu Hazuki arrives home just in time to see his father killed by Lan Di, a man Ryu's father obviously knew very well. Ryu attempts to stop Lan Di, but is effortlessly beaten to within an inch of his life. After recovering from his injuries Ryu sets out to track down his father's murder as well as uncover his family's secrets and the mystery of the Phoenix and Dragon mirrors that Lan Di seeks.

Much of Shenmue's gameplay involves talking to Ryu's friends and the various people around town, hoping to find hints or clues that lead to the next step in the story. Any details Ryu learns are written down in his notebook for future review. Ryu can buy items from stores or try his luck with capsule toy machines, but the vast majority of items you can buy have no purpose outside of filling out your inventory screen. Ryu can also visit an arcade and play arcade accurate versions of  Hang-On and Space Harrier as well as games like darts and pool.

Ryu is a trained martial artist, and while a true martial artist knows it is better to avoid a fight, sometimes it is still necessary. Ryu can train his moves, either by repeatedly doing them while training, or by sparing with his friend Fuku-san. Fighting plays like a simplified Virtua Fighter game, although with toned down air juggling. Ryu's training also gives him heightened reflexes, and sometimes during a cutscene the player will have only a moment to press a button (displayed onscreen) to get Ryu out of danger. Failing an input prompt is not always fatal, but whether Ryu survives or not depends on the danger he was in.

Included with the game is the Shenmue Passport disc. On this disc players can receive tutorials about various aspects of the game like minigames or the battle system, watch cutscenes they've already seen in the game, and listen to music from the game. This disc also includes the option to go online to a special site where players can review world-wide minigame rankings, get hints for the game from Nozomi, review game maps of Yokosuka, trade uncommon items found in the game for even rarer items only available on the passport, and visit the official homepage. This service went offline along with the rest of SegaNet, and all online features are currently impossible to access.</desc>
		<image>./images/Shenmue disc4-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Shenmue disc4-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shenmue disc4-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 3: Nemesis</name>
		<desc>So Evil they even gave it a subtitle!

The final installment of the Resident Evil series for the Playstation, Resident Evil 3 takes place during the events of Resident Evil 2. The midwestern town of Raccoon City is in ruins, having been overrun with the undead creating T-virus thanks to the wacky hijinks of William Birkin and Umbrella Inc. As Jill "master of unlocking" Valentine (one of the two main protagonists of the original Resident Evil), you must find a way out of the zombie-infested remains of the city alive. Along the way, you'll interact with and receive help from three heavily armed Umbrella mercenaries who have also become stranded in Raccoon City thanks to the incompetence of their employer. Standing in the way of your group's last escape are a horde of flesh-eating zombified citizens, homicidal mutants, and a relentless killing machine known only as Nemesis who is determined to hunt down and kill the survivors of the original Resident Evil, including Jill.

A dramatic improvement over Tyrant/Mr. X/G from the previous games, Nemesis possesses the same maneuverability as Jill allowing him to run (faster than you, in fact), use firearms (such as a rocket launcher), dodge attacks, and even move through doors and from room to room in pursuit of Jill. On top of that he still possesses the nigh indestructibility we've come to know and... well, know from Umbrella's ultimate bio-weapons. 

Like its two predecessors Resident Evil 3 is a third-person action-adventure game with polygonal characters on pre-rendered backgrounds with cinematic camera angles, a technique originally pioneered by Alone in the Dark. Although the game uses the same basic engine and gameplay as the previous games, improvements include auto-targeting, a 180 degree spin, and a new dodge move that allows you to avoid enemy attacks by pressing a button a second before they strike. Another addition is Jill's ability to create different kinds of ammunition by mixing together three different types of gunpowder found throughout the game. Compared to Resident Evil 2, the amount of available ammunition and healing items has been significantly decreased, making the game more difficult. The variety of zombie citizens has also been made more diverse.

The number of polygons in the character models has also been increased, along with the possible screen resolution and color depth for the PC version (up to 1600 X 1200 at 32 bits, from a maximum of 640 X 480 at 16 bits for Resident Evil 2). Another welcome addition in the PC version is the ability to skip cutscenes as well as the door loading animation.

The PC and Dreamcast versions includes all eight of Jill's possible costumes, as well as the mercenary mini-game Operation Mad Jackal which allows you to play as one of the three Umbrella soldiers. On the Playstation version, these special features must be unlocked by beating the game with a high score.
</desc>
		<image>./images/Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toy Commander.cdi</path>
		<name>Toy Commander</name>
		<desc>Some of the greatest adventures that kids have growing up occur in their imaginations as they play with their toys.  Toy Commander is a game that attempts to capture these adventures in an interactive, three dimensional world. The player's perspective is that of the toy vehicles that inhabit a house. The various gameplay areas are all based on rooms in this giant house. 

Gameplay in Toy Commander is mission based.  In each mission, you control one or more toy vehicles to accomplish certain objectives. The objectives in each mission vary widely.  In some missions, you must drive an army truck and shoot things, in some you fly helicopters to pick up and drop off objects, and in some you must race against computer controlled vehicles. 

There is a story line that ties together the missions in single player mode. A coalition of old toys has started a rebellion against the new toys in the house. An evil Teddy Bear, the Toy Commander, is leading this rebellion.  It's your job to stop him. In each mission, your basic goal is to complete the task in as short a time as possible.  If you meet a certain time goal, the mission is completed.  By completing 4 missions, you get to challenge the Boss character in the room.  If you successfully destroy the boss, he will assist you in the final fight against the Toy Commander.

In addition to the single player mode, there is a 4-player simultaneous deathmatch mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/Toy Commander-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Toy Commander-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Toy Commander-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>No Cliché</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shenmue disc1.cdi</path>
		<name>Shenmue</name>
		<desc>That day in November when the snow turned to rain. Ryu Hazuki arrives home just in time to see his father killed by Lan Di, a man Ryu's father obviously knew very well. Ryu attempts to stop Lan Di, but is effortlessly beaten to within an inch of his life. After recovering from his injuries Ryu sets out to track down his father's murder as well as uncover his family's secrets and the mystery of the Phoenix and Dragon mirrors that Lan Di seeks.

Much of Shenmue's gameplay involves talking to Ryu's friends and the various people around town, hoping to find hints or clues that lead to the next step in the story. Any details Ryu learns are written down in his notebook for future review. Ryu can buy items from stores or try his luck with capsule toy machines, but the vast majority of items you can buy have no purpose outside of filling out your inventory screen. Ryu can also visit an arcade and play arcade accurate versions of  Hang-On and Space Harrier as well as games like darts and pool.

Ryu is a trained martial artist, and while a true martial artist knows it is better to avoid a fight, sometimes it is still necessary. Ryu can train his moves, either by repeatedly doing them while training, or by sparing with his friend Fuku-san. Fighting plays like a simplified Virtua Fighter game, although with toned down air juggling. Ryu's training also gives him heightened reflexes, and sometimes during a cutscene the player will have only a moment to press a button (displayed onscreen) to get Ryu out of danger. Failing an input prompt is not always fatal, but whether Ryu survives or not depends on the danger he was in.

Included with the game is the Shenmue Passport disc. On this disc players can receive tutorials about various aspects of the game like minigames or the battle system, watch cutscenes they've already seen in the game, and listen to music from the game. This disc also includes the option to go online to a special site where players can review world-wide minigame rankings, get hints for the game from Nozomi, review game maps of Yokosuka, trade uncommon items found in the game for even rarer items only available on the passport, and visit the official homepage. This service went offline along with the rest of SegaNet, and all online features are currently impossible to access.</desc>
		<image>./images/Shenmue disc1-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Shenmue disc1-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shenmue disc1-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Tennis 2 - Sega Professional Tennis (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Virtua Tennis 2</name>
		<desc>Sequel to the original game which was released two years prior.

The games graphics have been improved, and there is a greater roster of players to choose from. The most noteworthy addition is that of female players, such as Monica Seles and Venus and Serena Williams. You cannot however play as a male against a female.

The gameplay is a lot faster than the original. The players you control move a lot faster, as do the AI computer players. Less diving, but more getting at shots that go behind you and over the shoulder shots.

The game modes from the original are the same, featuring tournament mode, where you play against the pros; exhibition mode for a one-on-one, best-out-of-three game; and world tour mode which now features the option of creating and customizing your own player. Build you player up, buy equipment and hire pros to play in doubles matches with you.</desc>
		<image>./images/Virtua Tennis 2 - Sega Professional Tennis (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Virtua Tennis 2 - Sega Professional Tennis (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Virtua Tennis 2 - Sega Professional Tennis (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20011123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>es,fr,de</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rez.cdi</path>
		<name>Rez</name>
		<desc>Rez is a fast-action shooter that takes you deep into the world’s computer network. The “Project K” Network has recently been upgraded to handle the rapid expansion of the information age and the core, known as “Eden,” holds the most advanced artificial intelligence the world has ever seen. Unfortunately, Eden cannot handle the ability to create her own thoughts and buckles under the pressure in an existential breakdown. She is lost deep inside the system, and you’re the only one that can bring her back online, saving the world from utter chaos.

You must blast complex viruses, unlock passwords, and destroy firewall bosses as you search for Eden. Each stage is in a constant state of flux dependent on your shooting techniques, which ultimately control the music and colors of your environment. The deeper you get into the dreamlike cyber world of Rez, your form will evolve or devolve depending on your progress.</desc>
		<image>./images/Rez-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Rez-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rez-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>United Game Artists</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dino Crisis.cdi</path>
		<name>Dino Crisis</name>
		<desc>Three years ago a brilliant scientist disappeared while researching a new form of energy. The government that funded his research wrote the whole affair off as a loss, which made it all the more upsetting when reports of Dr. Kirk's good health and nearly finished research came in. A special forces team is sent to the doctor's private island laboratory to extract him and his research, but they are totally unprepared for some of the side effects of his developments. Side effects that come from 100 million years in the past.

Dino Crisis is a survival horror game that is very similar in both control and gameplay to its sister series, Resident Evil. As in that series, protagonist Regina will have limited supplies and ammo with which to fight deadly enemies while searching rooms for keys (some figurative, some literal) to open locked areas. Unlike Resident Evil games, Regina will find very few actual supplies laying around, and will instead find "plugs" that are used to open caches of emergency supplies located around the complex. There are only enough plugs to open some of these caches, however, so care must be taken to decide what items are really needed. In another change from Resident Evil, the game is rendered in 3D, allowing the camera to rotate or pan, although camera angles are still out of the control of the player. Even the dumbest dinosaur is smarter than the undead, and enemies can chase and disarm Regina, and even occasionally follow her through doors.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dino Crisis-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Dino Crisis-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dino Crisis-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20001114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NexTech</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Namco Museum (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Namco Museum</name>
		<desc>A total of 12 games are offered in Namco Museum: 

1. Pac-Man

2. Pac-Man Arrangement

3. Galaga

4. Galaga Arrangement

5. Dig Dug

6. Dig Dug Arrangement

7. Pole Position

8. Pole Position II

9. Ms. Pac-Man

10. Galaxian

11. Pac-Attack

12. Pac-Mania

For the first time since their arcade days, Pac-Man Arrangement, Galaga Arrangement and Dig Dug Arrangement are ported to the home console.

Everything is exactly the same as the original arcade versions, including the music, cut scenes, graphics, and even the many graphical errors that appear.</desc>
		<image>./images/Namco Museum (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Namco Museum (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Namco Museum (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mass Media, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Set Radio (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Jet Set Radio</name>
		<desc>Jet Set Radio is a video game developed by Smilebit and published by Sega on June 29, 2000. Jet Set Radio was developed for the Dreamcast, although a 2D version of the game was later released for Game Boy Advance and was developed by Vicarious Visions, and published by THQ. Its sequel, Jet Set Radio Future was released 2 years later for the Xbox after SEGA became a software-based company. The game is known for spearheading the use of cel-shaded graphics in video games.</desc>
		<image>./images/Jet Set Radio (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Jet Set Radio (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Jet Set Radio (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Smilebit</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<lang>es,fr,de</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shenmue disc3.cdi</path>
		<name>Shenmue</name>
		<desc>That day in November when the snow turned to rain. Ryu Hazuki arrives home just in time to see his father killed by Lan Di, a man Ryu's father obviously knew very well. Ryu attempts to stop Lan Di, but is effortlessly beaten to within an inch of his life. After recovering from his injuries Ryu sets out to track down his father's murder as well as uncover his family's secrets and the mystery of the Phoenix and Dragon mirrors that Lan Di seeks.

Much of Shenmue's gameplay involves talking to Ryu's friends and the various people around town, hoping to find hints or clues that lead to the next step in the story. Any details Ryu learns are written down in his notebook for future review. Ryu can buy items from stores or try his luck with capsule toy machines, but the vast majority of items you can buy have no purpose outside of filling out your inventory screen. Ryu can also visit an arcade and play arcade accurate versions of  Hang-On and Space Harrier as well as games like darts and pool.

Ryu is a trained martial artist, and while a true martial artist knows it is better to avoid a fight, sometimes it is still necessary. Ryu can train his moves, either by repeatedly doing them while training, or by sparing with his friend Fuku-san. Fighting plays like a simplified Virtua Fighter game, although with toned down air juggling. Ryu's training also gives him heightened reflexes, and sometimes during a cutscene the player will have only a moment to press a button (displayed onscreen) to get Ryu out of danger. Failing an input prompt is not always fatal, but whether Ryu survives or not depends on the danger he was in.

Included with the game is the Shenmue Passport disc. On this disc players can receive tutorials about various aspects of the game like minigames or the battle system, watch cutscenes they've already seen in the game, and listen to music from the game. This disc also includes the option to go online to a special site where players can review world-wide minigame rankings, get hints for the game from Nozomi, review game maps of Yokosuka, trade uncommon items found in the game for even rarer items only available on the passport, and visit the official homepage. This service went offline along with the rest of SegaNet, and all online features are currently impossible to access.</desc>
		<image>./images/Shenmue disc3-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Shenmue disc3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shenmue disc3-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shenmue disc2.cdi</path>
		<name>Shenmue</name>
		<desc>That day in November when the snow turned to rain. Ryu Hazuki arrives home just in time to see his father killed by Lan Di, a man Ryu's father obviously knew very well. Ryu attempts to stop Lan Di, but is effortlessly beaten to within an inch of his life. After recovering from his injuries Ryu sets out to track down his father's murder as well as uncover his family's secrets and the mystery of the Phoenix and Dragon mirrors that Lan Di seeks.

Much of Shenmue's gameplay involves talking to Ryu's friends and the various people around town, hoping to find hints or clues that lead to the next step in the story. Any details Ryu learns are written down in his notebook for future review. Ryu can buy items from stores or try his luck with capsule toy machines, but the vast majority of items you can buy have no purpose outside of filling out your inventory screen. Ryu can also visit an arcade and play arcade accurate versions of  Hang-On and Space Harrier as well as games like darts and pool.

Ryu is a trained martial artist, and while a true martial artist knows it is better to avoid a fight, sometimes it is still necessary. Ryu can train his moves, either by repeatedly doing them while training, or by sparing with his friend Fuku-san. Fighting plays like a simplified Virtua Fighter game, although with toned down air juggling. Ryu's training also gives him heightened reflexes, and sometimes during a cutscene the player will have only a moment to press a button (displayed onscreen) to get Ryu out of danger. Failing an input prompt is not always fatal, but whether Ryu survives or not depends on the danger he was in.

Included with the game is the Shenmue Passport disc. On this disc players can receive tutorials about various aspects of the game like minigames or the battle system, watch cutscenes they've already seen in the game, and listen to music from the game. This disc also includes the option to go online to a special site where players can review world-wide minigame rankings, get hints for the game from Nozomi, review game maps of Yokosuka, trade uncommon items found in the game for even rarer items only available on the passport, and visit the official homepage. This service went offline along with the rest of SegaNet, and all online features are currently impossible to access.</desc>
		<image>./images/Shenmue disc2-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Shenmue disc2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shenmue disc2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daytona USA.cdi</path>
		<name>Daytona USA</name>
		<desc>Just like the arcade version, pick one of three tracks (beginner, advanced, or expert) and either automatic or standard transmission. A pounding music soundtrack kicks in as you are slapped into your car to await the green light. The game offers both a traditional arcade mode with checkpoint time splits and a special PC mode that pits you against the other cars over different race distances. The PC mode also offers more car choices, with a variety of speed, acceleration, and grip characteristics. It even rewards successful players (meaning those finishing first, second, or third in the difficult setting) by offering up to ten more upgraded cars to drive. Once underway, the goal is to work from last to first as smoothly and quickly as possible</desc>
		<image>./images/Daytona USA-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Daytona USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Daytona USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amusement Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220911T052356</lastplayed>
		<gametime>111</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crazy Taxi 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to the smash hit Crazy Taxi puts you in the drivers seat once again with 4 new drivers to choose from, and a brand new city to wreck havoc with, New York City.

In Crazy Taxi, you crashed your taxi through the streets as fast as possible, making money by performing stunts and picking up/dropping off passengers to certain destinations. For Crazy Taxi 2, you can pick up more then one passenger at a time, meaning more money faster, new stunts including the 'hop', which allows you to hop over buildings and take the quick route past the traffic, and plenty of mini games, such as Crazy Golf.</desc>
		<image>./images/Crazy Taxi 2 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Crazy Taxi 2 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crazy Taxi 2 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220921T201545</lastplayed>
		<gametime>87</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Stone 2 (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Power Stone 2</name>
		<desc>The world's most revolutionary fighting game does it again! Power Stone 2 takes go-anywhere, grab-anything combat, and introduces awesome new innovations to the hit arcade fighting series. Now, up to four players wage insane battles in fully interactive, multi-level stages. Master over 120 different items used in battle - weapons, vehicles traps, power-upsand more! As if chaotic swashbuckling battles weren't enough, combine forces with other players to battle monstrous bosses to win the game!</desc>
		<image>./images/Power Stone 2 (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Power Stone 2 (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Power Stone 2 (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000824T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220921T201953</lastplayed>
		<gametime>222</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Psychic Force 2012 (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Psychic Force 2012</name>
		<desc>Psychic Force 2012,  the sequel to Psychic Force,  is a one-on-one fighting game with a twist. The matches take place inside a giant floating cube. You are able to fly, using your psychic abilities, around a 3D arena with six walls. Each of the ten available characters, Might, Regina, Wendy, Emilio, Setsuna, Patty, Gudeath, Genshin, Carlo, and Gates, are controlled with three buttons: guard, weak attack and strong attack. The effect varies with the distance. Next to the regular life meter, there is also a power meter. By using special moves, the meter is drained and your moves are limited. It is possible to recharge, and the capacity of the power meter expands when you lose a lot of health.

Additionally, each fighter has its own unique moves, energy attacks and a weapon, which they use, mid-flight, to pummel their opponent. There are three main game modes: training, versus and a story mode using static anime-inspired images and in-engine cut scenes to tell the story. The story centers around two groups of psychics with differing ideals about co-existence with humans. In the middle of this are several neutral psychics with ties to members in either group.

The later PlayStation port, renamed to Psychic Force 2, adds the 3 missing characters from the first game (Genma, Brad and Sonia), the psy-expand mode where the player can play a series of special battles to learn other character attacks, and an anime intro video replacing the original in-game intro. It also lowers the overall difficulty of the CPU fighters and makes some control adjustments (for instance the shield can now optionally be enabled with a single button). Of course, the graphics were notably degraded.</desc>
		<image>./images/Psychic Force 2012 (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Psychic Force 2012 (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Psychic Force 2012 (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220921T202147</lastplayed>
		<gametime>95</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ready 2 Rumble Boxing (Europe) (En,Fr,De).chd</path>
		<name>Ready 2 Rumble Boxing</name>
		<desc>Ready 2 Rumble Boxing is a boxing video game developed by Midway and published in 1999 for the Dreamcast, PlayStation, Game Boy Color, and Nintendo 64. The success of the Dreamcast version led to it becoming one of the few Sega All Stars titles.

Like Nintendo's Punch-Out!! series, it features many characters with colorful personalities (i.e. Afro Thunder, Boris "The Bear" Knokimov, etc.); however, unlike the Punch-Out!! series, Ready 2 Rumble Boxing is in 3D, thus allowing for more control over one's character in the ring. Also unlike Punch-Out!!, players can choose whichever boxer they want from a rather large selection of characters.

One unique graphic feature of the game is the gradual bruises gained by players as the fight progresses (like hematomas and swellings), present in all fifth-generation versions. While this is not necessarily a new feature to games (it had been implemented before in SNK's 1992 game Art of Fighting), it garnered much appraisal from reviewers, because of the added fun factor this element supply to the game.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing (Europe) (En,Fr,De)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing (Europe) (En,Fr,De)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing (Europe) (En,Fr,De)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220921T202430</lastplayed>
		<gametime>156</gametime>
		<lang>de,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure (U).cdi</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure</name>
		<desc>Yet again Sonic and friends find themselves wrapped up in the schemes of Dr. Robotnik. This time he plans to exploit the power of Chaos, a malevolent being that feeds upon the power of the Chaos Emeralds. In their own ways five heroes will do what they can to save Station Square and, perhaps, the entire world.

The player can select from which character to play after meeting them with Sonic, and each has their own unique version of each level. Sonic's levels involve racing through a level as quickly as possible, destroying any robots along the way. Tails can hover over distances, and his levels are similar to Sonic's except that he must beat an opponent to the finish line. Amy can't charge up ramps or run as quickly as Sonic and Tails, but she does have a giant hammer she can break obstacles with. The goal of her levels is to avoid being captured by a robot sent after her by Dr. Robotnik. E102 Gamma is a slow, difficult to maneuver robot, but it has guns and missiles that can lock on to several targets at once, chaining together attacks and earning a higher score and more time on the clock. The goal of its levels is to reach a boss enemy and destroy it before time runs out. The final character is Big the Cat, a fisherman searching for his lost frog. Big's levels are almost entirely devoid of action or fighting; he just fishes. Each character can find items that increase their abilities as the story progresses, such as a ring for Sonic that lets him home along lines of rings, or improved lures for Big. A final chapter wrapping up the story is unlocked after all other characters have been completed.

Additionally each of the characters can visit the Chao garden where they can raise baby Chaos. By petting, feeding, and showing animals found in levels to the Chaos they can grow stronger, and optionally be put into races against other Chaos. As well each level in the game has additional objectives that can be completed to acquire extra emblems, although the emblems don't do anything in this version of the game. Finally at one time it was possible to go online and download additional levels and bonuses in the game, such a Christmas theme for Station Square and a level sponsored by AT&amp;amp;T, but since SegaNet shut down this is no longer possible.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic Adventure (U)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic Adventure (U)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic Adventure (U)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sonic Team</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220921T203258</lastplayed>
		<gametime>767</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure 2.cdi</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure 2</name>
		<desc>Sonic has returned! This time, his nemesis Dr. Eggman has teamed up with Shadow, a dark hedgehog with a mysterious past, and is aiming once again (like he doesn't) to rule the entire world with the power of the Chaos Emeralds! It's up to Sonic and his friends to stop Eggman and put him out of business for good!

With new features such as a story line told from the view of both the good guys and the villains, greater speed, and an improved A-Life system, Sonic Adventure 2 is poised to be Sonic's greatest and most dangerous mission yet!</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic Adventure 2-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic Adventure 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic Adventure 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20070618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220921T203609</lastplayed>
		<gametime>235</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="13514">
		<path>./Crazy Taxi (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi</name>
		<desc>Get behind the wheel of one of the 4 taxis and become one of the craziest drivers by picking up your passengers and getting them back to their destination as quickly as possible. Choose the shortest routes in these bustling cities and master your driving to earn maximum dollars. For even more fun, a very rhythmic soundtrack adorns these crazy road adventures!</desc>
		<image>./images/Crazy Taxi (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Crazy Taxi (Europe)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Crazy Taxi (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crazy Taxi (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Crazy Taxi (Europe)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Crazy Taxi</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220921T201352</lastplayed>
		<gametime>572</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220929T175709" />
	</game>
</gameList>
