<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="4880">
		<path>./007 - Agent Under Fire (v1.01)(USA).iso</path>
		<name>James Bond 007 in Agent Under Fire</name>
		<desc>Driven by a completely new and original storyline, James Bond 007: Agent Under Fire is a first-person action game that balances furious action and stealth tactics. An evil world organization has been replacing world leaders with their more docile clones and it's up to you to put a stop to it. As Bond, you'll encounter villains and allies, both new and familiar, detailed 3D environments, and spy-packed, fast-action gameplay. And don't worry, Q will provide you with all the innovative weapons, sophisticated spy-craft, and state-of-the-art gadgets that Bond fans expect.</desc>
		<image>./images/007 - Agent Under Fire (v1.01)(USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/007 - Agent Under Fire (v1.01)(USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/007 - Agent Under Fire (v1.01)(USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/007 - Agent Under Fire (v1.01)(USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/007 - Agent Under Fire (v1.01)(USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020312T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>James Bond 007</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161234" />
	</game>
	<game id="4836">
		<path>./007 - Everything or Nothing (USA).iso</path>
		<name>007: Everything or Nothing</name>
		<desc>Think like Bond, act like Bond, and experience an entirely new Bond adventure. James Bond, the world's greatest secret agent, returns in Everything or Nothing with new guns and gadgets, combat skills, and clever tricks--and it's up to you to put them to good use. Travel through four exciting continents including the Valley of the Kings in Egypt and the French Quarter in New Orleans. The game also features two-player co-op missions and four-player multiplayer arena modes.</desc>
		<image>./images/007 - Everything or Nothing (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/007 - Everything or Nothing (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/007 - Everything or Nothing (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/007 - Everything or Nothing (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/007 - Everything or Nothing (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20040217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<family>James Bond 007</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="4932">
		<path>./007 - From Russia with Love (USA).iso</path>
		<name>James Bond 007: From Russia With Love</name>
		<desc>Inspired by the 1963 movie of the same name, From Russia with Love lets you play as the classic James Bond as portrayed by Sean Connery. You can drive in classic cars and use upgradeable weapons and gadgetry to complete the game's nonlinear missions. From Russia with Love also lets you invest in and upgrade your character to customize his performance.</desc>
		<image>./images/007 - From Russia with Love (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/007 - From Russia with Love (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/007 - From Russia with Love (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/007 - From Russia with Love (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/007 - From Russia with Love (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<family>James Bond 007</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="4798">
		<path>./007 - Nightfire (USA).iso</path>
		<name>007: NightFire</name>
		<desc>The ultimate secret agent is back in his most dangerous adventure yet in James Bond 007: NightFire. Explore new heights and depths like never before--infiltrate towering skyscrapers, take on treacherous underwater missions, and maneuver your sleek Aston Martin V12 Vanquish through the streets of Tokyo. New state-of-the-art upgradeable gadgets and weapons and original missions--including zero-gravity assignments--will leave you shaken and stirred.</desc>
		<image>./images/007 - Nightfire (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/007 - Nightfire (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/007 - Nightfire (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/007 - Nightfire (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/007 - Nightfire (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20021119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>James Bond 007</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="4976">
		<path>./1080 Avalanche (USA).iso</path>
		<name>1080° Avalanche</name>
		<desc>Nintendo takes players back to the slopes with 1080 Avalanche, the sequel to the popular N64 title 1080 Snowboarding. Detailed character models, interactive environments and overhauled snowboarding physics take advantage of the processing power of the GameCube. The game features more than a dozen snow-filled mountain tracks, complete with varied snow conditions and interactive environments that throw new challenges at players, including dangerous avalanches, collapsing bridges, cave-ins, and more. Race against computer opponents, against course times, in four player mode, or just to earn trick points. Master a new set of tricks involving flips, twists, grabs and grinds.</desc>
		<image>./images/1080 Avalanche (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/1080 Avalanche (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/1080 Avalanche (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/1080 Avalanche (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/1080 Avalanche (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NST</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skiing</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5205">
		<path>./18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker (USA).iso</path>
		<name>18 Wheeler: American Pro Trucker</name>
		<desc>Join the convoy! AM2's off the wall arcade smash, 18-Wheeler American Pro Trucker is rambling to the PlayStation2 computer entertainment system for one heck'uva pit stop! Get behind the wheel of a 60 foot long, 20 ton, 18-wheeled beast and buckle up as you haul tail from New York to California and everywhere in between in the most intense joyride of your life! 10-4 good buddy - Over and out!</desc>
		<image>./images/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20020218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="78463">
		<path>./2002 FIFA World Cup Korea Japan (USA).iso</path>
		<name>2002 FIFA World Cup</name>
		<desc>The 2002 installment in the Electronic Arts soccer series. The game features 16 leagues, 500-plus teams and a total of 10 tournaments. FIFA also makes use of a reward system that lets you unlock new tournaments and even get some player cards. All of the game's rosters can be manipulated, teams can be edited (uniforms, stadiums, etc.), current players can be tweaked and new players can be created. As far as modes go, FIFA 2002 adds a World Cup qualification tournament. This allows you to take any of the teams in the AFC, CONCACAF, UEFA, or CONMEBOL and go through a series of matches that determine who gets to participate in the 2002 World Cup in Korea in Japan.</desc>
		<image>./images/2002 FIFA World Cup Korea Japan (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/2002 FIFA World Cup Korea Japan (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/2002 FIFA World Cup Korea Japan (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/2002 FIFA World Cup Korea Japan (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/2002 FIFA World Cup Korea Japan (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer</genre>
		<family>FIFA</family>
		<players>4+</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5220">
		<path>./4x4 Evo 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>4x4 Evo 2</name>
		<desc>So you've had enough of watching your favorite SUV pillage some rocky terrain in a TV commercial and decide to imitate art. Only, you paid a lot for that SUV and the idea of scratching its paint or blowing out its transmission is holding you back from your dirty dreams. Worry not, Mud Warrior, just slip in 4x4 EVO 2 and witness the awesome power high torque all terrain vehicles possess. The game features Quick Race, Free Roam, Time Attack and Career Racing, hundreds of licensed vehicles, parts for customization, and 30 racing stages from across the world.</desc>
		<image>./images/4x4 Evo 2 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/4x4 Evo 2 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/4x4 Evo 2 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/4x4 Evo 2 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/4x4 Evo 2 (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20021010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Terminal Reality</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5021">
		<path>./Aggressive Inline (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Aggressive Inline</name>
		<desc>Chris Edwards Aggressive Inline is a trick-based action sports game featuring extreme sports legend Chris Edwards, the founding father of aggressive inline skating, as well as other high-profile skaters such Taig Kris, Jaren Grob and Shane Yost. Gamers can play as one of their favorite inline stars, as they master and explore an array of fully-interactive levels, each filled with pedestrians, traffic systems and outrageous gravity-defying challenges.</desc>
		<image>./images/Aggressive Inline (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Aggressive Inline (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Aggressive Inline (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Aggressive Inline (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Z-Axis</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5194">
		<path>./Alien Hominid (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Alien Hominid</name>
		<desc>You're a little yellow alien.  The FBI has shot down your ship while flying over planet Earth.  And it, quite literally, lands right on their doorstep.  After a series of FBI Agents swipe your ship, what option do you have other than to blow up everything in your path to get it back?

Alien Hominid is a 2D side-scrolling shooter with heavy references to the Metal Slug series of games - from the hand-drawn graphics, huge explosions, right down to the ability to eviscerate FBI Agents when you get up close to them.  The graphics are by featured artist Dan Paladin.  Your goal, is quite simply, to get to the end of the stage, and die as little as possible.  Which is made difficult due to the fact that any bullet is an instant kill.

To help you out, you can grab a range of power-ups, such as lasers, spread shots, shotguns and more, as well as hijacking vehicles and using them for protection.  Grenades can be lobbed, and you can jump on enemy shoulders and choose to bite their heads off if you like, or pick them up and throw them at other enemies.  You can also dive underground for a short period of time to avoid enemies - while underground, you can drag agents into the ground to kill them.

The GBA version of the game is identical in gameplay, however, with a few bosses removed (such as the robot bee and the FBI big-fisted tank robot).  The PlayStation 2, Xbox and Xbox 360 versions of the game include a special "PDA Game" with very simple-looking graphics.  Your goal in this game is to kill all the agents by hopping on their heads, and then reach the exit.  Included with this game is a level editor, allowing you to make your own levels and then send them to friends if you have the Xbox or Xbox 360 version.</desc>
		<image>./images/Alien Hominid (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Alien Hominid (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Alien Hominid (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Alien Hominid (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Alien Hominid (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20041121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Behemoth</developer>
		<publisher>O3 Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5326">
		<path>./All-Star Baseball 2002 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>All-Star Baseball 2002</name>
		<desc>Marketed behind 4-Time World Series Champion and New York Yankee Shortstop, Derek Jeter, All-Star Baseball 2002 brings to the Gamecube its fantastic double play combination of superior game-play and outstanding graphics. In fact, the All-Star Baseball franchise is so strong, it has the distinction of being selected twice as Baseball Game Of The Year!</desc>
		<image>./images/All-Star Baseball 2002 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/All-Star Baseball 2002 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/All-Star Baseball 2002 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/All-Star Baseball 2002 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20011118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>All-Star Baseball</family>
		<players>4+</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5268">
		<path>./All-Star Baseball 2003 featuring Derek Jeter (USA).iso</path>
		<name>All-star Baseball 2003</name>
		<desc>Four-time World Series Champion Derek Jeter headlines this latest edition of All-Star Baseball. Every player from the Major League Baseball 2002-2003 season is here, with hundreds of stats, rules and options to modify and jazz up your baseball experience. Along with the usual season mode, there's also the playoff's to be won, home run competition's, multiplayer options and all-star modes.</desc>
		<image>./images/All-Star Baseball 2003 featuring Derek Jeter (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/All-Star Baseball 2003 featuring Derek Jeter (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/All-Star Baseball 2003 featuring Derek Jeter (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/All-Star Baseball 2003 featuring Derek Jeter (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>All-Star Baseball</family>
		<players>4+</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5306">
		<path>./All-Star Baseball 2004 featuring Derek Jeter (USA).iso</path>
		<name>All-Start Baseball 2004</name>
		<desc>All-Star Baseball 2003 combines true-to-life graphics with superior gameplay to create the most exciting baseball experience for any fan. Featuring Derek Jeter, four-time World Series Champion, All-Star Baseball 2003 is the only baseball game available this year on all next generation hardware systems.</desc>
		<image>./images/All-Star Baseball 2004 featuring Derek Jeter (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/All-Star Baseball 2004 featuring Derek Jeter (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/All-Star Baseball 2004 featuring Derek Jeter (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/All-Star Baseball 2004 featuring Derek Jeter (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>All-Star Baseball</family>
		<players>4+</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5227">
		<path>./Amazing Island (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Amazing Island</name>
		<desc>The 'black evil' has taken over the island, and the Maboo Tribe have called upon you to bring order and outcast the evil that has taken control. To do so, you must create your own creature and train it up, entering it into various competitions against the 'black evil' and working towards the main goal. As the competitions are completed, you will unlock new features to improve your own creature in speed, strength and general looks.

Play single and multiplayer battles on the GameCube, or upload your creatures to the Game Boy Advance, taking them on the road to challenge your friends and unlocking unique items and features for the creatures you design.</desc>
		<image>./images/Amazing Island (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Amazing Island (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Amazing Island (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Amazing Island (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20040824T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ancient</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5204">
		<path>./American Chopper 2 - Full Throttle (USA).iso</path>
		<name>American Chopper 2 - Full Throttle</name>
		<desc>A motorcycle enthusiast's game based on Discovery Channel's hit TV series. Gamers take on the role of Paul Sr., Paulie, Mikey or Vinnie and are challenged to build four choppers for an upcoming motorcycle competition. All the while, gamers must compete in family battles, races and other biker challenges in order to earn bike parts and the respect of Paul Sr. Players test their custom creations at the final showdown.</desc>
		<image>./images/American Chopper 2 - Full Throttle (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/American Chopper 2 - Full Throttle (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/American Chopper 2 - Full Throttle (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/American Chopper 2 - Full Throttle (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Creat Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="4772">
		<path>./Animal Crossing (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Animal Crossing</name>
		<desc>Occasionally strange but completely addictive, Nintendo's Animal Crossing for the GameCube is not so much a game as a simulation of life on a small town. Players begin the game by setting out to live life on their own in a colorful town, where they are greeted by a seemingly endless supply of things to do and characters to meet.Time passes in Animal Crossing in real-time, as the month, day, season, and time of day matches that of the player's. Holiday seasons come and go in Animal Crossing, just as they would in the real world. Experience the freedom to fish, decorate your house, go bug catching, garden, write letters, and even play original Nintendo NES games in this imaginative, and addictive game.</desc>
		<image>./images/Animal Crossing (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Animal Crossing (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Animal Crossing (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Animal Crossing (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Animal Crossing (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Animal Crossing</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5013">
		<path>./Animaniacs - The Great Edgar Hunt (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Animaniacs: The Great Edgar Hunt</name>
		<desc>Based on the multiple Emmy Award-winning animated series from Warner Bros. Animation and Amblin Entertainment, and featuring the actual voice actors from the series. Animaniacs: The Great Edgar Hunt is a third-person action adventure, which brings the colourful and hysterical world of the Animaniacs wonderfully to life. Players must guide the Warner brothers - and the Warner sister - through six levels in a quest to locate the hidden Edgar trophies. Wakko, Yakko and Dot each have their own special abilities, and each must be used in order to fully explore the luscious landscapes. Five 'Pinky &amp; The Brain mini-games vary the pace of the adventure, as they explore the huge Animaniacs world, which is populated with dozens of characters from the cartoon.</desc>
		<image>./images/Animaniacs - The Great Edgar Hunt (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Animaniacs - The Great Edgar Hunt (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Animaniacs - The Great Edgar Hunt (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Animaniacs - The Great Edgar Hunt (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Animaniacs - The Great Edgar Hunt (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20051014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Warthog</developer>
		<publisher>Ignition Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Animaniacs</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5256">
		<path>./Ant Bully, The (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Lucas Fourmi Malgre Lui</name>
		<desc>Go pick on someone your own size! After bullying an innocent ant colony, a young boy named Lucas is magically shrunk down to ant size and embarks on a remarkable adventure. Play as Lucas, experiencing the dangerous and thrilling life of an ant as you battle, explore and forge new friendships with natives and other species in his new ant world. Help Lucas evolve from recluse to hero in his quest to save the colony from extermination. Based on the exciting moments from Warner Bros CG animated movie directed by John A. Davis (of the Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius series.)</desc>
		<image>./images/Ant Bully, The (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ant Bully, The (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ant Bully, The (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ant Bully, The (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20070502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artificial Mind &amp; Movement</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5150">
		<path>./Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Aquaman: Battle of Atlantis</name>
		<desc>Aquaman, DC Comics' superhero who can breathe underwater and communicate telepathically with marine animals, is coming to next-generation consoles. Developer and publisher TDK Mediactive has not announced which platforms yet, but a GameCube release seems likely.</desc>
		<image>./images/Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Aquaman - Battle for Atlantis (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>20030730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lucky Chicken</developer>
		<publisher>TDK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161610" />
	</game>
	<game id="5287">
		<path>./Army Men - Air Combat - The Elite Missions (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Army Men : Air Combat : The Elite Missions</name>
		<desc>Army Men: Air Combat - The Elite Missions is a fast and furious game of toy helicopter-based combat set in the Army Men universe. It combines the trigger-twitching action of shooter-style gameplay with more strategic environment interaction via the winch mechanic. Continuing the classic struggle between the Green and Tan Armies, the heroic Captain Blade and his Alpha Wolf Squadron once again take to the skies with an onslaught of missions, incredible helicopter physics, deep gameplay, stunning cinematics and exciting character interaction. Real Combat. Plastic Men.</desc>
		<image>./images/Army Men - Air Combat - The Elite Missions (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Army Men - Air Combat - The Elite Missions (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Army Men - Air Combat - The Elite Missions (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Army Men - Air Combat - The Elite Missions (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Army Men - Air Combat - The Elite Missions (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20030326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3DO</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Plane, 3rd person</genre>
		<family>Army Men</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161613" />
	</game>
	<game id="5036">
		<path>./Batman - Rise of Sin Tzu (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Batman: Rise of Sin Tzu</name>
		<desc>Sin Tzu, cunning master of strategy and martial arts, makes history as the first Batman character to debut in a video game. To commemorate this event, DC Comics and Warner Bros. have showcased the talents of veteran scriptwriter Flint Dille and reknown comic book artist, Jim Lee as Sin Tzu's co-creators and character designers. The third-person action game lets up to two players join forces as Batman and Robin or Nightwing and Batgirl and take on the scum of Gotham City. Utilizing 35 different attacks and plenty of Bat-gadgets, players fight their way through 12 levels, from the Gotham City Docks to the infamous Arkham Asylum.</desc>
		<image>./images/Batman - Rise of Sin Tzu (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Batman - Rise of Sin Tzu (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Batman - Rise of Sin Tzu (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Batman - Rise of Sin Tzu (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Batman - Rise of Sin Tzu (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20031111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<family>Batman</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161620" />
	</game>
	<game id="4954">
		<path>./Batman - Vengeance (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Batman: Vengeance</name>
		<desc>Batman Vengeance, developed by Ubi Soft Montreal, is a 3D action-adventure based on the animated television series. The game pits players as the Dark Knight himself on a quest to stop a mysterious crime wave in Gotham City. Batman has full freedom of movement to go anywhere within wide-open, sprawling 3D environments -- some that stretch up and up and up. The caped crusader can walk, run, sneak against walls, climb, glide through the air with his cape and engage in hand-to-hand combat. The game features 19 stages, 40 minutes of rendered cinematics, and plenty of Bat gadgets, like batarangs, batgrapples, flash bombs, remote charges, batcuffs, nets, the batlauncher, batscope and more.</desc>
		<image>./images/Batman - Vengeance (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Batman - Vengeance (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Batman - Vengeance (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Batman - Vengeance (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Batman - Vengeance (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20011118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Fighter Scrolling</genre>
		<family>Batman</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161627" />
	</game>
	<game id="4961">
		<path>./Batman Begins (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Batman Begins</name>
		<desc>In this adaptation of the film of the same name, the origins of the Batman legend are explored. Playing as both Bruce Wayne and his alter-ego, Batman, you will need to hunt evil forces in familiar locations such as Arkham asylum, Gotham City, but also in the Himalaya. Using both stealth and brutal skills, you take on enemies in true beat-em-up style. Batman has a vast array of moves, from kicks and punches to more exotic special moves. Multiple enemies can be attacked at once, and there are tricks to break through enemies' defenses. Also, certain attacks can only be used as a finishing move when opponents are weakened.

Next to the melee combat, Batman carries his Bat Utility Belt with a Batgrapple to reach higher areas, the Batarang and gadgets such as smoke and flash grenades, a lockpick, camera hacker and an optical wire to peek from behind corners.

Certain levels turn Batman Begins into a racing game, as you drive the shiny Batmobile at high speeds though Gotham City. During these missions, your progress is measured by a reputation meter, which increases when you take out cops and thugs, and decreases when you harm civilians. There is nitro available for even higher speeds and an armour meter shows the status of your car.</desc>
		<image>./images/Batman Begins (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Batman Begins (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Batman Begins (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Batman Begins (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Batman Begins (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Eurocom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Batman</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161710" />
	</game>
	<game id="4872">
		<path>./Battalion Wars (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Battalion Wars</name>
		<desc>You play in a fictional world, where war has erupted between the Frontiers and the Tundrans.  You are ordered to command the Frontiers to victory.  Using your troops you can command them to attack, defend, and follow you, as well as garrison them in bunkers, capture bases, and hop in vehicles.  You can switch between a first-person view, and control one of your men to lead in battle, or you can use the top-down view, where you have a good view of the battlefield.  Through an expansive campaign, a number of different nations, and a garrison that would impress even Napoleon, you can see just how fun war may be.</desc>
		<image>./images/Battalion Wars (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Battalion Wars (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Battalion Wars (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Battalion Wars (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Kuju Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T161710" />
	</game>
	<game id="5007">
		<path>./Beach Spikers - Virtua Beach Volleyball (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Beach Spikers</name>
		<desc>Beach Spikers is an action beach volleyball game for one to four players. Several modes of gameplay are included: arcade (a conversion of the arcade game), world tour (the player creates a team, develops a relationship with their partner to increase her ability, and aims to be the world champs), vs mode (play against other players or the cpu) and a tutorial mode. Several mini-games are also featured, such as beach countdown where teams play volleyball with a bomb and hope it doesn't explode on their side of the net, and beach flags where the player needs to capture a flag before their opponent.

Beach Spikers comes with a number of predefined teams, or the player can create their own team from a variety of female athletes. Each character can be customized in appearance as well, from hair and skin color to uniform.</desc>
		<image>./images/Beach Spikers - Virtua Beach Volleyball (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Beach Spikers - Virtua Beach Volleyball (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Beach Spikers - Virtua Beach Volleyball (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Beach Spikers - Virtua Beach Volleyball (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Beach Spikers - Virtua Beach Volleyball (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020812T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5010">
		<path>./Beyblade VForce - Super Tournament Battle (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Beyblade : VForce</name>
		<desc>Beyblade is a baffling game that is both so niche and so ill- executed that I can only recommended to the true fanatics out there who devour anything the franchise has to offer. Everyone else will be downright insulted by the simple, stupid game mechanics and horrendously outdated visual and audio presentations. This title does not look, sound or act any differently from its PS1 predecessor, which is a travesty.
                Stay as far away from this unfortunate digital afterbirth as possible.</desc>
		<image>./images/Beyblade VForce - Super Tournament Battle (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Beyblade VForce - Super Tournament Battle (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Beyblade VForce - Super Tournament Battle (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Beyblade VForce - Super Tournament Battle (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Takara</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Beyblade</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4785">
		<path>./Beyond Good &amp; Evil (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Beyond Good &amp; Evil</name>
		<desc>In the future, on the planet Hillys, the population suffers from constant attacks from the alien DomZ. The situation is gradually getting worse, as the rate of DomZ kidnapings increase. The Alpha Section forces, who are in charge of protecting citizens, seem to be completely ineffective, not even fighting the DomZ. In the midst of this situation, the secretive organization IRIS alleges that the Alpha Section is involved in a massive government conspiracy, and seeks to expose the truth through journalism.

You control the young reporter/photographer Jade, with her companions Pey'j and Double H. After experiencing first-hand a DomZ attack, she is contacted by IRIS, who recruit her as an action reporter. Jade is now tasked with infiltrating the Alpha Section, exposing the government conspiracy, and ultimately finding the truth for herself.

Beyond Good &amp; Evil is an action-adventure game with diverse game play. Most of the game is based on stealth and puzzles, but there are sequences of racing, shooting, combat, and platform action. There are several mini-games and even an online ranking system (used by entering codes online after they are assigned in-game when the game is saved). As the game progresses, a large story unfolds, even dealing with some social issues on the way.</desc>
		<image>./images/Beyond Good &amp; Evil (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Beyond Good &amp; Evil (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Beyond Good &amp; Evil (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Beyond Good &amp; Evil (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Beyond Good &amp; Evil (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5190">
		<path>./Big Air Freestyle (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Big Air Freestyle</name>
		<desc>Big Air Freestyle is a motor cycle racing game with up to 10 riders on over 20 different tracks, supercross or motorcross. Also includes 6 freestyle arenas and multiplayer.

You can select from 3 classes of bikes. The 125cc class has the lowest speed but most control. 250cc has an equal amount of speed and control. The 500cc has the most speed but the least control.

With the 6 freestyle arenas your goal is to perform as many stunts as you can within a given time limit. There are seven Fantasy Stunts in the game that must be unlocked for you to be able to perform them.</desc>
		<image>./images/Big Air Freestyle (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Big Air Freestyle (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Big Air Freestyle (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Big Air Freestyle (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Paradigm Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5224">
		<path>./Big Mutha Truckers (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Big Mutha Truckers</name>
		<desc>Big Mutha Truckers is a truck racing game where you are one of Ma Jackson's four kids. You have to make money for 60 days. The one who earns most money in that period will get Ma's bussiness. There are plenty obstacles to change your success to failure.

Players make cash by trading various commodities in the five cities that make up Hick State County, by taking on special jobs (some legal, some not so legal), by wagering with other rival drivers and by causing as much chaos as possible!</desc>
		<image>./images/Big Mutha Truckers (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Big Mutha Truckers (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Big Mutha Truckers (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Big Mutha Truckers (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<developer>Empire Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4889">
		<path>./Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Billy Hatcher And The Giant Egg</name>
		<desc>A boy and his friends playing in the forest get transported to a magical land. Separated from his friends billy finds...a chicken suit? This suit lets him hatch eggs in his quest to bring back morning, save the giant egg, and defeat the evil crows who want to destroy it. On the way he can hatch eggs that he finds when he does he is rewarded with mystical creatures and ''hats''. These help him defeat the crows and save the giant egg.</desc>
		<image>./images/Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5090">
		<path>./Bionicle (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bionicle</name>
		<desc>There's turmoil in the island of Mata Nui. The dark spirit Makuta has infected the Rahi throughout the island -- using his control of the Bohrok, Bohrok-Kal, and Rahkshi to kidnap the Matoran villagers throughout the various Wahi. It's up to the guardians of each Wahi, the Toa warriors Tahi, Lewa, Kopaka, Gali, Pohatu, and Onua, to rescue the Matorans and find the Toa of Light, who is the only one strong enough to stop Makuta. Players control the six Toa heroes in this blend of platform action, combat and racing. Use elemental powers to defeat enemies, then snowboard down mountains, surf through lava fields, ride mine carts and grind along tree limbs.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bionicle (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bionicle (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bionicle (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bionicle (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20031020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Bionicle</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5141">
		<path>./Bionicle Heroes (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bionicle Heroes</name>
		<desc>Bionicle Heroes brings to life the most powerful and exciting LEGO characters ever seen in one game, in an action-packed world of adventure and discovery. Take control of a young hero as he steps out of the real world and into the strange and dangerous universe of Bionicle. Only by mastering the powers and special abilities of the greatest Bionicle heroes will he be able to overcome the many challenges ahead.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bionicle Heroes (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bionicle Heroes (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bionicle Heroes (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bionicle Heroes (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Bionicle Heroes (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060406T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Bionicle</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5091">
		<path>./Black &amp; Bruised (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Black &amp; Bruised</name>
		<desc>Black &amp; Bruised is a cartoonish take on boxing with 18 different boxers, each with their own personality and fighting style.  There are five different modes including multi-player, exhibition and a story mode told with CG with each boxer's life story is played out in story mode.  Each boxer has a different special attack and power-ups can be picked up to use in matches.  There are 30 different facial expressions for each boxer reacting to punches and misses giving them a life-like appearance.</desc>
		<image>./images/Black &amp; Bruised (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Black &amp; Bruised (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Black &amp; Bruised (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Black &amp; Bruised (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Fiction</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4909">
		<path>./Blood Omen 2 - The Legacy of Kain Series (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Blood Omen 2</name>
		<desc>Blood Omen 2 puts you in the role of the vampire Kain as he searches for his slain brethren. You'll move through crowds while cloaked in stealth, feed on the peasant herds, and use mind control to overcome vampire-proof inventions. With each success, you gain dark powers that give you access to treacherous new areas and help you fight stronger enemies. As you develop your vampire skills, you'll unfold the continuing epic of Nosgoth and Kain's attempts to rule over the realm .</desc>
		<image>./images/Blood Omen 2 - The Legacy of Kain Series (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Blood Omen 2 - The Legacy of Kain Series (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Blood Omen 2 - The Legacy of Kain Series (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Blood Omen 2 - The Legacy of Kain Series (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Blood Omen 2 - The Legacy of Kain Series (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Legacy of Kain</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5079">
		<path>./BloodRayne (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bloodrayne</name>
		<desc>There are things in the world that humanity should not know about, and things it must be protected from. It is these things that the Brimstone Society hunts, and their newest agent for the cause is the half-vampire codenamed BloodRayne. Her mission will take her from clearing out the walking dead and man-sized insects in the swamps of Louisiana to hunting down members of the secretive Gegengheist Gruppe branch of the Nazi military around the world, as well as the monsters they unwittingly awakened.

Rayne's primary weapons against both monsters and men are the blades attached to her arms, and as the game progresses she will gain additional attacks to string together. Rayne can also hold many weapons, such as pistols, shotguns, and sub machine guns, at once, but she is not overly attached to them and will discard any weapon that runs dry. Her enhanced vampiric strength even allows her to rip up mounted gun emplacements and fire them from the hip. Another vampiric strength is her ability to drain the blood out of any human she can grab in order to restore her health. By killing enemies Rayne's rage meter will fill, eventually allowing her to enter Blood Rage, slowing the world around her and gaining new combo attacks that can dismember or totally cut in half weaker opponents. Rayne's ability to perceive the world will grow as the game progresses as well, allowing her to see living things through walls, zoom in on distant targets, and speed up her perception that everything, herself included, appear to slow down.</desc>
		<image>./images/BloodRayne (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/BloodRayne (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/BloodRayne (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/BloodRayne (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/BloodRayne (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Majesco</developer>
		<publisher>Terminal Reality</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4849">
		<path>./Bloody Roar - Primal Fury (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bloody Roar : Primal Fury</name>
		<desc>Primal Fury, called Bloody Roar Extreme in Japan, is a traditional 3D polygonal fighter that boasts a brawling style similar to that of Fighting Vipers. The twist is that each of the game's 16 characters can transform from human to beast shape and take on new fighting abilities. Bloody Roar: Primal Fury comes as an updated port to the PlayStation 2 released Bloody Roar 3, and is differentiated by enhanced, more detailed graphics, more rounded character models and a better framerate, among other additions. Developed by Eighting, the game is rated "T" for Teen by the ESRB.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bloody Roar - Primal Fury (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bloody Roar - Primal Fury (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bloody Roar - Primal Fury (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bloody Roar - Primal Fury (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5307">
		<path>./Blowout (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Blowout</name>
		<desc>Blowout is a game that takes a classic gameplay concept and updates it with modern graphics and sounds. This game is a side-scrolling platform shooter. The graphics are 3-dimensional polygons, but the action stays almost entirely in a 2-dimensional plane.

The setting for the game is a space station that has been overrun by hostile aliens. You play as a bad-ass soldier dude who will single-handedly wipe the aliens out.

You travel around each level in a non-linear fashion.  You have to fight your way through endless hordes to find keys, flip switches, use elevators, and then ultimately defeat a big boss at the end.</desc>
		<image>./images/Blowout (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Blowout (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Blowout (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Blowout (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20031126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaos Kontrol</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4908">
		<path>./Bomberman Generation (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bomberman Generation</name>
		<desc>Bomberman returns with a new cel-shaded 3D look. The same storyline applies, however. Bomberman has been given the task of taking back a powerful element of magic, and protecting it from the hands of evil. To do so, he must use his bombing abilites to blast his way through mazes filled with crazy enemies and hidden secrets. There are 5 worlds in all, each with 16 levels to complete. And after completing cetain objectives and picking up items, Bomberman will learn new techniques and abilities to improve his range with his bombs or use new weapons.

Also included is a 4 player classic bomberman multi-player modes. Unlike the adventure mode, all of the multi-player modes are set in the original 2D, top down style perspective. The last man standing wins in most rounds, with the added twist of other enemies on screen and timed battles.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bomberman Generation (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bomberman Generation (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bomberman Generation (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bomberman Generation (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Bomberman Generation (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Universal</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Bomberman</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5195">
		<path>./Bomberman Jetters (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bomberman Jetters</name>
		<desc>Bomberman is back in his second game for the Nintendo Gamecube. Jetters features a single-player campaign and the fan-favorite multiplayer battles. In the single-player game, players take on the roles of Bomberman and Max. Your goal is to stop the Hige Hige Bandits who plan to destroy Planet Bomber by crashing an artificial comet, Dark Star, into it. In this platforming quest, you will be aided by your use of bombs, and by Charaboms, creatures that you find that have their own special abilities that will help you progress through the game. After feeding a Charabom it will evolve, which will then make it more powerful. There are many types of Bombs and Charaboms to find throughout the single-player adventure.

Jetters also contains the classic Bomberman 4-player battles in which you and up to 3 friends basically blast each other with bombs until only 1 Bomberman remains. There is a revenge feature which keeps you in the action even after you lose. If you get blown up by a bomb, you appear on the exterior of the arena and can shoot bombs at players in the game, making sure that you can always be a part of the action.

There are 8 main battle arenas and many different types of multi-player battles. Bomberman Jetters was also originally released as a budget title for only $19.99, which made it less than half the price of most games when they first come out.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bomberman Jetters (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bomberman Jetters (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bomberman Jetters (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bomberman Jetters (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Majesco</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<family>Bomberman</family>
		<players>4+</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5152">
		<path>./Bratz - Forever Diamondz (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bratz : Forever Diamondz</name>
		<desc>Yasmin, Cloe, Sasha, and Jade are back for a brand new adventure sending them across the country in search of the hottest fashion designer. Players will experience unique adventures through the eyes of the four playable characters, in detailed open world environments, as they compete for a spot in "America Rocks Fashion" TV show. Fans will discover new features that include a figure skating competition and the ability to adopt a pet to train, dress, accessorize and showcase in competitions.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bratz - Forever Diamondz (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bratz - Forever Diamondz (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bratz - Forever Diamondz (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bratz - Forever Diamondz (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<developer>Blitz Games</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5169">
		<path>./Bratz - Rock Angelz (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bratz : Rock Angelz</name>
		<desc>Bratz Rock Angelz will empower fans of the wildly popular line of fashion dolls to explore their own "passion for fashion" in a unique interactive adventure game. Fans will be immersed in the Bratz World as they embark on a series of voyages in search of intriguing stories to inspire and create their very own fashion magazine. Bratz Rock Angelz lets you slip into the shes of any of the four Bratz Girls. You can customize all of the Bratz girls hair, make-up, and outfits as you shop for the latest fashions and travel to exotic International locations to investigate the hottest stories to create your own fashion magazine. Bratz Rock Angelz literally brings the toy franchise to life by letting players chat face-to-face with the Bratz characters in their own world.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bratz - Rock Angelz (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bratz - Rock Angelz (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bratz - Rock Angelz (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bratz - Rock Angelz (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<developer>Blitz Games</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4828">
		<path>./Buffy the Vampire Slayer - Chaos Bleeds (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Buffy the Vampire Slayer: Chaos Bleeds</name>
		<desc>Buffy the Vampire Slayer: Chaos Bleeds is a 3rd person action-adventure game based on the successful cult series Buffy the Vampire Slayer. Just like the show, the adventure takes place at ground zero for all things vampire -- Sunnydale, California. Developed with the show's writers as a 'lost episode' from season 5, Chaos Bleeds involves an unraveling tale in which a dimensional bleed has been enabled by Pure Evil to consume humanity once and for all. It's up to Buffy and her friends to stop it all from happening ... again!</desc>
		<image>./images/Buffy the Vampire Slayer - Chaos Bleeds (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Buffy the Vampire Slayer - Chaos Bleeds (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Buffy the Vampire Slayer - Chaos Bleeds (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Buffy the Vampire Slayer - Chaos Bleeds (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20030828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Universal</developer>
		<publisher>Eurocom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5025">
		<path>./Burnout (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Burnout</name>
		<desc>Burnout is a arcade style racing game in the mold of the Test Drive or Need For Speed series.  In this game, you are racing on realistic streets with real traffic to contend with.

There are 6 courses on which to race, 3 of which are reminiscent of Europe, and 3 from the USA.  There are several vehicles to choose from, ranging from compact cars to pickups.  However, they are not based on real makes and models.

One notable feature of Burnout is the "Burn Meter."  The Burn Meter is a gauge that is filled by performing reckless stunts, like racing into oncoming traffic, or power-drifting through corners.  Once the Burn Meter is filled, your car gets a super speed boost.</desc>
		<image>./images/Burnout (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Burnout (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Burnout (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Burnout (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Burnout (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Games</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Burnout</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4935">
		<path>./Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Burnout 2 : Point of Impact</name>
		<desc>Burnout 2: Point of Impact builds upon this strong speed-driven franchise with improved gameplay, new game options and bigger, better and more insane crashes. Players can test their nerves and skills by taking to the air, sliding through corners, and swerving to avoid head-on collisions, while filling their meter to unleash a burst of speed previously exclusive to airplanes. In addition to an offensive driving 101, Burnout 2 features a four-player crash mode, six different locations with 30 stages, realistic weather effects, and 14 cars (plus hidden ones). The GameCube release improves over the PlayStation 2 original with 15 additional crash junctions. Supports DPL2 and 480p.</desc>
		<image>./images/Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Burnout 2 - Point of Impact (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030409T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Games</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Burnout</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5177">
		<path>./Bust-A-Move 3000 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bust-a-Move 3000</name>
		<desc>The legendary Super Bust a Move is has arrived on the GameCube with 5 challenging modes to test your skills, including the new 4 player mode</desc>
		<image>./images/Bust-A-Move 3000 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bust-A-Move 3000 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bust-A-Move 3000 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bust-A-Move 3000 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Bust-A-Move 3000 (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="59895">
		<path>./Cabela's Big Game Hunter 2005 Adventures (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Cabela's Big Game Hunter - 2005 Adventures</name>
		<desc>The hunt returns in Cabela's Big Game Hunter: 2005 Adventures. Get in on the pulse-pounding hunting action as you stalk a variety of game. This hunting simulation attempts to bring as much authenticity as possible to the console-hunting genre. Players can stalk their prey through realistic environments that feature changing seasons, weather, diverse vegetation, rivers, and lakes. There are fines for violating hunting laws and several choices of firearms, ammunition, and hunting vehicles. Play 18 unique missions on a variety of terrains. And in Career Hunt mode you can unlock new equipment and missions.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cabela's Big Game Hunter 2005 Adventures (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Cabela's Big Game Hunter 2005 Adventures (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Cabela's Big Game Hunter 2005 Adventures (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cabela's Big Game Hunter 2005 Adventures (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fun Labs</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Cabela's</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="59897">
		<path>./Cabela's Outdoor Adventures (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Cabela's Outdoor Adventures</name>
		<desc>Cabela's Outdoor Adventures provides you with the hunting and fishing expedition of a lifetime with 22 outdoor adventures across North America and beyond. Fly, float, and trek from Utah to Mexico to New Zealand in search of trophy bucks or stop off and angle for the local species of fish. While on your adventure you'll also have the opportunity to hunt both big game and small game, compete in a shooting contest, and embark on varied missions. Your Cabela's Guide introduces each true-to-life outdoor adventure where stealth strategy and technique are of the utmost importance.

                New enhancements for 2006 include:
                * Mini-Map that allows you to sense and see where the game is hiding
                * Lock-On, which secures your aim over a target for a sure kill in easy mode
                * Steady Aim, featuring a finer control over your aim--mimicking the calm a hunter must achieve before squeezing the trigger
                * Sprint mode to get into position to take your best shot
                * Angling for bass in pristine streams while territorial bears protect their fishing spots
                * Variety of species of deer, big and small game animals, and fish</desc>
		<image>./images/Cabela's Outdoor Adventures (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Cabela's Outdoor Adventures (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Cabela's Outdoor Adventures (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cabela's Outdoor Adventures (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20050913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magic Wand Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Cabela's</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4865">
		<path>./Call of Duty - Finest Hour (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Call of Duty: Finest Hour</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty: Finest Hour is a squad-based console first-person shooter set in WWII. Head to the frontlines of combat to experience intense battlefield moments from World War II's most legendary conflicts including the Russian infantry charge at Stalingrad, the British PPA Commando raids in North Africa and the American led tank charges in Belgium -- through the eyes of citizen soldiers from an alliance of countries who together helped shape the course of modern history. Take on the Nazi war machine through authentic single-player combat missions and utilize an explosive arsenal of WWII weapons from the Russian, British, American and German armories, including pistols, machine guns, sniper rifles and grenades. Play as an American, British or Russian soldier, each with his own story.</desc>
		<image>./images/Call of Duty - Finest Hour (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Call of Duty - Finest Hour (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Call of Duty - Finest Hour (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Call of Duty - Finest Hour (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Creative Sparks</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Call Of Duty</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4882">
		<path>./Call of Duty 2 - Big Red One (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Call of Duty 2 : Big Red One</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty 2: Big Red One offers cinematic intensity as never before on consoles. The hallmark cinematic intensity of Call of Duty returns with a more complete gameplay experience of World War II combat. Experience a wide variety of missions on land, sea, and in the air, with the aid of over three dozen authentic American, Italian, French, and German weapons. Charge into battle together as Allied and Axis planes duel overhead, artillery explosions shake the ground and choke the air, and bullets and shrapnel streak past you and your squadmates. Experience war-torn Europe and Africa, from the blistering desert expanses of Tunisia and Libya to the beautiful yet deadly countrysides of Italy, France, Belgium, and Germany.</desc>
		<image>./images/Call of Duty 2 - Big Red One (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Call of Duty 2 - Big Red One (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Call of Duty 2 - Big Red One (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Call of Duty 2 - Big Red One (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treyarch Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Call Of Duty</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5005">
		<path>./Capcom vs. SNK 2 EO (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Capcom vs. SNK 2 EO : Millionaire Fighting 2001</name>
		<desc>Capcom VS SNK 2 is composed almost entirely of classic Street Fighter and SNK fighting techniques, which means lots of charge moves, half and quarter circles, and super moves. What's new to the game are the different "grooves," or fighting styles. Although the "Capcom" and "SNK" grooves were introduced in a previous game, Capcom VS SNK 2 takes this concept a step further by introducing six different grooves: C, A, P, S, N, and K. Depending on which groove you choose, the type and number of fighting techniques you have available changes, with half of the grooves leaning towards traditional Capcom fighting and the other half leaning towards SNK-styled battle. The difference between the two fighting styles is mainly the availability of certain non-lethal moves such as air blocks, dodging, and rolling, with each groove having its own balanced mixture of the said moves.</desc>
		<image>./images/Capcom vs. SNK 2 EO (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Capcom vs. SNK 2 EO (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Capcom vs. SNK 2 EO (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Capcom vs. SNK 2 EO (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5182">
		<path>./Carmen Sandiego - The Secret of the Stolen Drums (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Carmen Sandiego: The Secret of the Stolen Drums</name>
		<desc>The last descendant of an African King reveals an ancient secret with his dying words: Deep in the jungles of Rwanda lies a hidden temple containing a great diamond which possesses the knowledge of all nations. The map to the temple has been etched onto the skins of eight drums scattered throughout the world. All eight drums must be re-united to open the temple. But beware, the drums are protected by mysterious powers, and legend has it that elemental spirits guard the treasure. Players travel through nine exotic locations, learning their history and geography, and solving challenging puzzles on their way.</desc>
		<image>./images/Carmen Sandiego - The Secret of the Stolen Drums (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Carmen Sandiego - The Secret of the Stolen Drums (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Carmen Sandiego - The Secret of the Stolen Drums (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Carmen Sandiego - The Secret of the Stolen Drums (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Artificial Mind &amp; Movement</developer>
		<publisher>Bam Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Carmen Sandiego</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="5286">
		<path>./Casper - Spirit Dimensions (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Casper : Spirit Dimensions</name>
		<desc>Spiral into phantom dimensions where you will fiercely battle for the fate of the spirit world! Portals will transport you to mysterious realms that are populated by ghosts of the past, present and future; all possessed by the evil Kibosh. Use your powers of flight and fright to become the quickest, smartest and most powerful ghost in the Spirit Dimension!</desc>
		<image>./images/Casper - Spirit Dimensions (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Casper - Spirit Dimensions (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Casper - Spirit Dimensions (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Casper - Spirit Dimensions (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<developer>Lucky Chicken</developer>
		<publisher>TDK</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162149" />
	</game>
	<game id="4958">
		<path>./Catwoman (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Catwoman</name>
		<desc>Another licensed title by EA, based on the movie with the same name, starring Halle Berry. The game follows the film's plot and its models and graphics are based upon the respective characters and locations as seen in the movie. Halle Berry also lends her voice to the character, aside from her likeness.

Catwoman has an impressive array of powers at her disposal with which to overcome obstacles and fight her enemies. The gameplay is split between overcoming obstacles using Catwoman's agility and whip, and defeating (but not killing) enemies using her abilities and the aforementioned whip, again.</desc>
		<image>./images/Catwoman (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Catwoman (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Catwoman (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Catwoman (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Catwoman (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162152" />
	</game>
	<game id="5236">
		<path>./Chaos Field (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Chaos Field</name>
		<desc>Chaos Field is a top-down space shooter similar in concept to the Gradius series, or Ikaruga. You control one of three ships, each with their own pilot and unique weapon systems. 

The game takes place over 5 phases, in each phase you face a number of boss battles. Unlike other games if this genre, almost the entire game is composed of boss battles, each boss requiring a different strategy to defeat. 

The game also uses a unique in-game difficulty adjuster. Called "fields", you can play in either Order or Chaos. Compared to Order, the Chaos Field offers you increased fire power and abilities, but also does the same for your enemies. Order Field is more relaxed on both sides. If you can play in the Chaos Field, you stand to gain substantially more points.</desc>
		<image>./images/Chaos Field (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Chaos Field (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Chaos Field (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chaos Field (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>O3 Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Milestone</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162212" />
	</game>
	<game id="5039">
		<path>./Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Charlie and the Chocolate Factory</name>
		<desc>Developed by High Voltage Software and licensed by Warner Bros., Charlie and the Chocolate Factory puts players right into the world of the film. You'll find the factory rampaged by the other children, who are running amok with greed and impishness. Use your special candy powers and the assistance of the Oompa-Loompas to restore order to Willy Wonka's sugary establishment. Beyond this, Charlie will have to use a variety of candy to overcome obstacles and potential enemies. Everlasting Gobstoppers, for instance, are basically rocks that Charlie can throw around. The game features celebrity voice talent and the likeness of Johnny Depp as Wonka.</desc>
		<image>./images/Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20050722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Voltage</developer>
		<publisher>Global Star Software</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162221" />
	</game>
	<game id="5264">
		<path>./Charlie's Angels (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Charlie's Angels</name>
		<desc>The whole world is startled at the unbelievable series of events that are currently taking place. Somehow, the world's most famous monuments are being stolen - one after the other. Their size and weight are of no signifance for these cunning thieves and their devious mastermind. Police and special task forces from every country are baffled. Tourism is down, and governments are desperate as the list of missing monuments keeps growing - the Statue of Liberty, the Eiffel Tower, the Great Wall of China, you name it...all have vanished without a trace. However, the call has been made, and Charlie has been briefed.</desc>
		<image>./images/Charlie's Angels (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Charlie's Angels (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Charlie's Angels (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Charlie's Angels (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20030718T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162228" />
	</game>
	<game id="4856">
		<path>./Chibi-Robo! Plug into Adventure! (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Chibi-Robo!</name>
		<desc>Gamers take control of the Chibi Robo, a pint-sized machine designed specifically to take care of a family's house. The robot needs to keep the house "happy." To do that, Chibi must walk around the home and clean it up, interact with other machines and people, and even -- according to the storyline - stop a group of bumbling thieves from making off with precious valuables. An electricity counter located in the bottom-right corner of the screen constantly counts down. When Chibi is getting low, players will want to recharge. The game features a day and night system, where days last about 10 minutes and nights the same. The environments slightly change depending on the time of day. For instance, a character not available in the day might be sleeping on the couch at night, and robots normally roaming the level in the afternoon might be gone in the evening.</desc>
		<image>./images/Chibi-Robo! Plug into Adventure! (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Chibi-Robo! Plug into Adventure! (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Chibi-Robo! Plug into Adventure! (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chibi-Robo! Plug into Adventure! (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20060208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Skip</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162312" />
	</game>
	<game id="5303">
		<path>./City Racer (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Downtown Run</name>
		<desc>Ignite the engine and power up your Dodge Viper. Strap into real cars like the Dodge Viper as you blaze your way through the competition on the most famous city streets in the world. It?s going to take more than mere speed to beat the competition, its going to take skill. Powerslide, Drift, and sideswipe the competition as you drive with style on your way to the winner's circle.</desc>
		<image>./images/City Racer (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/City Racer (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/City Racer (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/City Racer (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20030429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162312" />
	</game>
	<game id="5202">
		<path>./Codename - Kids Next Door - Operation - V.I.D.E.O.G.A.M.E. (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Codename: Kids Next Door Operation: V.I.D.E.O.G.A.M.E.</name>
		<desc>Play as your favorite Kids Next Door operative on 14 diverse levels, each with a different style, in this action-packed game. Utilize each Kids Next Door member's unique strengths and special skills as you dive, dodge, jump and attack to complete your mission. Engage in intense battles with Stickybeard, Knightbrace, The Toiletnator and other notorious and nasty villains from the show. And when Father masterminds an Arctic Prison break to free the villains, gather "Powuh Ups," collect and build your weapons, and get ready for an epic showdown on the Moon Base.</desc>
		<image>./images/Codename - Kids Next Door - Operation - V.I.D.E.O.G.A.M.E. (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Codename - Kids Next Door - Operation - V.I.D.E.O.G.A.M.E. (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Codename - Kids Next Door - Operation - V.I.D.E.O.G.A.M.E. (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Codename - Kids Next Door - Operation - V.I.D.E.O.G.A.M.E. (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>2K Games</developer>
		<publisher>High Voltage</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162322" />
	</game>
	<game id="4925">
		<path>./Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.00)(USA).iso</path>
		<name>Conflict : Desert Storm</name>
		<desc>Conflict: Desert Storm lets you take charge of the best known and most feared special operations forces in the world: the elite British SAS or the US Delta Force squads. You're the best trained, best equipped and best organised Special Forces in the world. The area that has been assigned to you is yours for the taking. Seek, locate and destroy enemy targets and personnel. Create havoc and confusion throughout the enemy's lines of communication and supply. What lies before you is an opportunity in a soldier's lifetime. Take your equipment, take your training and use it well. Features included squad-based combat (both alone or co-operatively with friends), 15 missions, and scripted events.</desc>
		<image>./images/Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.00)(USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.00)(USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.00)(USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.00)(USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pivotal Games</developer>
		<publisher>SCi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162436" />
	</game>
	<game id="4925">
		<path>./Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.01)(USA).iso</path>
		<name>Conflict : Desert Storm</name>
		<desc>Conflict: Desert Storm lets you take charge of the best known and most feared special operations forces in the world: the elite British SAS or the US Delta Force squads. You're the best trained, best equipped and best organised Special Forces in the world. The area that has been assigned to you is yours for the taking. Seek, locate and destroy enemy targets and personnel. Create havoc and confusion throughout the enemy's lines of communication and supply. What lies before you is an opportunity in a soldier's lifetime. Take your equipment, take your training and use it well. Features included squad-based combat (both alone or co-operatively with friends), 15 missions, and scripted events.</desc>
		<image>./images/Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.01)(USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.01)(USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.01)(USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Conflict - Desert Storm (v1.01)(USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pivotal Games</developer>
		<publisher>SCi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162436" />
	</game>
	<game id="4848">
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot - The Wrath of Cortex (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot: The Wrath of Cortex</name>
		<desc>The fifth Crash adventure features engaging gameplay, quirky characters and exotic locales. Still smarting from his last defeat, Dr. Neo Cortex has developed a new diabolical plan to steal ancient crystals and unleash destructive gods on Crash and the planet Earth. With Crash and his sister Coco, it's now up to you to find and return all the crystals across dangerous levels, including a volcanic island, a Japanese village, and the jungles of Africa. You'll find many ways to move around, whether you maneuver a Jeep, fly a hang glider, or pilot a Crash-Mech. But don't marvel too long at the new inventions, because you might find yourself in a heap of destruction.</desc>
		<image>./images/Crash Bandicoot - The Wrath of Cortex (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Crash Bandicoot - The Wrath of Cortex (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Crash Bandicoot - The Wrath of Cortex (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crash Bandicoot - The Wrath of Cortex (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Crash Bandicoot - The Wrath of Cortex (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020917T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Crash Bandicoot</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162436" />
	</game>
	<game id="4950">
		<path>./Crash Nitro Kart (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Crash Nitro Kart</name>
		<desc>Crash Bandicoot returns to the karting scene with a host of other characters from the adventure series, and this time they have both Neo Cortex and Emperor Velo to worry about. Velo has taken the crew to a remote planet, forced to race for their lives against Neo Cortex and his many evil doers.

Choose from various game modes, from the straight into the action Arcade mode to Adventure mode, following Crash and the gang in the story to save Earth. Race against four friends in multiplayer battle modes, plus connect to the Gamecube for extra options and upload your high scores to the internet ranking system.</desc>
		<image>./images/Crash Nitro Kart (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Crash Nitro Kart (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Crash Nitro Kart (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crash Nitro Kart (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Crash Nitro Kart (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20030708T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Universal</developer>
		<publisher>Vicarious Vision</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Crash Bandicoot</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221101T162820</lastplayed>
		<gametime>217</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162436" />
	</game>
	<game id="4869">
		<path>./Crash Tag Team Racing (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Crash : Tag Team Racing</name>
		<desc>For the first time ever in a racing game, players will be able to fuse two cars together on the fly to form a super vehicle with the all-new "clashing" technology. In Crash Tag Team Racing, players can combine their car with an opponent's mid-race to make a super-car equipped with a powerful turret gun. When clashed, players can either get behind the wheel and drive or fire an onboard weapon. Each character has his or her own uniquely deadly 360? rotating turret. Players can continue the action out of the car where they can explore the entire world on foot and collect upgrades for their cars and unlock bonus tracks.</desc>
		<image>./images/Crash Tag Team Racing (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Crash Tag Team Racing (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Crash Tag Team Racing (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crash Tag Team Racing (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Crash Tag Team Racing (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Crash Bandicoot</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221101T163345</lastplayed>
		<gametime>485</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="4943">
		<path>./Crazy Taxi (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi</name>
		<desc>Crazy Taxi is an arcade-like racer where the player takes the role of a taxi driver who weaves his way through crowded streets, across sidewalks and even under water, in a wild and frantic race to deliver passengers on time. The courses are largely set inside cities crowded with general traffic and pedestrians (which can't be run over, they dive away). The main goal is to bring as many customers as possible to their destination in time. Available customers are marked through circles and the colour represents the distance and the fare they offer. Green means long rides with plenty of money, and red ones are very short. 

In the main Arcade mode there is a timer that quickly runs down. It can be replenished by picking up customers. While driving reckless maneuvers are encouraged. Players can disregard all traffic rules and customers give extra tips for speedy and dangerous driving, but these can only be cashed when the customer arrives at his destination in time. By the same token the reward at the end of a ride is based on the amount of time left, as each customer also has a personal timer. The city is filled with slopes and jumps, and the game uses a very loose driving model. No damage can be done to the car, so driving as fast as possible is encouraged. While driving players can toy with the gears to perform two special tricks: a crazy drift and a crazy boost to speed up more quickly.

Next to the Arcade mode there is an Original mode, and Crazy Box where specific goals need to be met on closed down courses. In the regular modes it is possible to disregard the usual timer and play for a fixed amount of minutes. At the end of the race the player is rewarded with a license, either D, C, B or A, with S for an outstanding performance. Next to the interactive courses from the arcade version there is a new course for home consoles. There are four cabs and drivers to choose from. The cars have different statistics and the drivers different attitudes while racing. The game has a soundtrack featuring The Offspring and Bad Religion (not for the Xbox 360 version).</desc>
		<image>./images/Crazy Taxi (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Crazy Taxi (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Crazy Taxi (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crazy Taxi (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Crazy Taxi (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20011118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Crazy Taxi</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5211">
		<path>./Cubivore (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Cubivore</name>
		<desc>Cubivore is a "Call of the Wild" brought to an interactive media. Gento Matsumotos serene and surreal portrait of wilderness lost then civilization reverting (or progressing) to wilderness. The music though not long is of high quality and presents eerie and beautiful pieces. 
Of course the most obvious thing about Cubivore would be the graphics. 99% of all scenery and creatures in the game are made of cubes, rectangles, or squares. Even water ripples away from a falling step in squares. Blood pools in squares upon the ground and even the moon and sun appear as cubes in the sky. 

As you move through the game you will eat prey (Or sometimes outfight a predator) To gain new forms and power. The more forms you gain the more wilderness goes back to the land (This wilderness has recently been stolen by a rather nasty Killer cubivore). Naturally it is your goal to dethrone this killer of the wild and set your self up as king of the beast, thus filling the land once again with wilderness.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cubivore (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Cubivore (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Cubivore (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cubivore (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5361">
		<path>./Cubix Robots for Everyone - Showdown (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Cubix: Robots for Everyone: Showdown</name>
		<desc>All over Bubble Town, robots of all shapes and kinds are going out of control! Solex has infected them, causing them to go haywire and destroy the environment. Connor, Abby, and the rest of the Cubix gang must track down these rogue robots before the evil Dr. K and his gigantic robot Kolossal do.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cubix Robots for Everyone - Showdown (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Cubix Robots for Everyone - Showdown (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Cubix Robots for Everyone - Showdown (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cubix Robots for Everyone - Showdown (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20030602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blitz Games</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / 3D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5341">
		<path>./Curious George (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Georges Le Petit Curieux</name>
		<desc>Curious George is a colorful action adventure that is based on the Curious George animated movie. In the game you can help George explore a variety of areas, collect items such as bananas, and unlock minigames. The game features a variety of different objectives set in areas from the movie. You can also unlock scenes from the movie, extra costumes, and production art.</desc>
		<image>./images/Curious George (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Curious George (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Curious George (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Curious George (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20060201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5118">
		<path>./Custom Robo (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Custom Robo</name>
		<desc>This is the fourth installment in the Custom Robo series, but the first one to be released outside of Japan. On an unknown planet in the future, custom robos are used for criminal purposes. Those who can manipulate the robots through brain waves are called "Commanders". When you and your comrades learn of a strong, autonomous maneuvering robot, you decide to investigate the matter.

The game mixes action (fighting), simulation (assembling) and RPG elements (do some detective work to unravel the mystery) in a single game. You can construct your own robot with over 200 parts, including over 50 guns, 30 bombs, 30 pods and 15 legs. In a typical arena match, you have to fight real-time battles and victory means you can acquire new parts and continue with the storyline. As there are different kinds of battles (two-on-two, tag team, four-player battle royale), you have to use different strategies and make use of the obstacles in the arena.</desc>
		<image>./images/Custom Robo (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Custom Robo (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Custom Robo (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Custom Robo (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20040304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5104">
		<path>./Dakar 2 - The World's Ultimate Rally (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Dakar 2</name>
		<desc>The world?s most insane off-road rally race returns to the consoles bigger and badder than ever before with Dakar 2: Special Stages Racing. Choose from a vast assortment of fully licensed trucks, cars and motorcycles in which you?ll compete against the elements that mother-nature has placed in your path to victory. This is a no holds barred quest for world rally supremacy!</desc>
		<image>./images/Dakar 2 - The World's Ultimate Rally (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dakar 2 - The World's Ultimate Rally (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dakar 2 - The World's Ultimate Rally (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dakar 2 - The World's Ultimate Rally (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Dakar 2 - The World's Ultimate Rally (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221101T162436</lastplayed>
		<gametime>378</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="4999">
		<path>./Dance Dance Revolution - Mario Mix (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Dance Dance Revolution - Mario Mix</name>
		<desc>Boogie down with Mario, DDR-style. Players shake their things to more than 25 dance-flavored songs, from classic Nintendo themes to familiar favorites. With five difficulty levels, dancers of all abilities will be able to get into the groove. Have fun getting in shape! The special "Workout" feature tracks the calories burned while playing. Someone has stolen the Music Keys and released the music they held. Without the Music Keys, the unstable power of the music is wreaking havoc on the land. Mario must recover them before the chaos destroys the entire Mushroom Kingdom! The path to the keys is simple: Left, Right, Up, Down, Right, Down... In Dance Dance Revolution: Mario Mix, players clear levels by performing the correct steps. Once they clear all the levels in a particular world, they'll collect a Music Key. Collect all the Music Keys to win.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dance Dance Revolution - Mario Mix (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dance Dance Revolution - Mario Mix (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dance Dance Revolution - Mario Mix (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dance Dance Revolution - Mario Mix (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Dance Dance Revolution - Mario Mix (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<family>Dance Dance Revolution</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5119">
		<path>./Dark Summit (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Dark Summit</name>
		<desc>The military has mysteriously closed the summit of Mt. Garrick, and Chief O'Leary is trying desperately to drive snowboarders off the mountain.

Dark Summit is a twist on the snowboarding genre.  Instead of trying to pull off insane tricks, you'll be completing various missions, such as "Find the Bomb" and "Destroy the Cannon".  Pulling off tricks earns you points to buy new equipment.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dark Summit (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dark Summit (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dark Summit (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dark Summit (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Dark Summit (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5052">
		<path>./Darkened Skye (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Darkened Skye</name>
		<desc>The Skittles brand candies "Taste the Rainbow" ad campaign is the inspiration behind this action adventure game in which the tasty, brightly-colored orbs are transformed into magical spheres with tremendous powers.

You play Skye of Lynlora, a "sexy Warrior-Hero-Adventurer-Goddess with a smart mouth" whose mundane life as a Dwentil shepherdess is changed forever when she comes upon one of the magical Skittles while following a stray dwentil.  It is up to Skye to reassemble the Great Rainbow which has been squelched by the evil Lord Necroth.  Armed with her sense of humor and trusty staff, harness the power of the Skittles to defeat Necroth’s minions, solve ancient mysteries and ultimately save the world.

As the witty, and often sarcastic, Skye, you’ll be running, jumping and battling your way across graphically beautiful, medieval lands depicted in 3-dimensional detail.  The story and plot unfold gradually as you meet numerous, unique non-player characters and solve many puzzles along the way.</desc>
		<image>./images/Darkened Skye (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Darkened Skye (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Darkened Skye (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Darkened Skye (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Simon &amp; Schuster Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>TDK</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5045">
		<path>./Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX 2</name>
		<desc>Dave Mirra returns along with 14 pro riders including Ryan Nyquist, Mike Laird and Collin Mackay. 8 levels are on offer, with a total of 1,500 tricks to master. You can create your own BMX park thanks to the Park Editor mode. And while you attempt to master the tricks, you can listen to the soundtrack featuring Ozzy Osbourne, The Cult, Methods of Mayhem, Godsmack and Rage Against the Machine (all except Game Boy Advance version).</desc>
		<image>./images/Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX 2 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX 2 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX 2 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX 2 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX 2 (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20011118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Z-Axis</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Cycling</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5242">
		<path>./Army Men - Sarge's War (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Army Men: Sarge's War</name>
		<desc>Global Star Software, who picked up the license to the popular ARMY MEN series from 3DO, brings fans of the little plastic soldiers ARMY MEN: Sarge's War for the Gamecube. Following the character of Sarge, a war-scarred veteran, gamers must stop a renegade sect of the Tan Army before they can derail the signing of a peace treaty between the Green and Tan armies. A third-person perspective shooter game, Sarge's War is an easy game to pick up but a difficult one to master. The levels get progressively harder, with Sarge facing waves of enemies at a time. Fortunately, the game has a target lock feature, so Sarge can pick off his enemies one at a time. Some levels require Sarge to destroy walls, fences, or enemy artillery, and in other levels, he takes command of turret gun to wreak some major damage. In addition to the single-player campaign, ARMY MEN: Sarge's War contains several multiplayer modes, including death match, capture the flag, and team advance. Fans of the ARMY MEN series will be glad to see it continued with ARMY MEN: Sarge's War. Players who have fond memories of waging war with the little plastic army men or enjoy third-person shooters will also find Sarge's War a fun, entertaining game to pick up.</desc>
		<image>./images/Army Men - Sarge's War (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Army Men - Sarge's War (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Army Men - Sarge's War (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Army Men - Sarge's War (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20040821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3DO</developer>
		<publisher>Global Star Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<family>Army Men</family>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5097">
		<path>./ATV - Quad Power Racing 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>ATV Quad Power Racing 2</name>
		<desc>ATV: Quad Power Racing 2 is all about big tricks, big boots to the face and big finishes. It's arcade ATV racing. ATV Quad Power Racing 2 combines 10 of the top pro riders in the world and 40+ real-life sponsors with fast, edge of your seat, arcade gameplay.Game features include 10 of the top professional riders from all over the world including Dana Creech, Kory Ellis, Tim Farr and others plus 10 stylized characters; 15 massive tracks in 5 different globe-spanning environments plus two freestyle arenas; kick attacks that teach your competitors not to even think about passing you; over-the-top control system and physics model give you the power pull huge air and ridiculous power slides; 20+ freestyle tricks; and real-life sponsors.</desc>
		<image>./images/ATV - Quad Power Racing 2 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/ATV - Quad Power Racing 2 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/ATV - Quad Power Racing 2 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/ATV - Quad Power Racing 2 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5247">
		<path>./Auto Modellista (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Auto Modellista</name>
		<desc>Faithful port of Capcom's cel-shaded PlayStation 2 racer, sans online support. The game features nine tracks in all, eight normal and one hidden, and 69 real-world, licensed vehicles -- presented anime-style thanks to the toon-shading technique. Players can choose from arcade mode, a standard enter and race scenario, garage life, which is the career mode of the game, and VJ and Theater, an arena enabling players to watch, edit and direct race replays of their choice. Cars can be fully customized down to the tires, brakes, suspension, turbine kits, mufflers, transmissions and more with hundreds of parts to choose from. Supports two-player split-screen racing.</desc>
		<image>./images/Auto Modellista (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Auto Modellista (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Auto Modellista (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Auto Modellista (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5382">
		<path>./Backyard Baseball (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Backyard Baseball</name>
		<desc>Major League Baseball pros join the Backyard Kids. Now, for the first time on the Sony PlayStation 2 computer entertainment system, young baseball fans can pick Alex Rodriguez, Alfonso Soriano and 14 other stars, all playing as kids. Choose lineups, team logos, and awesome fields and control every pitch. With outrageous power-ups and surprises, kids can smash homeruns, throw clutch strikeouts and have a one-of-a-kind Backyard Sports experience. Features include all 30 MLB team logos, customizable players, quick, single games and Season Play mode, Home Run Derby mini-game, full stats and standings in Season Play, multiple camera views and instant replay, unlockable fields and special players, tutorial mode, baseball darts and other mini-games.</desc>
		<image>./images/Backyard Baseball (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Backyard Baseball (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Backyard Baseball (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Backyard Baseball (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030409T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Humongous</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>Backyard Sports</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5375">
		<path>./Backyard Football (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Backyard Football</name>
		<desc>Combines Authentic NFL plays and strategies with the wild and wacky antics of the Backyard gang. Players have control of the style, location, pace, and strategy of the game. And, with multiple levels, the game is easy enough for rookie players yet mega challenging for more seasoned veterans.</desc>
		<image>./images/Backyard Football (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Backyard Football (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Backyard Football (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Backyard Football (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20071016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FarSight Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Football</genre>
		<family>Backyard Sports</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162820" />
	</game>
	<game id="5368">
		<path>./Backyard Sports - Baseball 2007 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Backyard Sports Baseball 2007</name>
		<desc>Backyard Baseball 2007 is the fifth iteration of the best selling youth baseball video game of all time and the only kid's game to hold the coveted Major League Baseball (MLB) and Major League Baseball Players Association (MLBPA) licenses. Backyard Baseball 2007 features a roster full of top MLB pros as kids and includes all 30 MLB teams, uniforms, and logos. In addition, the game's kid-friendly, non-violent format, and high level of diversity makes it especially popular with parents.</desc>
		<image>./images/Backyard Sports - Baseball 2007 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Backyard Sports - Baseball 2007 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Backyard Sports - Baseball 2007 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Backyard Sports - Baseball 2007 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20100403T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Humongous</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>Backyard Sports</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162821" />
	</game>
	<game id="5153">
		<path>./Bad Boys - Miami Takedown (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bad Boys: Miami Takedown</name>
		<desc>Mike Lowrey and Marcus Burnett of the Tactical Narcotics Team are back and oh so bad. Featuring all the fast pace and all-out action of the movie, it's your job to ensure that these TNT cops are not DOA! Somewhere on the streets of Miami, something is going down which must be stopped. You can play as either Mike or Marcus in first or third-person viewpoints, making your way through 15 stages of fast paced, all-action gameplay, with gameplay featuring multiple mission objectives. In addition to a variety of weapons, destructible environments, and changing playstyles, the game features a Bad Boy rating system, where you are rewarded for your actions and achievements. Play the perfect cop or be a Bad Boy. What are YOU gonna do?</desc>
		<image>./images/Bad Boys - Miami Takedown (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bad Boys - Miami Takedown (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bad Boys - Miami Takedown (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bad Boys - Miami Takedown (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.1</rating>
		<releasedate>20041105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blitz Games</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162944" />
	</game>
	<game id="4833">
		<path>./Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Baldur's Gate : Dark Alliance</name>
		<desc>Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance features a distinctive blend of action and adventure set in the most popular Dungeons &amp; Dragons campaign setting: The Forgotten Realms franchise owned by Wizards of the Coast Inc. Played from a third person perspective, Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance immerses players in the port town of Baldur's Gate. Faithful adaptation of the third edition rules set for the Dungeons &amp; Dragons roleplaying game and customizable player and character development allow for an engrossing gameplay experience for up to two players at once. Dramatic spell effects and powerful abilities enhance this action-packed game, assisting the player in combat against an abundance of terrifying monsters found throughout the adventure.</desc>
		<image>./images/Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20021119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Snowblind</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Baldur's Gate</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162944" />
	</game>
	<game id="4758">
		<path>./Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 1)(USA).iso</path>
		<name>Baten Kaitos: Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean</name>
		<desc>An original roleplaying game for Nintendo GameCube from the team behind Xenosaga. The game makes heavy use of cards for everything from fighting battles to purchasing items. Cards are actually a central part of the story as well, as they are holders for "Magnus" which is short for "Magna Essence." Magnus is the true nature of all things throughout the world, including swords, magic spells and even apples that are gathered in the town in which your adventures start out. A real item can be turned into Magnus form and stored in a blank card. It can then be taken out from the card and will turn back into real form. Features detailed CG cutscenes to tell the story and turn-based battle sequences.</desc>
		<image>./images/Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 1)(USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 1)(USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 1)(USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 1)(USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Software (JP)</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162944" />
	</game>
	<game id="4758">
		<path>./Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 2)(USA).iso</path>
		<name>Baten Kaitos: Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean</name>
		<desc>An original roleplaying game for Nintendo GameCube from the team behind Xenosaga. The game makes heavy use of cards for everything from fighting battles to purchasing items. Cards are actually a central part of the story as well, as they are holders for "Magnus" which is short for "Magna Essence." Magnus is the true nature of all things throughout the world, including swords, magic spells and even apples that are gathered in the town in which your adventures start out. A real item can be turned into Magnus form and stored in a blank card. It can then be taken out from the card and will turn back into real form. Features detailed CG cutscenes to tell the story and turn-based battle sequences.</desc>
		<image>./images/Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 2)(USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 2)(USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 2)(USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Baten Kaitos - Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean (Disc 2)(USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Software (JP)</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162944" />
	</game>
	<game id="4774">
		<path>./Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 1)(USA).iso</path>
		<name>Baten Kaitos Origins</name>
		<desc>Baten Kaitos Origins is a prequel to Baten Kaitos: Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean. Long ago, the evil god Malpercio attempted to destroy the other gods; a large battle of the gods ensued, and following this the people of the world were forced to flee to various islands floating in the sky. 1000 years after the war the people live peacefully in the sky for the most part; but Emperor Olgen, the emperor of one of these islands, has begun a plot to gain control of all the islands.

The main character of the story is Sagi, a "Spirit-born" individual who has been given a secret mission to assassinate Emperor Olgen. In similar fashion to Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean, you don't actually control Sagi in the game but rather his guardian spirit. Throughout the game you can give Sagi advice, and as you progress the story will unfold revealing the plot that may threaten all of the islands...

Gameplay is similar to Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean and features a card based battle system. Many items in the world have a "magna essence"; these items can be captured in a card for use later. Some items are useful for attacking and defending, others can help replenish your health, and some can be used to solve puzzles. When a battle begins your deck of cards will be randomly dealt to you; battles are turn based, on each turn you can select cards from those visible to use. Different cards also feature different attributes, and various combos are possible. When a battle is won, your characters will earn experience points, gold, and will also recover all hit points.

The battles in the game aren't random; as you explore the worlds, enemies will be visible on screen in some areas and contact with them begins the battle. In addition to the main story line, numerous sub-quests will also become available by talking with various characters; completing a sub-quest will typically earn a useful item for you as well as provide an opportunity for your characters to level up. You will encounter many types of enemies on both the main quest and subquests; since different enemies may require different strategies, you have the ability to customize the deck of cards you will use in battle. As you gain experience, you will also gain the ability to create multiple decks.</desc>
		<image>./images/Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 1)(USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 1)(USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 1)(USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 1)(USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>tri-Crescendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162944" />
	</game>
	<game id="4774">
		<path>./Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 2)(USA).iso</path>
		<name>Baten Kaitos Origins</name>
		<desc>Baten Kaitos Origins is a prequel to Baten Kaitos: Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean. Long ago, the evil god Malpercio attempted to destroy the other gods; a large battle of the gods ensued, and following this the people of the world were forced to flee to various islands floating in the sky. 1000 years after the war the people live peacefully in the sky for the most part; but Emperor Olgen, the emperor of one of these islands, has begun a plot to gain control of all the islands.

The main character of the story is Sagi, a "Spirit-born" individual who has been given a secret mission to assassinate Emperor Olgen. In similar fashion to Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean, you don't actually control Sagi in the game but rather his guardian spirit. Throughout the game you can give Sagi advice, and as you progress the story will unfold revealing the plot that may threaten all of the islands...

Gameplay is similar to Eternal Wings and the Lost Ocean and features a card based battle system. Many items in the world have a "magna essence"; these items can be captured in a card for use later. Some items are useful for attacking and defending, others can help replenish your health, and some can be used to solve puzzles. When a battle begins your deck of cards will be randomly dealt to you; battles are turn based, on each turn you can select cards from those visible to use. Different cards also feature different attributes, and various combos are possible. When a battle is won, your characters will earn experience points, gold, and will also recover all hit points.

The battles in the game aren't random; as you explore the worlds, enemies will be visible on screen in some areas and contact with them begins the battle. In addition to the main story line, numerous sub-quests will also become available by talking with various characters; completing a sub-quest will typically earn a useful item for you as well as provide an opportunity for your characters to level up. You will encounter many types of enemies on both the main quest and subquests; since different enemies may require different strategies, you have the ability to customize the deck of cards you will use in battle. As you gain experience, you will also gain the ability to create multiple decks.</desc>
		<image>./images/Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 2)(USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 2)(USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 2)(USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Baten Kaitos Origins (Disc 2)(USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>tri-Crescendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162944" />
	</game>
	<game id="4763">
		<path>./Def Jam - Fight for NY (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Def Jam: Fight For NY</name>
		<desc>The ultimate hip-hop fueled fighting game, Def Jam Fight For NY challenges players to step into the shoes of a ruthless street fighter battling for control of New York's hip-hop underground. The game features an all-new fighting engine including weapons, interactive environments, and five unique fighting styles that can be combined to form dozens of customized hybrid styles for the ultimate edge on the streets. Def Jam Fight For NY features more than 40 of the most well-known artists and personalities in hip-hop today, including Busta Rhymes, Carmen Electra, Lil' Kim, Ludacris, Method Man, Redman, Sean Paul, Slick Rick, Snoop Dogg, and many more. Experience 22 interactive venues with destructible environmental objects and rowdy spectators who like to get involved.</desc>
		<image>./images/Def Jam - Fight for NY (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Def Jam - Fight for NY (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Def Jam - Fight for NY (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Def Jam - Fight for NY (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20040928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162944" />
	</game>
	<game id="4986">
		<path>./Def Jam - Vendetta (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Def Jam Vendetta</name>
		<desc>The unlikely combination of Def Jam recording artists and underground wrestling is the subject of this Electronic Arts release, which features the 3D likenesses of such musicians as Ludacris, Redman, DMX, Scarface, Ghostface Killa, Method Man, and more as playable characters. Developed by AKI Corporation, whose previous experience in the genre includes titles WWF No Mercy and WCW/NWO Revenge, Def Jam Vendetta offers an estimated 1,500 animations for each of the 45 included characters. A total of ten different venues are available, and one of the featured modes offers a storyline complete with soap opera-style drama to go along with the suplexes and body slams. Up to four players can compete in Single, Tag-Team, Handicap, or Battle Royale matches.

EA combines the game-making prowess of Aki and the boisterous characters from hip-hop's Def Jam Records. The result is Def Jam Vendetta, a curious concoction that just might have the goods to attract hardcore and mainstream gamers alike. The game features 12 Def Jam artists including Redman, Method Man, Ludacris, DMX, N.O.R.E., and Scarface. As you make your way through the game, you'll be able to unlock all 45 characters plus aditional venues, girls, and concept art.</desc>
		<image>./images/Def Jam - Vendetta (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Def Jam - Vendetta (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Def Jam - Vendetta (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Def Jam - Vendetta (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T162956" />
	</game>
	<game id="5332">
		<path>./Defender (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Defender : For All Mankind</name>
		<desc>An intense combat-action flying experience, Defender offers players the ultimate in next-generation action and strategy. Players defend and protect the human race from an alien invasion as they assume the controls of next-generation combat-ready Defender ships. Battling an onslaught of vicious aliens, players strategically pilot their ship through more than 14 treacherous missions spanning the solar system, executing dynamic tactical maneuvers such as barrel rolls, 360-degree loops and spinning reversals in order to evade the enemy.</desc>
		<image>./images/Defender (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Defender (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Defender (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Defender (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20020101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>7 Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163013" />
	</game>
	<game id="4897">
		<path>./Die Hard - Vendetta (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Die Hard : Vendetta</name>
		<desc>In Die Hard: Vendetta, tactics and stealth are just as important as having a big gun and being a quick shot. The story picks up five years after the movie Die Hard With a Vengeance, and you play as LA cop John McClane. Your daughter, now a full-grown woman on the police force, finds herself in danger, and it's up to you to save her. In your investigation, you'll meet old friends, uncover helpful clues, and solve objectives--all while using stealth or an arsenal of weaponry to move past enemies.</desc>
		<image>./images/Die Hard - Vendetta (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Die Hard - Vendetta (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Die Hard - Vendetta (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Fox Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>NDA Productions</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Die Hard</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163018" />
	</game>
	<game id="4963">
		<path>./Digimon Rumble Arena 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Digimon : Rumble Arena 2</name>
		<desc>The Japanese release of Digimon Rumble Arena 2.

                Digimon Battle Chronicle lets you play as and against your favorite Digimon characters. The game features all the popular Digimon from all four seasons of the TV show, plus secret Digimon. Each Digimon has a signature move that can earn Digipoints and, with enough Digipoints, you can Digivolve and destroy your opponents. In locations ranging from icy glaciers to fields of fire, you can conquer the Digimon in single-player mode or compete against three of your friends in multiplayer brawls.</desc>
		<image>./images/Digimon Rumble Arena 2 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Digimon Rumble Arena 2 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Digimon Rumble Arena 2 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Digimon Rumble Arena 2 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Digimon</family>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221101T161710</lastplayed>
		<gametime>40</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="4919">
		<path>./Digimon World 4 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Digimon World 4</name>
		<desc>Digimon World 4, known as Digimon World X in Japan, is the second Digimon video game on GameCube, PlayStation 2, and Xbox game consoles, simultaneously. Instead of being a standard role-playing game like the previous Digimon games, Digimon World 4 has hack and slash gameplay and supports up to four players. The game is loosely based on the Digital Monster X-Evolution film (in fact, the game's opening uses footage from the film itself). The Nintendo GameCube version was not released in the PAL Region.</desc>
		<image>./images/Digimon World 4 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Digimon World 4 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Digimon World 4 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Digimon World 4 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Digimon</family>
		<players>4+</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="59899">
		<path>./Dinotopia - The Sunstone Odyssey (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Dinotopia - The Sunstone Odyssey</name>
		<desc>Dinotopia: The Sunstone Odyssey is being billed as an action-adventure title offers a unique blend of puzzle, role-playing and exploration elements. The game revolves around Drake Gemini, as he embarks on a personal quest to reunite his family and become a Guardian of Dinotopia. Drake will get to explore the skies and lands in an around the fabled civilization where men and dragons live together (and fight together) with uncanny harmony.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dinotopia - The Sunstone Odyssey (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dinotopia - The Sunstone Odyssey (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dinotopia - The Sunstone Odyssey (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dinotopia - The Sunstone Odyssey (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20030723T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicious Cycle Software</developer>
		<publisher>TDK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="5229">
		<path>./Disney Sports - Basketball (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Disney Sports Basketball</name>
		<desc>Disney Sports Basketball brings exaggerated moves and original locations to life as your favorite Disney characters take to the court. Mickey and his pals, who include Minnie Mouse, Donald Duck, and Goofy, come together for three-on-three-style basketball action with arcade-style gameplay. Choose your team, and then take on five game modes, including Exhibition, Season, and All-Star Game, among others. If you can master the game's intuitive controls, you can take your team all the way to the finals or dominate three of your friends in Multiplayer mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/Disney Sports - Basketball (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Disney Sports - Basketball (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Disney Sports - Basketball (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Disney Sports - Basketball (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="152379">
		<path>./Disney Sports - Football (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Disney Sports Football</name>
		<desc>Disney Sports Football: Get ready for hard-hitting tackles and wild touchdowns as Mickey, Goofy, and other Disney characters take to the gridiron. You'll create a team and compete in four modes: Challenge, Cup, Exhibition, and Practice. You'll have plenty of running and passing plays, offensive and defensive formations, and turbo moves to master, plus magic items to boost your team's performance. In single or multiplayer modes, you'll face a variety of opponents inside fantastic stadiums.</desc>
		<image>./images/Disney Sports - Football (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Disney Sports - Football (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Disney Sports - Football (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Disney Sports - Football (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Football</genre>
		<family>Disney</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="5183">
		<path>./Disney Sports - Skateboarding (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Disney Sports Skateboarding</name>
		<desc>Disney Sports Skateboarding, much as the title implies, is a skateboarding game game based on the Disney license.  It features eight levels set around the world and many favorite Disney characters like Mickey, Minnie, Donald and Goofy.

Like most modern skateboarding games, the structure of Disney Sports Skateboarding owes much to the Tony Hawk series.  Here, the trick system is far simpler as there's no balance meter and most tricks require fewer buttons.  Each level has a set of goals that must be accomplished in order to progress, such as a high score goal, knocking over objects or completing a checkpoint race.</desc>
		<image>./images/Disney Sports - Skateboarding (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Disney Sports - Skateboarding (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Disney Sports - Skateboarding (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Disney Sports - Skateboarding (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="5114">
		<path>./Disney Sports - Soccer (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Disney Sports Soccer</name>
		<desc>Disney Sports Soccer takes the fun of a neighborhood soccer game and adds your favorite Disney characters. In three different game modes, including a multiplayer mode, you can use magic, power-ups, and special moves to defeat your opponents. Up to four players can assume the role of Mickey Mouse, Minnie Mouse, Donald Duck, Goofy, or other Disney favorites, and they can compete in a variety of stadiums, including Eagle Summit. You can also exchange items between your Game Boy Advance and GameCube.</desc>
		<image>./images/Disney Sports - Soccer (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Disney Sports - Soccer (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Disney Sports - Soccer (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Disney Sports - Soccer (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Disney Sports - Soccer (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="5109">
		<path>./Disney's Chicken Little (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Disney's Chicken Little</name>
		<desc>Walt Disney Pictures' Chicken Little catapults players smack dab into the middle of Oakey Oaks, Chicken Little's hometown, where they experience first-hand all of the action, humor, fun and heart-warming adventure as portrayed in the film. Taking on the roles of Chicken Little and his friends Abby Mallard, Runt-of-the-Litter and Fish-out-of-Water, players must try to outwit bully Foxy Loxy and save the town from an alien invasion all the while attempting to reverse Chicken Little's tarnished reputation from that unfortunate "acorn incident." You know, the one where he shouted, "The sky is falling!" causing mass chaos in the town of Oakey Oaks, and earning him the reputation of town fool.</desc>
		<image>./images/Disney's Chicken Little (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Disney's Chicken Little (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Disney's Chicken Little (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Disney's Chicken Little (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Disney's Chicken Little (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20051117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Avalanche Software</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="5135">
		<path>./Army Men - RTS (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Army Men: RTS</name>
		<desc>3DO's famous green plastic soldiers move into the realm of real-time strategy in Army Men RTS. On a mission to defeat a colonel who has defected to the enemy, you command a number of units including infantry and several types of vehicles. Guide your elite corps of plastic troops across toy-proportioned battlefields such as a house's front yard, living room, and attic. Collect plastic and electricity resources to build structures and additional units. Use your radio call unit to bring death from above in the form of paratroopers or the dreaded magnifying glass which melts enemy forces.</desc>
		<image>./images/Army Men - RTS (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Army Men - RTS (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Army Men - RTS (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Army Men - RTS (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pandemic Studios / Coyote</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Army Men</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="4945">
		<path>./Batman - Dark Tomorrow (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Batman : Dark Tomorrow</name>
		<desc>The storyline begins with the disappearance of Gotham City Police Commissioner James Gordon and the lockdown of Arkum Asylum. As Batman, players will have to infiltrate Arkum Asylum to find Gordon and uncover clues that reveal a bigger plot involving a criminal mastermind. Batman: Dark Tomorrow is a third-person action adventure game in which players will have to use a number Batman's skills in order to progress through the game. To aid him, Batman will also have access to plenty of traditional Bat-gadgets. The game will take place in a variety of locations in Gotham City, including Arkum Asylum, the docks, the sewer system, an abandoned steel factory, and Gazette Square.</desc>
		<image>./images/Batman - Dark Tomorrow (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Batman - Dark Tomorrow (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Batman - Dark Tomorrow (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Batman - Dark Tomorrow (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Batman - Dark Tomorrow (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20030320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Fighter Scrolling</genre>
		<family>Batman</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="59896">
		<path>./Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2</name>
		<desc>Activision's popular CABELA series is great for hunters in the off-season, and the 2006 entry in the series, CABELAS DANGEROUS HUNTS 2 for the Game Cube, offers yet another great adventure in the outdoors. As usual, players will be traveling the world looking for the biggest and most dangerous game, which includes wolves, cougars, bears, and even polar bears. This time, the game takes players through Australia, Africa, Alaska, and even to the frozen tundra of Siberia as they stalk the most wanted game. Players will have several options when it comes to choosing guns, bullets, and other accessories. Animal calls, traps, decoys, and bait are all available for sell and use in the wild. As players move through the single player missions, however, they will be given tasks other than just hunting down specific game. Some levels require players to keep wild animals away from a camp, save lost hikers from grizzly bears, or help an injured forest ranger get back to town. One of the most interesting additions to the game is the inclusion of slow motion time. Players can slow down time to line up that perfect shot. Slow motion time only lasts for a few seconds, however, so players still have to be quick on aiming and firing. CABELAS hunting games are always great, and CABELAS DANGEROUS HUNTS 2 is no exception. Gamers looking for the next big challenge in virtual hunting won't be disappointed.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2 (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2 (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2 (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2 (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20051116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sand Grain Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Cabela's</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="4938">
		<path>./Conflict - Desert Storm II - Back to Baghdad (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Conflict: Desert Storm II : Back to Baghdad</name>
		<desc>Part 2 in the series, Back to Baghdad is a squad-based shooter that picks up right where the first Desert Storm left off. John Bradley, Paul Foley, Mick Connors, and David Jones are back once again to team up and once again take on Saddam's henchmen. Whether it's protecting friendly choppers from enemy fire, the burning oil fields, Iraq's chemical weapons program, or secret superguns, there was apparently enough unfinished business left to serve as the basis for a second game. For the sequel, the developers improved on the team-mate AI and game UI, but the biggest appeal is once again the split-screen co-operative multiplayer for up to four players.</desc>
		<image>./images/Conflict - Desert Storm II - Back to Baghdad (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Conflict - Desert Storm II - Back to Baghdad (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Conflict - Desert Storm II - Back to Baghdad (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Conflict - Desert Storm II - Back to Baghdad (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20040106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pivotal Games</developer>
		<publisher>SCi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
	<game id="5089">
		<path>./Dead to Rights (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Dead To Rights</name>
		<desc>Dead To Rights is an action-game, straight out.  You play as Jack Slate, a police officer in Grant City.  On a routine call, you find a dead body; the body is your father.  Later framed, Jack becomes a fugitive, on the run from the law.

Your quest will take you to various places, from strip joints and hotels, to office complexes, and even prison... as an inmate.

Dead To Rights is an action game in every sense of the word.  When fighting, you have the opportunity to perform various moves, such as grabbing an enemy from behind and using him as a human shield, to tossing a fire extinguisher and shooting it, causing a huge explosion.  When against an enemy and you have no gun drawn, you can perform "disarm" moves, which causes your character to steal the enemy's gun, then performing some sort of finishes, such as a neck breaker.  Initially, only a few disarm moves are available, but more can be unlocked as your progress.

A unique addition in this game allows you to control Jack's best friend, and partner, Shadow, his K-9 dog.  Using Shadow, you can kill enemies from far away, and retrieve their gun in Shadow's jaws.

Dead To Rights features adrenaline combat, which is similar to that of "Bullet-Time" from Max Payne.  You can perform slow-motion dives and spins, giving you an advantage, as long as your adrenaline holds out.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dead to Rights (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dead to Rights (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dead to Rights (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dead to Rights (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Dead to Rights (USA)-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221101T163345" />
	</game>
</gameList>
