<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="47064">
		<path>./Bakumatsu Rouman Tokubetsu Hen.zip</path>
		<name>The Last Blade : Beyond the Destiny</name>
		<desc>1863. History's hidden secret is revealed. During the age known as "Bakumatsu", 135 years ago, chaos rules! It's all yours: A new type of weapon fighting game in which Power and Speed weapons, in addition to various Repel moves can be used to experience a new sensation in video game thrills!</desc>
		<image>./images/Bakumatsu Rouman Tokubetsu Hen-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bakumatsu Rouman Tokubetsu Hen-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bakumatsu Rouman Tokubetsu Hen-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bakumatsu Rouman Tokubetsu Hen-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>2c7076bd626b8360f8d3834384323f30</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160802" />
	</game>
	<game id="47070">
		<path>./Baseball Stars Color.zip</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars Color</name>
		<desc>Baseball Stars Color is sports game about baseball. Game is similar to Baseball Stars from NES but has less realistic characters and gameplay's style. You manage own baseball team and play in series of matches. Game has typical baseball rules - one player throws the ball, second hits the ball, someone else grabs it etc. Each character has own statistics</desc>
		<image>./images/Baseball Stars Color-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Baseball Stars Color-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Baseball Stars Color-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Baseball Stars Color-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<family>Baseball Stars</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>f2f296f4be215e826fac519fba96609b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160804" />
	</game>
	<game id="47071">
		<path>./Big Bang Pro Wrestling.zip</path>
		<name>Wrestling Madness</name>
		<desc>Only a handful of top wrestlers can be show their face on the TV for their fans at home. In the I.E.W mat, this rule is no exception. In an event practiced for 300 years, only the best performances are in demand. This year, the great king of the I.E.W, Joseph Steel, returns to defend his throne. The story of eight top wrestlers competing for the greatest prize on the ring, the I.E.W champion belt, is about to begin...</desc>
		<image>./images/Big Bang Pro Wrestling-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Big Bang Pro Wrestling-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Big Bang Pro Wrestling-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Big Bang Pro Wrestling-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20001123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>S-Neo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Wrestling</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>ded30a66c68fd997ed7d69677da8a79d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160804" />
	</game>
	<game id="51150">
		<path>./Bikkuriman 2000 - Viva! Pocket Festiva!.zip</path>
		<name>Bikkuriman 2000 - Viva! Pocket Festiva!</name>
		<desc>The game is a collection of mini-games. 
The player selects Sei Tenshi Takeru or Tenjo P?chi (Takeru only in the NeoGeo Pocket Color version) to move around a park and play the attractions. 
One of the mini-games is free and can be used to gain coins, with other attractions requiring coins to participate. 
The player gains more coins according to their score in the games, and in some attractions a rare seal can be obtained. 
Besides being used to participate in mini-games, the coins can be spent in slot machines to obtain seals from the Bug Akuma vs. Giga Tenshi Seal series, which can later be seen in a museum. 
At first only a few mini-games are available, with more being unlocked by completing objectives.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bikkuriman 2000 - Viva! Pocket Festiva!-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bikkuriman 2000 - Viva! Pocket Festiva!-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bikkuriman 2000 - Viva! Pocket Festiva!-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bikkuriman 2000 - Viva! Pocket Festiva!-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>ca3e26e2f539dbd35092fa9d7f561aff</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160807" />
	</game>
	<game id="47025">
		<path>./Bio Motor Unitron.zip</path>
		<name>Biomotor Unitron</name>
		<desc>Biomotor Unitron is a RPG for the Neo Geo Pocket Color.

After a meteor brings a new source of energy to the world, the construction of giant robots begins. These robots are used for entertainment and fight in arena fights against one-another for the title Master of Masters. You play a duo of characters that participates in these gladiator battles. You can control both characters and have to explore and perform quests to earn money and items to upgrade your Unitron robot with. You can talk to inhabitants of the city and buy new items at stores.

The Unitron changes visibly when you apply upgrades and a great deal of upgrades are at hand. Over two hundred different weapon configurations are possible. Each weapon and part has a certain material and element. Fire weapons will work better against wooden robots than water-based robots.

Beneath the city there are large dungeons where most quests will have to be solved and most items will be found.

The battles are like in Pokémon, completely menu based. You pick whatever powers you want to use from a drop-down list.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bio Motor Unitron-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Bio Motor Unitron-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bio Motor Unitron-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bio Motor Unitron-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>f4bbe8cf42074b75c8a911bf7b0562d5</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160809" />
	</game>
	<game id="87588">
		<path>./Bust-A-Move Pocket.zip</path>
		<name>Bust-A-Move Pocket</name>
		<desc>The classic game Bubble Bobble is the ancestor of Puzzle Bobble. Your aim in each stage is to break all the bubbles, by breaking 3 or more of the same color.  The game contains a two-player mode where each player tries to break all bubbles first.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bust-A-Move Pocket-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Bust-A-Move Pocket-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bust-A-Move Pocket-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bust-A-Move Pocket-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>1afb182567c6030c6d68f257e6245184</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160811" />
	</game>
	<game id="51140">
		<path>./Cool Boarders Pocket.zip</path>
		<name>Cool Boarders Pocket</name>
		<desc>Cool Boarders Pocket differs to other games in the Cool Boarders series. It features an isometric (overhead) view instead of a third-person perspective. The game features two play modes a free-ride mode where the player navigates an obstacle course with no restrictions until he/she reaches the goal, and a survival mode where the player snowboards through the obstacle course until they run out of health. The game allows the player to choose one of two characters; a female or male snowboarder.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cool Boarders Pocket-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Cool Boarders Pocket-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Cool Boarders Pocket-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cool Boarders Pocket-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>UEP Systems</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skiing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>dc8fa0cedef94fe22a219f2eeca43dc0</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160813" />
	</game>
	<game id="51139">
		<path>./Cool Cool Jam (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Cool Cool Jam</name>
		<desc>Cool Cool Jam is a rhythm video game which appeared on the Neo Geo Pocket Color in 2000. Cool Cool Jam is comparable in gameplay to other rhythm games such as: PaRappa the Rapper, Donkey Konga or Beatmania.

The storyline involves a boy and a girl who are transported 1,000 years into the future. To return home they must form a successful and popular music band.

The game can be played by one or two players. In two player mode the game plays like a duet; the players take it in turn to play tune and receive a message after completion. The game also features a single player storymode which has adventure game elements. Various instruments can be played in the game. Each instrument has a different playing style. The instruments include:

Clapping to a beat - a bar moves across the screen the player taps a button when they see a red dot. If successful the dot glows.

Violin - The player taps either the A or B when a red light (button A) or a green light (button B) appears. The power can be altered by moving the joystick up and down.

Bluesharp - The player moves the joystick to coincide with the position of the lights. The player then pushes A or B depending whether a red or green light appears.

Guitar - The player pushes A or B to play the strings and the joystick controls the pick.

Saxophone - The player moves the joystick and the buttons to control the pitch as the symbols appear on screen.

Trumpet - The player moves the joystick in four directions to change the pitch to coincide with the coloured symbols. The player then pushes A or B when the marker appears. A bar indicates air pressure.

Guitar 2 - Plays the same as the previous Guitar game only upside down.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cool Cool Jam (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Cool Cool Jam (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Cool Cool Jam (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cool Cool Jam (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance / Rhythm</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>f367e3bd61c308966a4815200fafb6a6</md5>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160814" />
	</game>
	<game id="47027">
		<path>./Crush Roller.zip</path>
		<name>Crush Roller</name>
		<desc>Crush Roller is a game for the Neo Geo Pocket Color based on the 1981 arcade game Make Trax, which was released as Crush Roller in Europe and Asia.

The object of the game is to color the entire maze-like playing field with a paint brush. While you paint, two enemies walk around in the maze, when they hit you, you lose a life.

A level has rollers which you can push forward with your paint brush. If you capture an enemy in the path of the roller he dies and is temporarily taken out of the game. This scores you extra points. Each subsequent enemy rolled over is worth more points.

Every once in a while another creature will pop up, it will run around leaving behind track marks in your paint. Painting over this creature removes it from the game and scores you additional points. His tracks have to be repainted.

When the entire maze is painted you win the level. Unlike the original arcade version the Neo Geo Pocket Color version has multiple levels.</desc>
		<image>./images/Crush Roller-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Crush Roller-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Crush Roller-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crush Roller-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>4a3cf02b131c4a23d0bcec6b0d49c137</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160816" />
	</game>
	<game id="51151">
		<path>./Delta Warp.zip</path>
		<name>Delta Warp</name>
		<desc>Delta Warp is a puzzle game released in 2000 for the Neo Geo Pocket Color. The game involves the player moving triangular shaped tiles across a board whilst avoiding hazards such as ice. Delta Warp was released only in Japan but features English text menus and the simple gameplay style means it can be played by non-Japanese readers.</desc>
		<image>./images/Delta Warp-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Delta Warp-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Delta Warp-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Delta Warp-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iosys</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>d4651757a3db5a8e5a5a64c337c6002f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160820" />
	</game>
	<game id="47029">
		<path>./Densetsu no Ogre Battle Gaiden - Zenobia no Ouji.zip</path>
		<name>Densetsu no Ogre Battle: Zenobia no Ouji</name>
		<desc>A side story to the original Ogre Battle game for the SNES, Zenobia no Ouji's side-story takes place during the fourteenth chapter ("The Capital of Milano") of the original game.

Much like its predecessor, the game is a unique blend of traditional RPG and strategy gameplay. As the hero of the game, you lead a growing army of troops as you progress through the game in a series of pivotal battles. Before each battle you are given the option to setup your army into distinct groups. Then you are given a mission on the map and you can then set your army out to do your bidding. As your unit groups travel along the map on the way to their given objective, they'll happen along enemy unit groups. When they meet, the game switches to an isometric-view of the automated turn-based battle that ensues.</desc>
		<image>./images/Densetsu no Ogre Battle Gaiden - Zenobia no Ouji-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Densetsu no Ogre Battle Gaiden - Zenobia no Ouji-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Densetsu no Ogre Battle Gaiden - Zenobia no Ouji-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Densetsu no Ogre Battle Gaiden - Zenobia no Ouji-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Quest</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>26d0557d8a465aa8f430d5e4d94c679a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160822" />
	</game>
	<game id="47030">
		<path>./Densha De GO! 2 (J).zip</path>
		<name>Densha de GO! 2</name>
		<desc>The 1998 sequel of the popular Japanese train driving game by Taito has once again been ported to various home systems. For the first time on the PlayStation, it is possible to drive through the snow, and take a seat in the cockpit of a Shinkansen bullet train.

The gameplay is more arcade than simulation. The focus is on stopping at the stations at the perfect moment and position, keeping up with the schedule, obeying signals and speed limits, and ensuring the safety and comfort of the passengers. Mistakes result in points being deducted from a counter. If it reaches 0, the game is over.

The following routes are available:

1. Hokuhoku Line from Naoetsu to Uragawara
2. Tohoku Shinkansen from Morioka to Shin-Hanamaki
3. Akita Shinkansen from Akita to Omagari
4. Keihin-Tohoku Line from Shinagawa to Ueno
5. Osaka Loop Line from Osaka to Tennoji (not in the Arcade original)
6. Kagoshima Main Line from Hakata to Kokura (only in PlayStation and Windows versions)</desc>
		<image>./images/Densha De GO! 2 (J)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Densha De GO! 2 (J)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Densha De GO! 2 (J)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Densha De GO! 2 (J)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>c79dd020410d1d80c2709cb6af4cf64a</md5>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160825" />
	</game>
	<game id="87554">
		<path>./Dive Alert - Matt's Version.zip</path>
		<name>Dive Alert : Matt's Version</name>
		<desc>The player takes control of a character named Matt. The game is set in the future and the world is primarily surrounded by water. The only small patch of land called is called Terra. The player must show their worth to be accepted on to Terra by proving their skill as a submarine commander and destroying enemy vessels.

Matt's version features different characters, items and boats to Becky's version. These are logged in a device similar to a Pokédex. The battles take place against other ships. A radar view is used to help players guide torpedoes against the enemy. A large part of the game is text based with animated cutscenes. Two players can link-up with the cable to battle, exchange ships and accumulate other data.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dive Alert - Matt's Version-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Dive Alert - Matt's Version-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dive Alert - Matt's Version-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dive Alert - Matt's Version-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20000416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sacnoth</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>0c38b2d5d1a2be15d6c15c6b16b7bc98</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160827" />
	</game>
	<game id="87555">
		<path>./Dokodemo Mahjong.zip</path>
		<name>Doko Demo Mahjong</name>
		<image>./images/Dokodemo Mahjong-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Dokodemo Mahjong-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dokodemo Mahjong-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dokodemo Mahjong-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<genre>Asiatic board game / Mahjong</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>66885d788f8474295fccbeba107f2421</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160829" />
	</game>
	<game id="87556">
		<path>./Dynamite Slugger.zip</path>
		<name>Dynamite Slugger</name>
		<desc>Dynamite Slugger is a video game. It was released in 2000 for the Neo Geo Pocket Color handheld game console. The game is similar to other Baseball videogames on the Neo Geo Pocket Color such as Baseball Stars and Baseball Stars Color. Due to Dynamite Slugger being the latest baseball videogame to be released for the Neo Geo Pocket Color it features better graphics than other sports titles.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dynamite Slugger-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Dynamite Slugger-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dynamite Slugger-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dynamite Slugger-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>c84f675a617df14b1a1bf06f02be773d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160832" />
	</game>
	<game id="47032">
		<path>./Evolution - Eternal Dungeons.zip</path>
		<name>Evolution: Eternal Dungeon</name>
		<desc>A portable version of Evolution: The World of Sacred Device. Eternal Dungeon tells the story of the young explorer Mag Launcher and his quest for the fabled Evolutia, an item of immense power.

The basic premise of the game is to take quests in the town and then assemble your party and attempt to clear out the many dungeons in the game, grinding your characters and getting the loot and experience needed to advance the plot and buy items, equipment, and upgrades for your Cy-frame, a robotic attachment that enables Mag to enhance his combat abilities.

As expected for a portable version, the gameplay has been significantly downgraded from its original Dreamcast version. Town navigation is menu-driven and all graphics are now top-down 2D sprites, with all dungeons being pre-designed instead of randomly generated. Combat is turn-based using a menu system from which you select your actions for each party member (up to 3) and execute them, but otherwise remains unchanged.</desc>
		<image>./images/Evolution - Eternal Dungeons-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Evolution - Eternal Dungeons-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Evolution - Eternal Dungeons-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Evolution - Eternal Dungeons-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>9c9c2d533be340600ef9f92ed1253dd9</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160834" />
	</game>
	<game id="47033">
		<path>./Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton.zip</path>
		<name>Fantastic Night Dreams: Cotton</name>
		<desc>Fantastic Night Dreams: Cotton is a 2D side-scrolling shooter in which the player takes the role of the young witch Cotton, who sets out on her magical broom on a quest to get her favorite candy. Fortunately for us her obsession gets her in the way of several world-threatening terrors that she must destroy in standard shooter fare.

The game features an experience-earning system in which the more enemies the player kills the more he can upgrade his weapon by collecting power crystals. Players can also charge their weapon for special attacks and enlist the aid of Silk, Cotton's magical fairy friend who can form up in different "option" configurations.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>5a2a155706a201a1c0227c7fe671256f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160837" />
	</game>
	<game id="47034">
		<path>./Faselei!.zip</path>
		<name>Faselei!</name>
		<desc>Faselei! is one of the last titles to be released for the Neo Geo Pocket Color and even features digitised lyrics to the game's main theme. Heavily story driven, this strategy RPG takes place in a time when mechs known as TS are the weapon of choice for combat. Gameplay revolves around the battles and customising your TS between those battles.

Battles are part turn based and part realtime. The player inputs their actions at the beginning of the turn. The amount of actions they can input is dependant on their type of TS. Once they have finished their selection everything is played out in realtime for the duration of the turn. This makes thinking about what your opponents and allies will do in advance essential before taking your turn.</desc>
		<image>./images/Faselei!-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Faselei!-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Faselei!-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Faselei!-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sacnoth</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>f580078164dc2b8dffb9f38eeec1035d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160839" />
	</game>
	<game id="47035">
		<path>./Fatal Fury - First Contact.zip</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury : First Contact</name>
		<desc>Using the world-famous Japanese "SD" (Super-Deformed) artwork style, this is the only title of the Fatal Fury series to be released on SNK's color handheld.

The game is based on its arcade/console counterpart Real Bout Fatal Fury 2: The Newcomers, and has its main characteristics, like the possibility of execute special moves while blocking (a.k.a. Breakshots), the execution of high-strength blows (a.k.a. S. Power and P. Power moves) and the starring of two new combatants (Li Xiangfei and Rick Strowd).

Due to NGPC hardware limitations, some characters have been removed from the main cast (as well as the background/foreground battle plane system). With this, the fighters initially available for this contest are: Andy Bogard, Terry Bogard, Joe Higashi, Mai Shiranui, Kim Kaphwan, Ryuji Yamazaki, Rick Strowd, Li Xiangfei, Billy Kane, Wolfgang Krauser and Geese Howard.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fatal Fury - First Contact-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Fatal Fury - First Contact-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Fatal Fury - First Contact-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fatal Fury - First Contact-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Fatal Fury</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>690a3397f20e31b2c4a2833f51670245</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160844" />
	</game>
	<game id="47036">
		<path>./Ganbare NeoPoke Kun.zip</path>
		<name>Ganbare Neo Poke-kun</name>
		<desc>In this unique game you keep watch on the wacky Neo Poke-kun, a cartoony programmer...thing that lives locked in his small Tokyo apartment. You don't have direct control of his actions but instead interact with him indirectly by switching stuff in his apartment on and off, which triggers different reactions from him. More importantly you can invite different characters to visit Neo Poke-kun, which will also trigger different reactions from him. Depending on the time of day and the visitor you may get different reactions from Poke-kun, and if you make him happy enough he'll get to work and code a mini-game for you.

These collection of 30 games form the bulk of the gameplay, and include different clones of other games, shooters, short platformers, and compact puzzle challenges similar to Wario Ware

The game has a distinctly bizarre sense of humor with tons of wacky animations played whenever something happens to your Poke-kun, and while some games use basic vector graphics, most use 2D sprites.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ganbare NeoPoke Kun-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Ganbare NeoPoke Kun-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ganbare NeoPoke Kun-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ganbare NeoPoke Kun-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>99ed127490f9d5d6482d20cc6abc8056</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160848" />
	</game>
	<game id="87557">
		<path>./Infinity Cure (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Infinity Cure</name>
		<desc>A port of the visual novel "Infinity" for the Neo-Geo Pocket Color</desc>
		<image>./images/Infinity Cure (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Infinity Cure (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Infinity Cure (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Infinity Cure (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kindle Imagine Develop</developer>
		<publisher>Kindle Imagine Develop</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>4bda8b3669c5bbd72266853940d626cb</md5>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87600">
		<path>./Kikou Seiki Unitron - Sono Tsuide. Hikari Umareru Chi Yori.zip</path>
		<name>Bio Motor Unitron 2</name>
		<desc>Kikou Seiki Unitron (English: Armor Chronicles Unitron) is the sequel to Biomotor Unitron. 
It was only released in Japan.
The game takes place 400 years after Biomotor Unitron. 
Kikou Seiki Unitron plays similar to Biomotor Unitron with top down dungeons and menu-based combat. 
The game requires the player to upgrade their unitron robot with various weapons and accessories to compete against various enemies within the dungeon areas. 
Using a link cable two players can pit their unitrons against each other in a head-to-head battle.</desc>
		<image>./images/Kikou Seiki Unitron - Sono Tsuide. Hikari Umareru Chi Yori-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Kikou Seiki Unitron - Sono Tsuide. Hikari Umareru Chi Yori-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Kikou Seiki Unitron - Sono Tsuide. Hikari Umareru Chi Yori-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kikou Seiki Unitron - Sono Tsuide. Hikari Umareru Chi Yori-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>55387b2ffa9edf79668a76118a895993</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87558">
		<path>./King of Fighters - Battle de Paradise.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters - Battle de Paradise</name>
		<desc>The King of Fighters: Battle De Paradise is a board based, two player party game that plays in a similar manner as sugoroku. The player can either link with another user to play or challenge the CPU. Each side choose one of four original characters to represent their place on the board as well as an accompanying Striker character (the Extra Strikers from The King of Fighters '99: Evolution). If they're unsatisfied with their avatar's name, an option to rename their character is also given.

Players roll a dice and move along the board with various squares. Specially marked squares can trigger one of many mini-games for the player's striker to participate in for coins. Mini-games themselves are a collection of memory games, dodging contests, quiz challenges, and other games common to the genre. Some of these mini-games refer to SNK's older games such as T.A.N.K or previous King of Fighters titles. The main goal of the game is to gather coins to buy stars; the player with the most stars wins.</desc>
		<image>./images/King of Fighters - Battle de Paradise-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/King of Fighters - Battle de Paradise-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/King of Fighters - Battle de Paradise-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/King of Fighters - Battle de Paradise-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000706T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
		<family>The King of Fighters</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>362e9c04ec255225eeb0a9dee8fcac1b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47038">
		<path>./King of Fighters R-2.zip</path>
		<name>King of Fighters R-2</name>
		<desc>Using again the Japanese "SD" (Super-Deformed) artwork style (now reworked), the KOF Series makes your debut in the new SNK's color handheld. The title brings the same gameplay characteristics present in its arcade/console counter-part The King of Fighters '98, like the possibility of choose between two game modes (Advanced or Extra), an identical adaptation of the battle stages, the addition of "Advantage System" (directly related to the power gauges) and the chance to battle with a powered version of the "franchise boss", Rugal Bernstein.

Unlike the previous game (The King of Fighters R-1), this sequence doesn't have a defined storyline, but it's implicit that Rugal is still alive and returns once again to try conquer the world and satisfy his evil ambitions.

The teams included in the game were slightly reformulated and now are the following ones (this time, Leona Heidern and Iori Yagami are single entries):

1. Team Kusanagi (Kyo Kusanagi, Saisyu Kusanagi and Shingo Yabuki)Super Babe Team (Athena Asamiya, Yuri Sakazaki and Kasumi Todo)
2. New Southtown Team (Ryo Sakazaki, Mai Shiranui and Terry Bogard)
3. Orochi Team (Yashiro Nanakase, Shermie and Chris)</desc>
		<image>./images/King of Fighters R-2-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/King of Fighters R-2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/King of Fighters R-2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/King of Fighters R-2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>The King of Fighters</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>d5c583a11012494c2ed738b2a2c5ab53</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87559">
		<path>./Koi Koi Mahjong.zip</path>
		<name>Koi Koi Mahjong</name>
		<desc>"Koi Koi Mahjong" is a Mahjong simulation, reserved for the Japanese market.
The player can choose between 4 protagonists and 3 game modes.</desc>
		<image>./images/Koi Koi Mahjong-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Koi Koi Mahjong-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Koi Koi Mahjong-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Koi Koi Mahjong-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20000309T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<genre>Asiatic board game / Mahjong</genre>
		<md5>05ab35ed7be398072cae34783aa6751a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87560">
		<path>./Magical Drop Pocket.zip</path>
		<name>Magical Drop Pocket</name>
		<desc>Magical Drop Pocket's core mechanics are similar to those of Magical Drop III. The only exception is that that the battlefield consists of six columns instead of seven, akin to the Super Famicom ports of the first two Magical Drop games.

The game features Story, Self Challenge and Friend Challenge; these correspond to the standard 1P VS Com, Solo, and 2P VS modes featured in other Magical Drop games. Story features five difficulty modes while Self Challenge features three.

Like many other handheld puzzle games of the time, Story does not feature a "true" AI opponent; instead, the player attempts to fill a gauge by creating chains. While the player attempts to fill this gauge, the AI attacks at random intervals.</desc>
		<image>./images/Magical Drop Pocket-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Magical Drop Pocket-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Magical Drop Pocket-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Magical Drop Pocket-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SAS Sakata</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>0f120e95cadd338306781b180a448f59</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87561">
		<path>./Memories Off - Pure.zip</path>
		<name>Memories Off - Pure</name>
		<desc>Memories Off: Pure game takes place a few years prior to the events in Memories Off. (a Visual Novel released in 1999 on Playstation) 
Tomoya and Ayaka are neighbors who communicate with each other through their bedroom windows and who attend the same junior high school with Yue. 
One playthrough of Pure takes about 3-4 hours, but it has replay value through a pair of endings and during subsequent runthroughs to re-experience second-half scenarios from Ayaka's and Yue's points of view.</desc>
		<image>./images/Memories Off - Pure-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Memories Off - Pure-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Memories Off - Pure-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Memories Off - Pure-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kindle Imagine Develop</developer>
		<publisher>Kindle Imagine Develop</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>2e518837dfebd4cb10ac117a339c5854</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47040">
		<path>./Metal Slug - 1st Mission.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug : 1st Mission</name>
		<desc>As a member of the elite forces squad "Peregrine Falcons," your mission is to eliminate the evil Colonel Bildegaarn. Using the Metal Slug multifunction tank and the Slug Flyer as well as your wits and handgun blast through up to 17 missions in your quest to make the world safe from tyranny. Multiple stage progressions and a gameplay ranking system give reason to play through more than once. In-game save lets the player on the go turn off the Neo Geo Pocket and not lose progress.</desc>
		<image>./images/Metal Slug - 1st Mission-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Metal Slug - 1st Mission-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Metal Slug - 1st Mission-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Metal Slug - 1st Mission-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Metal Slug - 1st Mission-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ukiyotei</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Run and Gun</genre>
		<family>Metal Slug</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220928T063345</lastplayed>
		<md5>a7dfee9950d0679cabb4ee6dfc530fb6</md5>
		<gametime>137</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47041">
		<path>./Metal Slug - 2nd Mission.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug : 2nd Mission</name>
		<desc>Take control of the Metal Slug tank on the NGPC once again, this time to defeat the rebel strike force "Phantom." Travel through 38 stages in a non-linear battle path defeating enemy troops and rescuing hostages. Pilot the Metal Slug tank, Slug Flyer combat jet, and the Slug Sub submarine and fire the heavy machine gun, rocket launcher, and fire gun. Two unique playable characters, a list of rescued hostages, and a time attack mode add depth to this side-scroller.</desc>
		<image>./images/Metal Slug - 2nd Mission-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Metal Slug - 2nd Mission-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Metal Slug - 2nd Mission-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Metal Slug - 2nd Mission-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Metal Slug - 2nd Mission-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ukiyotei</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Run and Gun</genre>
		<family>Metal Slug</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>d159bd2b5e9a7f97236ec9a79c83c6c8</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87562">
		<path>./Mezase! Kanji Ou.zip</path>
		<name>Mezase! Kanji Ou</name>
		<desc>A kanji-study game with a quiz-like approach.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mezase! Kanji Ou-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Mezase! Kanji Ou-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mezase! Kanji Ou-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mezase! Kanji Ou-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20000120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Educational</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>2fd2ffa3e15e05fc4512a10d98fbdd95</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87563">
		<path>./Mizuki Shigeru no Youkai Shashinkan.zip</path>
		<name>Mizuki Shigeru No Youkai Shashinkan</name>
		<desc>This is an RPG based on the works of the famous manga artist Shigeru Mizuki, known in Japan for his knowledge of youkai (supernatural ghosts of Japanese folklore). In this game, you explore various areas of Japan, taking pictures of youkai, and using these pictures in card battles. This is a very popular game among Japanese NGPC enthusiasts.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mizuki Shigeru no Youkai Shashinkan-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Mizuki Shigeru no Youkai Shashinkan-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mizuki Shigeru no Youkai Shashinkan-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mizuki Shigeru no Youkai Shashinkan-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ukiyotei</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>89b605a1fc6db5855b432ccc62f9e6e3</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87564">
		<path>./Neo 21.zip</path>
		<name>Neo 21 : Real Casino Series</name>
		<desc>Neo 21 is a casino-style blackjack game that offers three modes of play: Casino Mode, Original Mode, and Versus mode. As a casino style game, it supports all the actions that players sitting at a casino blackjack table can perform.

Blackjack, also known as "twenty-one," is a card game where players attempt to put together a hand that adds up to as close to 21 in total points without going over. Aces count for one or eleven, face cards count for ten, and the other cards count as their respective values.

At the beginning of each hand, the dealer deals each player, including the dealer, two cards. Each round players can opt to hit, stand, split or double down. When a player calls for a hit, the dealer deals another card. A player who stands is dealt no more cards for the rest of the hand. Players who get dealt two cards of the same value can split them, put another wager down and play both as individual hands. Doubling down is the act of calling for one last hit, and doubling your wager at the same time. Any player who goes over 21 in value busts and loses.

In Neo 21, players engage in a one-on-one match against a CPU dealer, or in the Versus Mode, two players can compete via the link cable, with one acting as the dealer.</desc>
		<image>./images/Neo 21-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Neo 21-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Neo 21-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Neo 21-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dyna Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Dyna Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>0865f375ead2febbc86ab3fb9274b9b7</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87565">
		<path>./Neo Baccarat.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Baccarat - Real Casino Series</name>
		<desc>Experience the Thrills of NEO BACCARAT, the New Game in the Pocket Casino Series!

Will the House win? Or maybe the Player? Guess on the winner and place your bets! "Baccarat" is the hottest game in the casino. And now you can find all its pulse-pounding excitement on NEOGEO POCKET COLOR! The Pocket Casino Series: NEO BACCARAT. Are you up for the challenge?!

Thrill to the fun of "Original Mode" and "Casino Mode" in Single-Player Games!
Use the NEOGEO POCKET LINK CABLE for 2-Player Showdowns!
Be it American- or European-Style Baccarat, NEOGEO POCKET's got it!

To see explanations of game rules, select the "Game Explanation" item in the Option Menu.</desc>
		<image>./images/Neo Baccarat-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Neo Baccarat-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Neo Baccarat-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Neo Baccarat-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dyna Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Dyna Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Cards</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>1018f765f460588d975c9b4e9385a547</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87566">
		<path>./Neo Cherry Master Color.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Cherry Master Color : Real Casino Series</name>
		<desc>Experience the play of actual casino gaming! Feel the fun of ultra-real slot machine game simulation!!
	
"Cherry Master", the slot machine popular in casinos throughout the world becomes part of the NEOGEO POCKET COLOR. With the vivid screen and the system of no different from the real thing, making for real, adult gaming entertainment!

Includes 2 modes for that tantalizing taste of slot machine gaming! (Original mode for professionals / Simple Mode for beginners)</desc>
		<image>./images/Neo Cherry Master Color-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Neo Cherry Master Color-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Neo Cherry Master Color-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Neo Cherry Master Color-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dyna Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>7992904f8c4040aee0cde040afbf757d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87567">
		<path>./Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou</name>
		<desc>Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou is a Sports game, developed and published by Dyna Corporation, which was released in Japan in 1999.</desc>
		<image>./images/Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19990422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dyna Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Dyna Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Race</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>cd5c1eb7cb2e83d6b6d64918574c8cdb</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87568">
		<path>./Neo Dragon's Wild.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Dragon's Wild : Real Casino Series</name>
		<desc>The super authentic Poker game simulation!!

The popular casino poker game for NEOGEO POCKET! This system can be enjoyed by everyone: from enthusiasts who enjoy casino game realism, to casino game novices. Now you can enjoy true game excitement with Neo Dragon's Wild - the new pocket casino game!

Beginners can select Simple Mode for easier game settings.
Skilled players can choose Original Mode to enjoy real poker with authentic feel.</desc>
		<image>./images/Neo Dragon's Wild-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Neo Dragon's Wild-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Neo Dragon's Wild-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Neo Dragon's Wild-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dyna Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>c0ced1d22506e46c4667bc0e926d921e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47042">
		<path>./Neo Geo Cup '98 Plus Color.zip</path>
		<name>NeoGeo Cup '98 Plus</name>
		<desc>Neo Geo Cup '98 Plus is a soccer game for the Neo Geo Pocket. The game features single match play, head-to-head play (using a link cable), and story mode. You can choose to play one of 16 international teams. Each team has their own collective stats. On the field you can perform passes, shots, dribbles, slidings and charges. In the story mode you have to win as many matches as possible in a series of tournaments. Before and during matches you can change the field formations and switch players. Each won match gives you prize money, this can be used to buy items for your team. These items usually improve one stat, but decrease another.</desc>
		<image>./images/Neo Geo Cup '98 Plus Color-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Neo Geo Cup '98 Plus Color-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Neo Geo Cup '98 Plus Color-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Neo Geo Cup '98 Plus Color-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>a6c3369f28558e4a9719dc54d50be713</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87569">
		<path>./Neo Mystery Bonus.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Mystery Bonus : Real Casino Series</name>
		<desc>Neo Mystery Bonus, while not the most fully featured slots game around, is quick and simple to get into. Like most other slots games You start by placing your bet then spin the slots and test your luck. The graphics are plain and depict the different icons on the machine very clearly. There are no extra modes in the game, just basic slots.</desc>
		<image>./images/Neo Mystery Bonus-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Neo Mystery Bonus-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Neo Mystery Bonus-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Neo Mystery Bonus-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dyna Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>cef050e2591435a5c41ff851afa55a82</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87570">
		<path>./Neo Poke Pro Yakyuu.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Poke Pro Yakyuu</name>
		<desc>NeoPoke Pro Yakyuu is a sports game, developed and published by SNK, which was released in Japan in 1999.</desc>
		<image>./images/Neo Poke Pro Yakyuu-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Neo Poke Pro Yakyuu-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Neo Poke Pro Yakyuu-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Neo Poke Pro Yakyuu-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19990527T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>93d3810ae176507ebaae782a612c930b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47043">
		<path>./Neo Turf Masters.zip</path>
		<name>Neo Turf Masters</name>
		<desc>Neo Turf Masters is a golf game that offers play in three different countries. You can play in the US, Germany, and Japan. There are 18 holes per course, just like in real life, which totals to 54 holes. The game features a two-player versus mode and three single player modes. You can choose from one of six different characters, who each have their own strengths and weaknesses. Like many other golf games, you use an accurate click type of play, where you click in an overhead map where you want to hit the ball, then adjust hook, slice, and power. In Versus mode, you can earn "super-clubs" that can only be used once. These can also be traded between friends.</desc>
		<image>./images/Neo Turf Masters-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Neo Turf Masters-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Neo Turf Masters-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Neo Turf Masters-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Golf</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>e055837bb0e227c1ddc3e68b0aa89ae9</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47044">
		<path>./Pac-Man.zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Man</name>
		<desc>One of the most popular and influential games of the 1980's, Pac-Man stars a little, yellow dot-muncher who works his way around to clear a maze of the various dots and fruit which inhabit the board.

Pac-Man's goal is continually challenged by four ghosts: The shy blue ghost Bashful (Inky), the trailing red ghost Shadow (Blinky), the fast pink ghost Speedy (Pinky), and the forgetful orange ghost Pokey (Clyde).  One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Pac-Man.

Pac-Man can turn the tables on his pursuers by eating of the four Energizers located within the maze.  During this time, the ghosts turn blue, and Pac-Man can eat them for bonus points.  This only lasts for a limited amount of time, as the ghost's eyes float back to their center box, and regenerate to chase after Pac-Man again.

Survive a few rounds of gameplay, and be treated to humorous intermissions between Pac-Man and the ghosts.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pac-Man-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pac-Man-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pac-Man-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pac-Man-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Pac-Man-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<family>Pac-Man</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>ac5ad76d5e6614ae576c2c837f0fab1d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87573">
		<path>./Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Azteca.zip</path>
		<name>Pachisuro Azure Oogoku Pocket Azteca</name>
		<desc>This software reproduces the popular pachislot machine "Azteca". In addition to playing the actual machine, the software is equipped with a database of "Reach Me" and "CT Lottery Laws" and a "CT Machine Notebook Mode" that allows users to enter records of their actual play at a real hall.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Azteca-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Azteca-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Azteca-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Azteca-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20000210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Slot machine</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>1676f66c906188d9dca7015fb5aada0e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87574">
		<path>./Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Dekahel 2.zip</path>
		<name>Pachi-slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Dekahel 2</name>
		<desc>Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket: DH2 is a Miscellaneous game, developed and published by Aruze Corp, which was released in Japan in 2001.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Dekahel 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Dekahel 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Dekahel 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Dekahel 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20010115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Slot machine</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>1cbb6692db2357f80691bc7462ed4eae</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87575">
		<path>./Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Delsol 2.zip</path>
		<name>Pachisuro Aruze Oogoku Pocket - Delsol 2</name>
		<desc>Includes "Del Sol 2," the successor to the "Azteca" pachislot machine. A total of four modes can be played: "Free Play Mode" for careful simulation, "Replay Removal Training Mode" and "CT Training Mode" for practice focused on techniques necessary for strategy, and "Notebook Mode" for actual data input and analysis.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Delsol 2-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Delsol 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Delsol 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Delsol 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Slot machine</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>59c600d2ffe3a44e8cfa96824dc90c8e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87576">
		<path>./Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - e-Cup.zip</path>
		<name>Pachisuro Aruze Ohgoku Pocket - E-cup</name>
		<desc>A pachislot machine simulator of the same name, based on the subject of golf. It features a "Replay Removal Training Mode" to learn techniques for winning large amounts of medals, and a "Strategy Memo Function" that allows users to create a database by entering the results of playing the actual machine, income and expenditure, and the payout status of the expansion.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - e-Cup-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - e-Cup-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - e-Cup-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - e-Cup-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Slot machine</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>0dbeba28e62ece2e9b08c62890650ff5</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87577">
		<path>./Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Hanabi.zip</path>
		<name>Pachisuro Aruze Oogoku Pocket Hanabi</name>
		<desc>Software aimed at capturing the popular pachislot "HANABI". We will support the capture of the actual machine with a full range of functions such as a function to make a note of the actual number of balls in the hall and the amount of income and expenditure, free play, and data analysis. There is also a "delay".</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Hanabi-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Hanabi-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Hanabi-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Hanabi-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>19991021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Slot machine</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>b3edf9ad99cbd433c8e62836f32092ec</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87578">
		<path>./Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Oohanabi.zip</path>
		<name>Pachi-slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Oohanabi</name>
		<desc>A complete reproduction of the actual pachislot machine of the same name published by Aruze. Using the function settings, various strategy techniques can be cultivated. It also has a "strategy memo function" that allows users to create their own original database by inputting the results of actual play at the hall, income and expenditure, and payout status of expansion.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Oohanabi-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Oohanabi-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Oohanabi-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Oohanabi-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20001214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Slot machine</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>3c340fe221635ba52aae8adcc8e43758</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87579">
		<path>./Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Porcano 2.zip</path>
		<name>Pachi-slot Aruze Oukoku Porcano 2</name>
		<desc>The latest in the Aruze Pachiro simulator series. This time, the popular PORKANO2 model is included. Practice with this software to hone your skills and conquer real pachislot.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Porcano 2-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Porcano 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Porcano 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Porcano 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20000720T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Slot machine</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>8efd3c40988452782e55548f7369a050</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87580">
		<path>./Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Ward of Lights.zip</path>
		<name>Pachisuro Aruze Oogoku Pocket Ward Of Lights</name>
		<desc>Reproduced Word of Lights following the No. 1 model Azteca in 1999. In addition to normal play as on the actual machine, there is a mode for intensive practice of replay removal and CT play, as well as a database and a mode for registering practice records.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Ward of Lights-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Ward of Lights-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Ward of Lights-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Ward of Lights-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Slot machine</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>da41c689c64815ad2b374a7ff52e819b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87581">
		<path>./Pachinko Hisshou Guide - Pocket Parlor.zip</path>
		<name>Pachinko Hissyou Guide Pocket Parlor</name>
		<desc>Software that reproduces the popular actual machine "CR Fever Casino RX". The software is complete with commentary by Mr. Osaki Ichimanbatsu, who is well-known for his work in the magazine "Pachinko Hissatsu Guide. A "Reach Gallery Mode" is also available, which displays the reach action and reliability.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachinko Hisshou Guide - Pocket Parlor-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachinko Hisshou Guide - Pocket Parlor-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachinko Hisshou Guide - Pocket Parlor-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachinko Hisshou Guide - Pocket Parlor-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19991125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vistec</developer>
		<publisher>Sankyo</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>299761888bb026d76b698b9745bd8d27</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87572">
		<path>./Picture Puzzle.zip</path>
		<name>Picture Puzzle</name>
		<desc>Picture Puzzle (Oekaki Puzzle in Japan) is a paint-by-numbers puzzle game developed by Success for the Neo Geo Pocket Color. The game plays identical to Nintendo's Picross series. Picture Puzzle offers a total of 200 puzzles: 20 5x5 puzzles, 105 10x10's, and 75 15x15's. This is biased towards smaller puzzles because the grids in anything larger would be incredibly tiny on the NGPC's screen. Also, larger puzzles take much longer to solve; smaller puzzles allows you to pick up the Pocket for 10-20 minutes at a time and, on a good day, solve a complete puzzle.

Upon completion of a puzzle, the game replaces it with a colored version of the same grid and gives it a title. Especially with the smaller puzzles, this is helpful in that it is sometimes otherwise unclear as to what exactly the completed picture is supposed to be. Because it colorizes them, the game requires the Neo Geo Pocket Color, i.e, it won't run on a monochrome Neo Geo Pocket.</desc>
		<image>./images/Picture Puzzle-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Picture Puzzle-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Picture Puzzle-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Picture Puzzle-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000616T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>81d3c10271ad5b09032dd00321b41aa0</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87583">
		<path>./Pocket Love if.zip</path>
		<name>Pocket Love If</name>
		<desc>The third in a series that was released up to the second Game Boy. The purpose is to train myself as a high school student and receive a confession from a girl on White Day. With the addition of new characters, the system and production have also been enhanced.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pocket Love if-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pocket Love if-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pocket Love if-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pocket Love if-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kindle Imagine Develop</developer>
		<publisher>Kindle Imagine Develop</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>62347264d918559a95034be7cea8756d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87585">
		<path>./Pocket Tennis Color.zip</path>
		<name>Pocket Tennis Color : Pocket Sports Series</name>
		<desc>This sports favorite boasts eight playable characters and enough tennis action to keep any fan happy. Enjoy realistic play that gives you complete array of shots, including lobs, high-speed smashes and more. Exhibition mode sets up a single match against the computer, or, with the NeoGeo Cable Link (sold separately), a friend. Tournament mode pits you against stiff competition to see if you've got what it takes to earn the title. Save your match results so you can brag later. Record mode lets you relax and enjoy your on-court accomplishments by viewing your records and trophies.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pocket Tennis Color-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pocket Tennis Color-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pocket Tennis Color-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pocket Tennis Color-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Tennis</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>c7bfc59b4cb593409541d4ccffe083b4</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87587">
		<path>./Puyo Pop.zip</path>
		<name>Puyo Puyo 2</name>
		<desc>The object of this head-to-head puzzle game is to clear your grid of falling patterns called puyos by forming chains of four or more same-colored puyos in a straight line or one of several geometric patterns. What makes this a challenging two-player contest is the fact that when you clear a chain of puyos from your grid, it drops a random piece of filler onto your opponent's grid. The more puyos you clear, the more you fill your opponent's grid, and if you can clutter up his grid enough to fill it to the top, you've won the game.</desc>
		<image>./images/Puyo Pop-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Puyo Pop-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Puyo Pop-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Puyo Pop-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<family>Puyo Puyo</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>d40dc57b9cc3a30a2400f8cfd8724578</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87588">
		<path>./Puzzle Bobble Mini.zip</path>
		<name>Bust-A-Move Pocket</name>
		<desc>The classic game Bubble Bobble is the ancestor of Puzzle Bobble. Your aim in each stage is to break all the bubbles, by breaking 3 or more of the same color.  The game contains a two-player mode where each player tries to break all bubbles first.</desc>
		<image>./images/Puzzle Bobble Mini-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Puzzle Bobble Mini-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Puzzle Bobble Mini-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Puzzle Bobble Mini-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>94537fd169751658f3a50a3b7a80cef2</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47047">
		<path>./Puzzle Link II.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle Link 2</name>
		<desc>The gameplay of Puzzle Link 2 is generally identical to the first game: Puzzle Link is a game where blocks of matching color have to be dissolved. New blocks constantly scroll into the screen from the top. The game is over when the first blocks reach the bottom of the screen. You can dissolve blocks by shooting at them. The shots form a line where they impact. If that line connects otherwise unconnected blocks of the same color they will dissolve.

There are new modes in Puzzle Link 2. Like the original, there are the standard challenge and puzzle rounds. But new to the series is the marathon-style game where you continue eliminating pieces as the game gradually increases speed. In this mode, more power-ups appear as the player performs faster. Here, you get three shots that will eliminate the same color tile from the board. The game also has link cable support for two players.</desc>
		<image>./images/Puzzle Link II-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Puzzle Link II-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Puzzle Link II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Puzzle Link II-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>7108cc38b0c5e14eec247db0f2f3b84c</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47046">
		<path>./Puzzle Link.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle Link</name>
		<desc>Puzzle Link is a game where blocks of matching color have to be dissolved. New blocks constantly scroll into the screen from the top. The game is over when the first blocks reach the bottom of the screen. You can dissolve blocks by shooting at them. The shots form a line where they impact. If that line connects otherwise unconnected blocks of the same color they will dissolve.

There are three different modes: In "Normal" you have to link two special blocks that appear after some time. If you manage to finish the level within the time limit you will unlock one of 50 collectible cards. In "Clear Mode" you have to clear a given constellation of blocks. "Battle Mode" is a two player link-cable mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/Puzzle Link-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Puzzle Link-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Puzzle Link-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Puzzle Link-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>aa331c8e2948e6273cab97b329751a1f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47046">
		<path>./Renketsu Puzzle Tsunagete Pon! Color.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle Link</name>
		<desc>Puzzle Link is a game where blocks of matching color have to be dissolved. New blocks constantly scroll into the screen from the top. The game is over when the first blocks reach the bottom of the screen. You can dissolve blocks by shooting at them. The shots form a line where they impact. If that line connects otherwise unconnected blocks of the same color they will dissolve.

There are three different modes: In "Normal" you have to link two special blocks that appear after some time. If you manage to finish the level within the time limit you will unlock one of 50 collectible cards. In "Clear Mode" you have to clear a given constellation of blocks. "Battle Mode" is a two player link-cable mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/Renketsu Puzzle Tsunagete Pon! Color-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Renketsu Puzzle Tsunagete Pon! Color-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Renketsu Puzzle Tsunagete Pon! Color-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Renketsu Puzzle Tsunagete Pon! Color-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>72119f96aa1ebd5a01562b0395089bcf</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87590">
		<path>./Rockman Battle &amp; Fighters.zip</path>
		<name>RockMan Battle &amp; Fighters</name>
		<desc>Rockman Battle &amp; Fighters is a fighting game similar to the two arcade titles Mega Man: The Power Battle, and Mega Man 2: The Power Fighters. 
Playing as one of four characters (Mega Man, Proto Man, Bass, and Duo), the player chooses between three sets of boss battles with various Robot Masters from the series.
The battles are fought linearly in any order, and after each boss is defeated, a special weapon is added to the player's arsenal. 
Each boss is weak to one specific weapon, so the player is encouraged to strategize the order in which the bosses are faced. 
Two players can use a link cable to transfer database information between systems, but no co-op or versus play is supported.</desc>
		<image>./images/Rockman Battle &amp; Fighters-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Rockman Battle &amp; Fighters-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Rockman Battle &amp; Fighters-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rockman Battle &amp; Fighters-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Rockman Battle &amp; Fighters-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000706T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>9cb0aaf4104e370efbc8b55ee04733dc</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47048">
		<path>./Samurai Shodown! II.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown II</name>
		<desc>One of SNK's legendary fighting game series has made a return! In Samurai Shodown II, you can take on one of the roles of 15 warriors as you fight your way through the land to defeat the evil Mizuki! Slash, kick, and slice your opponents in half...do whatever it takes...live by the sword, and die by its blade.</desc>
		<image>./images/Samurai Shodown! II-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Samurai Shodown! II-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Samurai Shodown! II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Samurai Shodown! II-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>3e46575450756953d755c23db12c4dd0</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47049">
		<path>./Shanghai Mini.zip</path>
		<name>Shanghai Mini</name>
		<desc>Shanghai Mini is a release for one more platform in the for ever continuing series of Activision's tile matching game. 

Included are classic, tournament and dynasty modes. Classic is normal game with six different board layouts. In tournament game player challenges the Tower of Shanghai and tries to beat the Shanghai Master by solving different board layouts within time limit. Dynasty is two player competition - against computer or human (requires link cable) opponent.</desc>
		<image>./images/Shanghai Mini-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Shanghai Mini-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Shanghai Mini-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shanghai Mini-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>7c262a2c6390445170d0bf83290c939c</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47032">
		<path>./Shinki Sekai Evolution - Hateshinai Dungeon.zip</path>
		<name>Evolution: Eternal Dungeon</name>
		<desc>A portable version of Evolution: The World of Sacred Device. Eternal Dungeon tells the story of the young explorer Mag Launcher and his quest for the fabled Evolutia, an item of immense power.

The basic premise of the game is to take quests in the town and then assemble your party and attempt to clear out the many dungeons in the game, grinding your characters and getting the loot and experience needed to advance the plot and buy items, equipment, and upgrades for your Cy-frame, a robotic attachment that enables Mag to enhance his combat abilities.

As expected for a portable version, the gameplay has been significantly downgraded from its original Dreamcast version. Town navigation is menu-driven and all graphics are now top-down 2D sprites, with all dungeons being pre-designed instead of randomly generated. Combat is turn-based using a menu system from which you select your actions for each party member (up to 3) and execute them, but otherwise remains unchanged.</desc>
		<image>./images/Shinki Sekai Evolution - Hateshinai Dungeon-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Shinki Sekai Evolution - Hateshinai Dungeon-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Shinki Sekai Evolution - Hateshinai Dungeon-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shinki Sekai Evolution - Hateshinai Dungeon-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>3ab7276071d35cd11f316b6b936cee38</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87592">
		<path>./Shougi no Tatsujin Color.zip</path>
		<name>Shougi No Tatsujin Color</name>
		<desc>Neo Geo Pocket version of "Master of Shogi". You can play against 8 unique characters, and you can choose from 3 levels: beginner, intermediate, and advanced.</desc>
		<image>./images/Shougi no Tatsujin Color-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Shougi no Tatsujin Color-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Shougi no Tatsujin Color-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shougi no Tatsujin Color-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19990319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<genre>Asiatic board game / Shougi</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>a874c1d95bade2143c0712d22ddbd452</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47050">
		<path>./SNK Gals Fighters.zip</path>
		<name>SNK Gals Fighters</name>
		<desc>Organized and sponsored by a mysterious fighter nicknamed as "Miss X", the first Queen of Fighters Tournament is officially open, but this competition differs of the others for allowing ONLY women as participants. Meanwhile, after have passed for several and tough fights (including a final showdown with Miss X), the winner will be rewarded with a mystical artifact known as the "K Talisman", that has the capacity to grant any wish. With this rare-unique possibility of accomplish their pessoal dreams and ambitions, 8 powerful femme fatale fighters were invited to face the biggest combat of their lives...

Behind this simple storyline, the title brings a cast of 8 all-female characters taken from SNK's fighting series The King of Fighters (Mai Shiranui, Yuri Sakazaki, Athena Asamiya, Leona Heidern, Shermie), The Last Blade (Akari Ichijyou) and Samurai Shodown (Shiki, Nakoruru); all with the same blows (parodied or not) of their origin games.

The gameplay is identical to KOF's Advanced Mode (e.g. Emergency Evasion and Run commands), but without SDMs. To increase the replay factor, a power-up mode was included: depending on your combat performance, you'll be favored with several random items (e.g. Start with full MAX gauge, Speed Up etc.) that can be used to improve your character for a while.</desc>
		<image>./images/SNK Gals Fighters-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/SNK Gals Fighters-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SNK Gals Fighters-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SNK Gals Fighters-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>08922d2bdc6c80d56ddf50836ccad77c</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47051">
		<path>./SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - Capcom Version.zip</path>
		<name>SNK vs. Capcom : Card Fighters Clash - Capcom Version</name>
		<desc>Compete in the SC Card Fighters' Clash tournament with your Capcom deck in this NGPC card game. Collect the 300 cards from both SNK and Capcom franchises and duel and trade with your friends using the extensive link mode. With mechanics similar to CCGs such as Yu-Gi-Oh and popular characters from both SNK and Capcom, Card Fighters clash offers both collection and strategy gameplay. This game also allows linking with SNK vs. Capcom: Match of the Millennium to transfer collectible points.</desc>
		<image>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - Capcom Version-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - Capcom Version-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - Capcom Version-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - Capcom Version-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>3bcc1c9ef59a75e3c2e6b49be6b84bab</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47052">
		<path>./SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - SNK Version.zip</path>
		<name>SNK vs. Capcom : Card Fighter's Clash - SNK Version</name>
		<desc>Compete in the SC Card Fighters' Clash tournament with your SNK deck in this NGPC card game. Collect the 300 cards from both SNK and Capcom franchises and duel and trade with your friends using the extensive link mode. With mechanics similar to CCGs such as Yu-Gi-Oh and popular characters from both SNK and Capcom, Card Fighters clash offers both collection and strategy gameplay. This game also allows linking with SNK vs. Capcom: Match of the Millennium to transfer collectible points.</desc>
		<image>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - SNK Version-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - SNK Version-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - SNK Version-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash I - SNK Version-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>74e8381e94565e21a3197449bb4423bf</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87593">
		<path>./SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash II.zip</path>
		<name>Snk Vs. Capcom - Card Fighters 2 - Expand Edition</name>
		<desc>SNK vs. Capcom: Card Fighter's Clash 2 Expand Edition continues the mascot packed trading card game action that began with the original.</desc>
		<image>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash II-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash II-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash II-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Card Fighters Clash II-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Playing cards</genre>
		<family>SNK Vs. Capcom</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>b2628da96bf4f278b13d3c5afd703ac7</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47053">
		<path>./SNK vs Capcom - Match Of The Millennium.zip</path>
		<name>SNK vs. Capcom : The Match of the Millennium</name>
		<desc>With 18 starting characters (26 total after unlocking), numerous battle modes and varied minigames, this may be the largest fighting game for the Neo Geo Pocket Color. Choose the fighting style that suits you from the available Single, Tag and Team modes. The SC Olympic mode grants access to minigames from a music game featuring Felicia to a whack-a-mole style game with Jubei. The Olympic mode also allows players to compete for gold, silver and bronze medals in various fighting challenges. Link features include NGPC-to-NGPC battles and NGPC-to-Dreamcast data exchange with other SNK titles.</desc>
		<image>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Match Of The Millennium-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/SNK vs Capcom - Match Of The Millennium-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Match Of The Millennium-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SNK vs Capcom - Match Of The Millennium-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>9a1e73255cd761747508e24d60b2db07</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47054">
		<path>./Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog : Pocket Adventure</name>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure, or Sonic Pocket Adventure for short, is a 1999 platform video game in the Sonic the Hedgehog series developed by SNK. It was released in December 1999 in North America, and May 2000 in Japan, exclusively for the Neo Geo Pocket Color handheld game console. It is also only the second game of the Sonic series ever to be released on a non-Sega video game console, the first being Sonic Jam on the Game.com. The game was praised by critics, receiving perfect scores from multiple reviews.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Sonic</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>b8a899ae2b0f1dfa0db5417de745a51e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87596">
		<path>./Soreike!! Hanafuda Doujou.zip</path>
		<name>Soreike!! Hanafuda Doujou</name>
		<desc>This software allows players to enjoy the game of Hanafuda (Japanese playing cards) "Koi Koi," with a "Tournament" mode in which players aim to win against nine other players, a "Battle Mode" in which players enjoy a game of "Sashi," and a "Certification Mode" in which they are judged on their abilities.</desc>
		<image>./images/Soreike!! Hanafuda Doujou-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Soreike!! Hanafuda Doujou-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Soreike!! Hanafuda Doujou-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Soreike!! Hanafuda Doujou-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19991216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dyna Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Dyna</publisher>
		<genre>Asiatic board game / Hanafuda</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>8b12fec8e96dad41380ab419a216ad08</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87597">
		<path>./Super Real Mahjong - Premium Collection.zip</path>
		<name>Super Real Mahjong - Premium Collection</name>
		<desc>Super Real Mahjong Premium Collection is the first portable installment of the Super Real Mahjong series. As usual, you play strip mahjong with pretty girls, this time several from many of the games. However, due to system limitations, only some strip scenes are animated. It also has some visual novel-like qualities, in particular a story mode where you try to focus on one girl each time the game is played. This is accomplished by choosing the right options when presented to you. If you manage to focus on a single girl, her CG is unlocked in the gallery.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Real Mahjong - Premium Collection-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Real Mahjong - Premium Collection-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Real Mahjong - Premium Collection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Real Mahjong - Premium Collection-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SETA Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SETA Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Asiatic board game / Mahjong</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>07873a332ef8ac5cb5177ee3c304ff2b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47047">
		<path>./Tsunagete Pon! 2.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle Link 2</name>
		<desc>The gameplay of Puzzle Link 2 is generally identical to the first game: Puzzle Link is a game where blocks of matching color have to be dissolved. New blocks constantly scroll into the screen from the top. The game is over when the first blocks reach the bottom of the screen. You can dissolve blocks by shooting at them. The shots form a line where they impact. If that line connects otherwise unconnected blocks of the same color they will dissolve.

There are new modes in Puzzle Link 2. Like the original, there are the standard challenge and puzzle rounds. But new to the series is the marathon-style game where you continue eliminating pieces as the game gradually increases speed. In this mode, more power-ups appear as the player performs faster. Here, you get three shots that will eliminate the same color tile from the board. The game also has link cable support for two players.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tsunagete Pon! 2-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Tsunagete Pon! 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Tsunagete Pon! 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tsunagete Pon! 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>2a8f9cb76e56000769e08200d8b25182</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47031">
		<path>./Dive Alert - Becky's Version.zip</path>
		<name>Dive Alert : Becky's Version</name>
		<desc>Dive Alert: Becky's Version is an RPG for the Neo Geo Pocket Color. There is another version of Dive Alert called Dive Alert: Matt's Version. The two games are rather like joint Pokemon releases (Red/Blue, etc) wherein they are overall the same game with a variety of smaller differences.

The player takes control of a character named Becky. The game takes place in the future and the world is primarily surrounded by water. The only land is a small patch called Terra. The player must prove their worth to be accepted on to Terra by proving their skill as a submarine commander and destroying enemy vessels.

Becky's version features different characters, items and boats from Matt's Version. These are logged in a device similar to a Pokédex (from Pokemon). Battles take place against enemy ships and a radar view is used to help the player guide torpedoes towards the enemy vessels. Much of the game is text-based with animated cutscenes. 

The game features the ability for two players to link up Neo Geo Pocket Color units to exchanges ships and data, and to battle one on one.  The game also features battery back-up and a training mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dive Alert - Becky's Version-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dive Alert - Becky's Version-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dive Alert - Becky's Version-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dive Alert - Becky's Version-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20000416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sacnoth</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>c148b30103de704eeed63dfe7a7d6100</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47064">
		<path>./Last Blade.zip</path>
		<name>The Last Blade : Beyond the Destiny</name>
		<desc>1863. History's hidden secret is revealed. During the age known as "Bakumatsu", 135 years ago, chaos rules! It's all yours: A new type of weapon fighting game in which Power and Speed weapons, in addition to various Repel moves can be used to experience a new sensation in video game thrills!</desc>
		<image>./images/Last Blade-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Last Blade-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Last Blade-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Last Blade-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>83fa4cb3c629aa57c12f9cec52c5a53d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87571">
		<path>./Nigeronpa.zip</path>
		<name>Nigeronpa</name>
		<desc>A simple handheld RPG mostly made up of side- and fetch quests. As you move through the game you can recruit friends and receive various licenses that function similar to jobs, that allow you to perform more powerful skills and magic attacks.</desc>
		<image>./images/Nigeronpa-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Nigeronpa-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Nigeronpa-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Nigeronpa-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20001123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dennou Eizou</developer>
		<publisher>Dennou Eizou</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>9c73091689138179323ff48b279f8b1e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="87584">
		<path>./Pocket Reversi.zip</path>
		<name>Pocket Reversi</name>
		<desc>Pocket Reversi is an adaptation by Success of the classic strategy game. In single-player, you must make your way through Tournament Mode, competing against eight progressively difficult opponents. You can also take the 'Ability Level Test' which grades you based on your play. For beginners, 'Reversi Lesson' provides ten short tutorial sessions to teach you the basics of the game. There's also a 'Free Play' mode where you can choose to see all available moves and to even take back your last move. Finally, there's a two-player mode accessible via the link cable.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pocket Reversi-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Pocket Reversi-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pocket Reversi-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pocket Reversi-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20000127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>50db2d67493cc92fa382a3f9cb16905c</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T161221" />
	</game>
	<game id="47028">
		<path>./Dark Arms - Beast Buster.zip</path>
		<name>Dark Arms : Beast Buster 1999</name>
		<desc>Dark Arms: Beast Buster 1999 is a RPG for the Neo Geo Pocket Color. It's a spin-off from the arcade game Beast Busters.

Parallel to our world we find the Dark Realm. As the player, you find access to this parallel dimension after signing a pact with the Master of the Dark Realm. In his realm, you are supposed to catch monsters. These can be fed to your biological weapons: Dark Arms. You weapons gain abilities from consumed monsters and can evolve into more powerful equipment. You can also find seeds in the Dark Realm that turn into new weapons.

The game features puzzles that have to be solved and a wide array of undead monsters that can be fed to your Dark Arms.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dark Arms - Beast Buster-image.jpg</image>
		<video>./videos/Dark Arms - Beast Buster-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dark Arms - Beast Buster-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dark Arms - Beast Buster-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T134207</lastplayed>
		<md5>fe0e58d34d650ae5174ca03d3efc67b0</md5>
		<gametime>25</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160818" />
	</game>
	<game id="124419">
		<path>./Another Day in Hell.zip</path>
		<name>Another Day in Hell</name>
		<image>./images/Another Day in Hell-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20050101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Iceman - Thor</publisher>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T134134</lastplayed>
		<md5>d94ea11f58b307d39ebafd7ce661b5e1</md5>
		<gametime>34</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T160757" />
	</game>
</gameList>
