<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./galaxy keiji gayvan.chd</path>
		<name>Galaxy Keiji Gayvan</name>
		<desc>Galaxy Deka Gayvan est un beat'em up. Vous incarnez seul ou à deux joueur Hiro et Michiko,, deux agents envoyés pour éliminer le criminel Ballas qui menace la paix sur terre.

Au fil du jeu, vous accumulez de l'énergie qui permet de se transformer en super héros (Gayvan et Mittchi). Ils deviennent alors plus fort et ont accès à de nouveaux coups spéciaux.

Un mode VS est également disponible.</desc>
		<image>./images/galaxy keiji gayvan-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/galaxy keiji gayvan-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/galaxy keiji gayvan-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/galaxy keiji gayvan-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fill in Café Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Intec Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./star parodia.chd</path>
		<name>Fantasy Star Soldier</name>
		<desc>Fantasy Star Soldier est la version US de l'excellent shmup Star Parodier. Cette version, bien que finalisée, n'est jamais sortie. Le jeu est parfaitement jouable.</desc>
		<image>./images/star parodia-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/star parodia-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/star parodia-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/star parodia-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inter State</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200307T230755</lastplayed>
		<gametime>201</gametime>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chou Aniki - Super Big Brothers (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Cho Aniki - Super Big Brothers</name>
		<desc>Dans Cho Aniki : Super Big Brothers sur Turbografx, le joueur contrôle Idaten ou Benten, deux guerriers célestes qui luttent pour mettre un terme au règne tyrannique de l'empereur Constructeur. Aidés par les robustes Adon et Samson, les deux guerriers ont pour mission de défaire l'armée impériale au fil des cinq niveaux proposés.</desc>
		<image>./images/Chou Aniki - Super Big Brothers (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Chou Aniki - Super Big Brothers (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Chou Aniki - Super Big Brothers (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chou Aniki - Super Big Brothers (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19921225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajou_Dracula_X_-_Chi_no_Rinne.chd</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Rondo of Blood</name>
		<desc>Castlevania : Rondo of Blood sur TurboGraphx CD est un jeu d'aventure/action dans lequel vous incarnez Richter Belmont qui part au secours de sa fiancée enlevée par Dracula. Au fil des niveaux, vous rencontrez de viles créatures et vous devez vous servir de votre précieux fouet pour les vaincre. Mais attention, à la fin de chaque niveau un boss vous attend. Un bon timing et de bons réflexes ne seront pas de trop pour en venir à bout.</desc>
		<image>./images/Akumajou_Dracula_X_-_Chi_no_Rinne-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Akumajou_Dracula_X_-_Chi_no_Rinne-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Akumajou_Dracula_X_-_Chi_no_Rinne-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Akumajou_Dracula_X_-_Chi_no_Rinne-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Plateforme</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./crest of wolf.chd</path>
		<name>crest of wolf</name>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./rainbow islands.chd</path>
		<name>Rainbow Islands</name>
		<desc>Ultra cute sequel to Bubble Bobble. Work your way up each level by jumping platforms and throwing out rainbows. You can collapse your rainbows by jumping on them from above, allowing you to destroy any enemies trapped underneath, or you can shoot them directly at anything heading your way. The rainbows can be powered up to shoot three at a time and are essential to use as temporary platforms to progress up the level.</desc>
		<image>./images/rainbow islands-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/rainbow islands-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19930630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC AVENUE</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kaze kiri ninja action.chd</path>
		<name>Kaze Kiri: Ninja Action</name>
		<desc>Kaze Kiri takes place in Feudal Japan where the kingdom princess Shizuhime is abducted by a group of mysterious ninjas. A feared swordsman called Kaze Kiri, hero of the game, is given the task to rescue the poor girl and restore order. Our ninja can can use a broad variety of fightings skills - he can run, jump, dash and slash without mercy anyone who gets in his way.</desc>
		<image>./images/kaze kiri ninja action-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/kaze kiri ninja action-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19940428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NAXAT Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gate of thunder.chd</path>
		<name>Gate of Thunder</name>
		<desc>Aries was a peaceful and calm planet for millennia; however, it is now faced with its worst crisis. The deadly army of Obellon fighters led by General Don Jingi, the evil merchant known to do anything for personal gain, is out to steal the “Starlight,” a powerful source of energy that could destroy the universe if misused. You must properly guide the “Hunting Dog” fighter-plane along with Hawk and Esty (special undercover agents protecting the Galaxy) to destroy Obellon before they destroy the world. 

You are the last resort of our planet.</desc>
		<image>./images/gate of thunder-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/gate of thunder-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc., Red Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type Complete (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>R-Type Complete CD</name>
		<desc>This CD combines both HuCards into the complete game, as it originally should have been. There are some added visual scenes to justify the CD format, as well as re-arranged music tracks for each level.</desc>
		<image>./images/R-Type Complete (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/R-Type Complete (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem Corp.</developer>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./seirei senshi spriggan.chd</path>
		<name>SEIREI SENSHI SPRIGGAN</name>
		<desc>Take on the alien hordes in this vertically scrolling shoot 'em up from the people behind Aleste. The power-up system in Spriggan relies on different coloured globes - you can have three of these in stock at any one time and the order they are in will vary what style of weapon you have. This allows for a certain degree of mix-and-match until you find your preferred combination. You can also eject these orbs, which act as a smart bomb in times of need.</desc>
		<image>./images/seirei senshi spriggan-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/seirei senshi spriggan-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./faussette amour.chd</path>
		<name>Fausetté amour</name>
		<desc>This is the adventures of Koruku Ransu, a young blue-haired warrior. The evil lord Goat Bone has kidnaped her beloved sister and also controls the minds of most of her best friends. Koruku wears a strong pink armor  Through seven long stages, one of Kokuru's friend awaits at the end of each one of them - however, she will have to defeat their dark side first and free their controlled minds.</desc>
		<image>./images/faussette amour-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/faussette amour-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AIM</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ginga Fukei Densetsu - Sapphire (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Ginga Fukei Densetsu Sapphire</name>
		<desc>Join the four girls pilots part of a futuristic police unit called the Burning Rabbits. Their duty is to go after bandits, to explore the far corners of the universe and to even venture back in time, whatever the risks, to prosecute the worst criminals. Because humanity is now advanced enough to travel through time, this special police force was created to protect society from these new "time criminals". You have four spaceships, to choose from. Each one balances out the next and usually trades off fire power for maneuverability and speed.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ginga Fukei Densetsu - Sapphire (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ginga Fukei Densetsu - Sapphire (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19951124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CAProductions Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./cd denjin rockabilly tengoku.chd</path>
		<name>Super Air Zonk</name>
		<desc>Zonk is back in Super Air Zonk!!

Now moving to a rockabilly beat and able to transform into nine different characters, Zonk lets loose through seven action-packed stages in another battle against his arch nemesis, Sandro Vitch. Power up Zonk with the classic Meat item, eventually turning him into the champion of justice, Ultra Zonk, or the fearsome Tyrano Zonk in the latter stages of the game.
Read More&gt;&gt;

After rescuing his friends from enemies, Zonk can also morph with them to combine powers. Fight enemies with killer tunes belted out from a trusty microphone. Hurl freshly made sushi at them. With its variety of wacky attacks, Super Air Zonk has a sense of humor all its own.</desc>
		<image>./images/cd denjin rockabilly tengoku-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/cd denjin rockabilly tengoku-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19930730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dual</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ryuuko no ken.chd</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting</name>
		<desc>A conversion of the 1992 Neo Geo game, Art of Fighting is based around two main characters - Ryo Sakazaki and Robert Garcia who set out to find Ryo's kindapped sister. Gameplay consists of standard 3 rounds one-on-one beat 'em up action with a spirit gauge that is combo charged for special attack power (think Street Fighter II's Had?ken). Every couple of stages you also get the chance to increase your stats a little by playing one of three mini games. These are fairly simple and usually involve a bit of timing or button bashing.</desc>
		<image>./images/ryuuko no ken-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/ryuuko no ken-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19940326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Psychic Storm (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Psychic Storm</name>
		<image>./images/Psychic Storm (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Psychic Storm (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alfa System</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet Japan Co., Ltd., Lasersoft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valis IV (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Valis IV</name>
		<desc>Yuko has become the goddess of the world of Vecanti and has watched over the world in peace since the defeat of Glames. Trouble brews when the Dark World prince named Galgear begins to search for a magical ring. This ring increases his powers, but to the loss of control he could have maintained under its effects, and the gods of Vecanti recognize this and imprison Galgear inside a crystal sunk into the ocean.

Fifteen years pass, and Galgear manages to break out of his prison, kidnapping the former heroine Valna and being pursued by troops led by Cham as a result. A member of her band, named Lena Brande, requests permission to infiltrate Galgear's stronghold and free Valna.</desc>
		<image>./images/Valis IV (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Valis IV (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet Japan Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pop n magic.chd</path>
		<name>Pop 'n Magic</name>
		<desc>A static screen action game in the style of Bubble Bobble or Don Doko Don, Pop 'n Magic allows you to trap enemies by firing your wand at them, then pick them up and throw them across the screen to destroy them. The bubbles they are trapped in are specific colours and care must be taken not to throw two of the same colour together as this will release the (now quite upset) creatures inside.</desc>
		<image>./images/pop n magic-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/pop n magic-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920727T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Riot</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet Japan Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Snatcher_(NTSC-J)_[KMCD2002].iso</path>
		<name>Snatcher</name>
		<desc>Snatcher CD-ROMantic is an Adventure game, developed and published by Konami, which was released in Japan in 1992.  A cyber punk adventure.</desc>
		<image>./images/Snatcher_(NTSC-J)_[KMCD2002]-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Snatcher_(NTSC-J)_[KMCD2002]-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19921023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kiaidan 00.chd</path>
		<name>Kiaidan 00</name>
		<desc>Year 20XX. Mad Scientist Dr. Gigaga's world conquest Operation has begun. The armored beast army that he created attacks humanity when he seizes the earth!! However, God did not abandon humanity. The super robot Kiaidan 00 created by Dr. Sakura, a genius scientist who escaped from Giga ga ! And the son of Dr. Sakura, the pilot of Kiaidan 00, Takeshi Sakura! The future of humanity is entrusted to them.</desc>
		<image>./images/kiaidan 00-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/kiaidan 00-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19921023T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Riot</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Darius 2 (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Super Darius</name>
		<desc>Super Darius is a 1990 port of Darius for the PC Engine CD-ROM², and the only attempt at an accurate port of the game for many years; it even uses recordings of music and sound effects straight from the PCB! Its other claim to fame is the introduction of all 26 bosses from the original draft for Darius, some of which were earlier seen on promotional material and some of which were used in Darius II instead.

A "light" version for normal PC Engines, Darius Plus, was released later in the year. At the time that was released, owning both versions allowed you to get Darius Alpha.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Darius 2 (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Darius 2 (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>NEC Avenue, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AKUMAJOU DRACULA X - CHI NO RONDO.cue</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Rondo of Blood</name>
		<desc>Castlevania: Rondo of Blood is the first CD game in the series, which allowed for more features to be included, such as CD quality soundtrack and visual cut-scenes. The opening, ending, and various cutscenes done in a hand-drawn visual style are included in the game. However, at the time this wasn't considered to be a very popular decision. Various details in the terrain are more polished than previous entries, and the behavior of the enemies is more elaborate. For example, the boss characters in the game will perform an unique final attack when their health meter is depleted. If the player didn't sustain any damage during the fight and manages to avoid this attack, a "Perfect Bonus" (1UP) is obtained.
The mechanic of picking upgrades in order to power up the whip, which until that time was a staple of the series, has been removed. A new feature is the Item Crash, a special sub-weapon attack during which the player becomes momentarily invincible and a powerful attack is performed, at the expense of a large amount of hearts. Similar to Castlevania III: Dracula's Curse, a branching path system has been implemented, but with some differences. Unlike the former, it's not possible to choose between two paths in between stages. Rather, there are two ways to proceed through a stage, one of the paths being hidden. Finding this path requires several tricks such as destroying a wall, deliberately falling down a pit, and so on. In addition, there are four characters who have been kidnapped by Dracula and require to be rescued. One of these characters, Maria, becomes playable after being rescued. She attacks with magical, whimsical skills, such as throwing doves at enemies, hiding in a turtle shell, and other animal based attacks. When playing as Maria, the cutscenes when rescuing the other characters, the conversation with Dracula, the ending, the player's defeat sequence, as well as the Game Over screen become more light-hearted in tone.
Once a stage is cleared, it can be selected from the "STAGE SELECT" in the file screen at the start of the game. Choosing "PLAYER SELECT" allows switching to Maria. Other things which are displayed are the completion percentage, the amount of continues left, "SOUND TEST", and "TECHNIQUE". The latter are videos which show the correct strategy to use against bosses. These videos can be unlocked by collecting certain amounts of money.</desc>
		<image>./images/AKUMAJOU DRACULA X - CHI NO RONDO-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/AKUMAJOU DRACULA X - CHI NO RONDO-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200914T035547</lastplayed>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ai Chou Aniki (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Ai Cho Aniki</name>
		<desc>Bo Emperor Conshyasu raise the Neo Builder Army to fight Idaten and Benten. However, the two fall in love and elope. This leaves Samson and Adon to fight the new threat, Su Emperor Roido!</desc>
		<image>./images/Ai Chou Aniki (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ai Chou Aniki (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya</developer>
		<publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kaizou choujin shubibinman 3 kai no princess.chd</path>
		<name>Kaizou Choujin Shubibinman 3: Ikai no Princess</name>
		<desc>Tasuke and Kyapiko are spending a nice relaxing day at the beach, when suddenly a huge spaceship appears overhead! This can only mean one thing... another invasion! Tasuke and Kyapiko suit up and set out to stop it... or is it all just a gross misunderstanding?</desc>
		<image>./images/kaizou choujin shubibinman 3 kai no princess-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/kaizou choujin shubibinman 3 kai no princess-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya</developer>
		<publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./super air zonk.chd</path>
		<name>Super Air Zonk</name>
		<desc>Zonk is back in Super Air Zonk!!

Now moving to a rockabilly beat and able to transform into nine different characters, Zonk lets loose through seven action-packed stages in another battle against his arch nemesis, Sandro Vitch. Power up Zonk with the classic Meat item, eventually turning him into the champion of justice, Ultra Zonk, or the fearsome Tyrano Zonk in the latter stages of the game.
Read More&gt;&gt;

After rescuing his friends from enemies, Zonk can also morph with them to combine powers. Fight enemies with killer tunes belted out from a trusty microphone. Hurl freshly made sushi at them. With its variety of wacky attacks, Super Air Zonk has a sense of humor all its own.</desc>
		<image>./images/super air zonk-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/super air zonk-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19930730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dual</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./space fantasy zone.chd</path>
		<name>Space Fantasy Zone</name>
		<desc>Take the graphics from Fantasy Zone and the gameplay from Space Harrier, mix them together and you get Space Fantasy Zone. This unreleased game has the basis of its gameplay in Space Harrier, but with some differences - you have an energy meter instead of one-hit-kills and you can upgrade your weaponry between levels in a shop.</desc>
		<image>./images/space fantasy zone-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/space fantasy zone-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC AVENUE</developer>
		<publisher>NEC Avenue, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon 2 - The Revenge (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Double Dragon II: The Revenge</name>
		<desc>In the year 2000,  A nuclear strike has left New York City in disaster and law and order have taken a backseat to crime and violence.  One of the most powerful crime syndicate in New York is called the Gen-Satsu-Ken, a mysterious organization led by a mysterious warrior who is a master in a wicked style of Kung Fu.  However two young men named Billy and Jimmy, masters of a martial art called the Sou-Setsu-Ken, were brave enough to challenge them.  One day, during a Gen-Satsu-Ken attack, Billy's girlfriend, Marian, is murdered by the Gen-Satsu-Ken. Billy and Jimmy swore revenge by taking down the Gen-Satsu-Ken once and for all.</desc>
		<image>./images/Double Dragon 2 - The Revenge (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Double Dragon 2 - The Revenge (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19930312T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NAXAT Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sylphia (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Sylphia</name>
		<desc>Sylphia is a vertical shooter published by Tonkin House. The game draws from Greek mythology and tells the story of Sylphia, a female warrior with a tragic destiny. Her tale starts as she lays fatally wounded in the temple of Athena - merciless monsters have taken over the city and she perished as she desperately tried to protect innocent villagers. The gods, touched by the sincerity of the young woman's devotion and love, decide to give Sylphia another chance... Now turned into a Sylphid with tremendous powers, the female warrior embarks on a long journey of revenge, ready to fight for her homeland. Sylphia starts equipped with a fairly basic fire weapon that can be upgraded in various ways - four different types based on the four basic elements are available throughout the game, from Fire (Red), Air (Green), Water (Blue) and Earth (Brown). Each weapon type is associated with an additional sub-weapon which range from Homing Fireballs (Red), Reverse Fire (Blue), Ring Blades (Green) and Rotating Rocks (Brown). Sylphia can also trigger a devastative special attack that deals great damage to on-screen enemies - this power is obviously available in limited quantities and may only be be used in desperate situations. Various other items are available for the taking, such as extra lives, Mirrors/Gems (slowly increase a health bar located at the bottom of the screen that gives the player an extra life when full) and Green Orbs (increase the active weapon's power level). Sylphia consists of eight stages and is single player only.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sylphia (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sylphia (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19931022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tonkin House</developer>
		<publisher>Tokyo Shoseki Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zero Wing (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Zero Wing</name>
		<desc>Horizontal shoot 'em up where you can suck in enemy craft and either use them as a shield or fire them off for extra damage.</desc>
		<image>./images/Zero Wing (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Zero Wing (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayxanber III (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Rayxanber III</name>
		<desc>RayXanbeR III is an Action game, developed and published by DataWest, which was released in Japan in 1992.</desc>
		<image>./images/Rayxanber III (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rayxanber III (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DataWest</developer>
		<publisher>DataWest</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Forgotten Worlds [U][SCD][TGXCD1030][Capcom][1992][PCE][aguichor].chd</path>
		<name>Forgotten Worlds</name>
		<desc>The Turbografx-16 version of the arcade smash.

It was released as a Super CD-ROM² title which supported a specialized 3-button controller that NEC released only in Japan. An American version for the TurboGrafx 16 was released by Turbo Technologies Inc. as well. With the 3-button controller, the player can control their character as they would in the Mega Drive version, with two buttons to rotate the character and one to shoot. 

With the standard TurboGrafx-16 controller, the Run button is used in the place of the third button to rotate the character to the left. The TurboGrafx-16 is one-player only, but allows the player to select between either of the two Unknown Soldiers at the start of the game (with their respective abilities from the arcade version retained).</desc>
		<image>./images/Forgotten Worlds [U][SCD][TGXCD1030][Capcom][1992][PCE][aguichor]-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Forgotten Worlds [U][SCD][TGXCD1030][Capcom][1992][PCE][aguichor]-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920327T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC</developer>
		<publisher>NEC Home Electronics, Ltd.</publisher>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200306T060427</lastplayed>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nexzr (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Nexzr</name>
		<desc>Space based vertically scrolling shoot ‘em up, similar in style to Super Star Solider, but far more challenging.</desc>
		<image>./images/Nexzr (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Nexzr (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19921211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NAXAT Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./download 2.chd</path>
		<name>DOWNLOAD 2</name>
		<desc>Shoot 'em up sequel that takes place over a series of very different and sometimes surreal landscapes.

Cheats/tips: CONFIG MODE: On the title screen push SELECT, I, II, I, II, I, II, I, II, I, II, SELECT
ALTERNATE GRAPHICS: From config mode, go to the DEMO section and watch the ending (9?). When the NEC Avenue logo appears, press UP, SELECT, II then RUN. When the game starts you should see the enemy and some background object replaced by slightly silly things (look out for Ultraman).</desc>
		<image>./images/download 2-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/download 2-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>nec adventure</developer>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dynastic hero.chd</path>
		<name>Dynastic Hero</name>
		<desc>The land of Tarron is under siege and you must save it from the wicked Drillkor Empire. A beautiful guide will help you along the way as only you, The Dynastic Hero, can deliver the goods!</desc>
		<image>./images/dynastic hero-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/dynastic hero-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19940520T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Raiden (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Super Raiden</name>
		<desc>A conversion of the classic arcade shoot 'em up, Raiden follows the conventions of the genre with coloured power up pods that give different weapons when collected. 

Raiden is one of the all-time greats in the annals of shoot 'em up history. It’s not just the excellent graphics and sounds, but the engaging gameplay that keeps you addicted for ages. It’s also capable of throwing up some hair-raising moments, and bullet dodging skills are pushed to the extreme</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Raiden (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Raiden (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Seibu Kaihatsu Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./flash hiders.chd</path>
		<name>Flash Hiders</name>
		<desc>A martial artist from the Wallace tribe named Bang Bipot and a temperamental sorceress named Tiria Rossette are on a trek across the world. The duo runs across and all but adopts Erue, an emotionally fragile young man somehow connected to an assortment of thugs, bounty hunters, and stranger things.</desc>
		<image>./images/flash hiders-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/flash hiders-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19931219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>RIGHT STUFF</developer>
		<publisher>Right Stuff</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chiki Chiki Boys (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Chiki Chiki Boys</name>
		<image>./images/Chiki Chiki Boys (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chiki Chiki Boys (Japan)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19940715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC AVENUE</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220921T215016</lastplayed>
		<gametime>39</gametime>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game id="106986">
		<path>./ane san.chd</path>
		<name>Ane-san</name>
		<desc>The two sisters, Ai and Yuuko, have taken different paths in life. Yuuko has been taken away by a mysterious gang. Ai is determined to save her from the clutches of crime. In a seemingly all-female city overrun by insane workers, biker gangs, and assorted criminals, Ai and her friends Chika and Makoto decide to work together in order to restore the world to normality again.

Ane-san is what is commonly called beat-'em-up, i.e. a fighting game that allows limited movement through side-scrolling environment. The player can choose to control a variety of female fighters. In the beginning, only Ai, Chika, and Makoto are selectable. Ai is the all-around balanced character, Chika is fast and fragile, while Makoto is very strong, but slow. Later in the game, other playable characters become available. Each fighter has a health points bar, which can be restored by healing items scattered through the levels. Once a character is dead, the player can continue playing with another one.

The player typically advances through side-scrolling stages, clearing each screen of enemies before being able to continue walking to the right. Each girl has the standard kicks, punches, and jumps at her disposal, as well as special moves, one per each girl. Stages culminate by boss battles (usually two per stage). 

Between the stages, the player can go shopping. A large variety of items is available, some enhancing the performance of the girls, but most purely for visual effect - the room the player views between the stages changes its appearance depending on the items the player has bought.

Also available between the stages (and as a separate gameplay mode, "vs.") is a mini-game, in which the player(s) have to rapidly press buttons in order to make the controllable girl execute a hideous grimace, that will surpass that of the opponent in ugliness and speed of execution.</desc>
		<image>./images/ane san-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/ane san-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/ane san-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/ane san-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200306T191133</lastplayed>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T122924" />
	</game>
</gameList>
