<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Burnout Legends (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl).iso</path>
		<name>Burnout Legends</name>
		<desc>The Burnout series goes portable with Burnout Legends for the PSP. You can play through redesigned tracks from the earlier Burnout games in nine different game modes, including Crash mode and Pursuit mode. Burnout Legends also contains new unlockable cars and content. You can challenge up to four other players to battle wirelessly in a single game or an entire customizable championship.</desc>
		<image>./images/Burnout Legends (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Burnout Legends (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20050913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200925T184319</lastplayed>
		<gametime>352</gametime>
		<lang>it,nl,es,de,en,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./God of War - Chains of Olympus.ISO</path>
		<name>God of War: Chains of Olympus</name>
		<desc>The game is set in Ancient Greece and loosely based on its mythology. The player controls Kratos, a Spartan warrior in the service of the Olympian Gods. Kratos is guided by the goddess Athena, who instructs him to find the Sun God Helios, as the Dream God Morpheus has caused the remaining gods to slumber in Helios' absence. With the power of the sun, Morpheus and Persephone, the Queen of the Underworld, with the aid of the Titan Atlas, intend to destroy the Pillar of the World and in turn Olympus. God of War: Chains of Olympus is chronologically the second chapter in the series, which focuses on vengeance as its central theme.</desc>
		<image>./images/God of War - Chains of Olympus-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/God of War - Chains of Olympus-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20080304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ready at Dawn</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200925T185239</lastplayed>
		<gametime>202</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken 6 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ru).iso</path>
		<name>Tekken 6</name>
		<desc>A must-have for Tekken aficionados, TEKKEN 6 sees the return of many familiar faces as well as new characters to create the largest line-up the series has ever seen. With a growing roster of fighters, each equipped with their own deadly techniques, moves and attack combinations, TEKKEN 6 will be the best King of Iron Fist Tournaments yet. Adding to the already rich gaming experience, a deeper character customization feature will only further enhance the incredible fighting intensity as players go mano-a-mano. Players can also take the battle online for classic match-ups and to compete for world domination.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tekken 6 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ru)-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tekken 6 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ru)-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20091124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>7</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200925T185653</lastplayed>
		<gametime>360</gametime>
		<lang>it,es,de,en,ru,fr</lang>
		<region>ru</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gran Turismo (Europe).iso</path>
		<name>Gran Turismo</name>
		<desc>The game is centered on an open-ended design. The single-player menu presents players with three variables ? Mode Selection (Time Trial, Single Race, and Drift Trial), Car Selection, and Track Selection. The player can pick and choose circuits and vehicles, with credits earned based on the difficulty, performance and number of laps they have chosen. Players can select from any number of laps, one to 99. There are 45 tracks (including layout variations) plus the added bonus of reverse on most tracks, which takes the track number close to 75. For the first time in the series, the game features the use of custom soundtracks that enables players to play their own songs while racing, but this option must first be unlocked by completing section B of the Driving Challenges. The music tracks can only be played if it is set on "MUSIC folder" and can be used for offline or online races.</desc>
		<image>./images/Gran Turismo (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Gran Turismo (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Gran Turismo (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20091001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polyphony Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200925T185910</lastplayed>
		<gametime>67</gametime>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninjamurai (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Ninjamurai</name>
		<image>./images/Ninjamurai (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Ninjamurai (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ninjamurai (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>Open Emotions</developer>
		<publisher>Open Emotions</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
		<md5>a6600f5bd97cfaa07b827d5990d1989d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Angry Birds (USA) (v2) (minis) (PSN).iso</path>
		<name>Angry Birds</name>
		<desc>The survival of the Angry Birds is at stake. Dish out revenge on the green pigs who stole the Birds' eggs. Use the unique destructive powers of the Angry Birds to lay waste to the pigs' fortified castles. Angry Birds features hours of gameplay, challenging physics-based castle demolition, and lots of replay value. Each of the 63 levels requires logic, skill, and brute force to crush the enemy.</desc>
		<image>./images/Angry Birds (USA) (v2) (minis) (PSN)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Angry Birds (USA) (v2) (minis) (PSN)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Angry Birds (USA) (v2) (minis) (PSN)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Rovio Mobile</developer>
		<publisher>Chillingo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris_USA.iso</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<desc>TETRIS? iconic blocky shapes are just as effective at occupying every spare thought when you?re not playing as they were when they debuted in 1984. As the times have changed, so too has TETRIS itself, becoming more visually striking while retaining that classic infectious gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tetris_USA-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Tetris_USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tetris_USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20090101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Impressionware</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Zombie Death (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Alien Zombie Death</name>
		<desc>Somewhere far far away in a random solar system, a lone space man dies... horribly. Take control of said fateful space man as he battles to his end against the dreaded Alien Zombies! Using a standard laser gun and a few pickups along the way, make sure you take out as many of those Alien Zombie suckers before they take you down. Its that simple. It's Alien Zombie Death.</desc>
		<image>./images/Alien Zombie Death (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Alien Zombie Death (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Alien Zombie Death (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20100325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PomPom Games</developer>
		<publisher>PomPom Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<md5>5842f37fee7c306c287e3f0d6307443c</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Speedball 2 - Evolution (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Speedball 2 Evolution</name>
		<desc>Various remakes of Speedball 2 have been released. Speedball 2100, released only for the PlayStation, is a 3D version of Speedball 2 with more options such as choosing and renaming any team, instead of having to play with Brutal Deluxe. This version, released in September 2000, failed to win over gamers and press because it lacked the speed and gameplay of the originals.[citation needed]

Empire Interactive released Speedball 2: Brutal Deluxe onto Xbox Live Arcade on October 17, 2007.[14] The game features a 3D graphics mode in addition to the "classic" visuals, as well as additional teams and online play.[15] According to statements by the Bitmap Brothers, this version of the game takes place in the 24th century. It was eventually delisted from Xbox Live Arcade, but people who have already downloaded it are still able to play it.

Frogster Interactive Pictures released a remake developed by Kylotonn, Speedball 2 Tournament onto Steam in November 2007.[16] In February 2011, Tower Studios released another updated version called Speedball 2: Evolution, developed by Vivid Games for iOS. The game features multiplayer support and achievements via Game Center.[17] It was also released for the PlayStation Portable and PlayStation 3.

A remake for the PC titled Speedball 2 HD was released December 5, 2013 on Steam. It's developed by Vivid Games and directed by Jon Hare.[18]</desc>
		<image>./images/Speedball 2 - Evolution (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Speedball 2 - Evolution (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Speedball 2 - Evolution (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>Tower Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Vivid Games</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players />
		<md5>af66719dcde9fc526e8a9a4fa829d04f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./I_Must_Run_PSN.iso</path>
		<name>I Must Run!</name>
		<desc>You have been convicted of a crime you didn't mean to commit. Your sentence was harsh despite the circumstances, and now you rot in jail. But those affected by your actions are not satisfied. Now, they are threatening to kill the one you love to exact revenge. And if you do not escape and reach the courthouse in 24 hours, she'll be gone. There are no other options. You must run.</desc>
		<image>./images/I_Must_Run_PSN-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/I_Must_Run_PSN-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/I_Must_Run_PSN-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20101214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gamelion Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Gamelion Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
		<md5>08fa10d296c1833e41c922ba595b3f7a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Out Run 2006 Coast 2 Coast.iso</path>
		<name>OutRun 2006 : Coast 2 Coast</name>
		<desc>OutRun 2006: Coast to Coast features a choice of 15 fully licensed Ferrari models, featuring the all-new F430 and F430 Spider, as well as the dazzling Superamerica and the stunning 550 Barchetta. Power your way across 15 new American themed environments from the "OutRun2 SP" arcade experience. Race from coast to glorious coast with a fresh new mission structure, a license mode and online play, with up to 6 players for a thrilling head-to-head journey.</desc>
		<image>./images/Out Run 2006 Coast 2 Coast-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Out Run 2006 Coast 2 Coast-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Out Run 2006 Coast 2 Coast-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Left to Die in Zombhai (Europe).cso</path>
		<name>Left To Die In Zombhai</name>
		<image>./images/Left to Die in Zombhai (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Left to Die in Zombhai (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Left to Die in Zombhai (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20110831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>iSquared Games</developer>
		<publisher>iSquared Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
		<md5>d494fb3f201fddc46510f4c1fa0fbf66</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Need For Speed Underground Rivals.cso</path>
		<name>Need for Speed : Underground Rivals</name>
		<desc>Customize 20 tuner cars and race on 10 new circuit tracks.

Eight modes including Drift Attack, and Rally Relay

Tune your ride performance and style

Special Features: 
   Wireless and Party Play Multiplayer Modes
   EAâ„¢ Pocket TRAX Music Visualization Player</desc>
		<image>./images/Need For Speed Underground Rivals-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Need For Speed Underground Rivals-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Need For Speed Underground Rivals-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="142898">
		<path>./Carol Vorderman Sudoku.iso</path>
		<name>Carol Vorderman Sudoku</name>
		<desc>Let the ultimate Sudoku expert, Carol Vorderman, show you how to play and conquer the number game phenomenon sweeping the world. With over 1 million puzzle boards to choose from, experience countless hours and hours of fun. Play a casual game, learn step-by-step strategies to play or even test your skills in head-to-head competitive matches. Play against a friend in exciting multi-player modes on the PlayStation and PSP system. Through it all, Carol will teach you how to hone your Sudoku skills and ultimately become a Sudoku Expert. Carol Vorderman's Sudoku features a game for every level Sudoku player with exciting features and challenges.</desc>
		<image>./images/Carol Vorderman Sudoku-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Carol Vorderman Sudoku-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Carol Vorderman Sudoku-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Carol Vorderman Sudoku-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>Atomic Planet Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153416" />
	</game>
	<game id="102316">
		<path>./Family Guy.iso</path>
		<name>Family Guy</name>
		<desc>This game is based on the animated television series Family Guy. It was also released for the PlayStation 2 and the original Xbox.

The game is split into 22 levels for the three playable characters: Peter, Stewie or Brian. Peter and Stewie have eight levels, while Brian has six. Each character has his own unique style of play.

A key feature of the game are mini-games done in the same style as the cutaway gags that the show is famous for, usually lasting less than 10 seconds. The mini-games often repeat cutaway gags from the shows, such as Peter inexplicably burning his hand in a waffle iron. Successfully completing the mini-game offers a bonus: Brian becomes invisible for a short period, while Peter and Stewie receive power-ups for their respective abilities.</desc>
		<image>./images/Family Guy-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Family Guy-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Family Guy-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Family Guy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Voltage Software</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153427" />
	</game>
	<game id="28293">
		<path>./Hot Shots Golf Open Tee.ISO</path>
		<name>Hot Shots Golf : Open Tee</name>
		<desc>Go golf crazy and take on a cast of colourful characters in the coolest clubhouse around. No need for airs and graces here - just select a golfer from a range of friendly faces, and customize their abilities, attributes and appearance before teeing off across a series of challenging courses and game modes. Go head-to-head with both friends and foes via WiFi compatible Ad Hoc Mode and become a true golfing legend.</desc>
		<image>./images/Hot Shots Golf Open Tee-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Hot Shots Golf Open Tee-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Hot Shots Golf Open Tee-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hot Shots Golf Open Tee-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clap Hanz</developer>
		<publisher>Clap Hanz</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Golf</genre>
		<family>Everybody's Golf</family>
		<players>8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153431" />
	</game>
	<game id="27873">
		<path>./Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles (Europe).iso</path>
		<name>Castlevania : The Dracula X Chronicles</name>
		<desc>Count Dracula has returned and captured the young woman close to the famous vampire hunter, Richter Belmont. Will Richter be able to defeat Dracula and rescue his girlfriend in this new 3D adventure for PSP?</desc>
		<image>./images/Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles (Europe)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles (Europe)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles (Europe)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles (Europe)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Castlevania</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200926T143800</lastplayed>
		<gametime>249</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153433" />
	</game>
	<game id="29180">
		<path>./Fly Fu (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Fly Fu</name>
		<desc>Fly Fu is a side-scrolling beat-'em-up game with characters designed from photographs of dead insects mixed with doodle art. 
Your girlfriend, Kate Moth, a fluffy moth was kidnapped by evil spiders and dragged away to the suburb.
You are not a common housefly but trained to fight. Being a Kung-Fu master, only you can save your love from the claws of the evil insects!</desc>
		<image>./images/Fly Fu (USA)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Fly Fu (USA)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Fly Fu (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fly Fu (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20100720T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Invictus</developer>
		<publisher>Invictus</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201001T000457</lastplayed>
		<md5>454096d71b9b8e9449de1370797a5df9</md5>
		<gametime>42</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153434" />
	</game>
	<game id="28416">
		<path>./Pilot Acadamy.iso</path>
		<name>Pilot Academy</name>
		<desc>Pilot Academy is a flight simulator on the PSP which encompasses all eras of flight, ranging from historic WWI fighter planes such as the famous Fokker Triplane (flown by the "Red Baron" Manfred von Richthofen) to modern military and civilian jet aircraft like the F-15, F-16 and Boeing 747. All aircraft names and designs are licensed.

In the initial lessons, the game teaches the player the basics of powered flight for both civilian and military purposes. The game uses all PSP buttons to deliver a flight simulation feel with the analog nub serving as a joystick. Controlling the flaps, air brakes, raising and lowering the landing gear as well as using the tail rudder are also possible. Military aircraft feature air-to-ground missiles, air-to-air-missiles, a machine gun and flares for self defense against missiles. The only thing missing from the simulation is a fuel gauge, but since most missions are rather short, this was probably a deliberate design choice. 

After civilian and military flight lessons are completed, the player is free to choose from various missions and challenges. Completing a task successfully unlocks new aircraft in the player's hangar which can then be flown any time in free flight mode (but only on the tropical map). Distinctions are also awarded for completion of a mission based on time taken, aircraft integrity, completion of objectives and level of excitement/comfort of passengers (if any) and determine the level of proficiency of the player pilot.

Flights take place over different types of terrain including tropical, desert, snow covered mountains and canyons and in varying weather conditions like rain, snow and even in a storm. Some missions begin while already airborne, while others require the player to taxi onto the runway, takeoff and land after completing the objective.  

Multiplayer supports up to four players dogfighting against each other or cooperatively with planes from any of the four military eras, e.g. a dogfight between a WWII propeller plane like the P-51 Mustang or the Spitfire versus an F-14 Tomcat or F-16 Falcon is possible.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pilot Acadamy-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pilot Acadamy-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pilot Acadamy-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pilot Acadamy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Rising Star Games</developer>
		<publisher>Kuju Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153443" />
	</game>
	<game id="28125">
		<path>./Loco Roco.iso</path>
		<name>LocoRoco</name>
		<desc>LocoRoco is an innovative 2D platform/action game available exclusively for the PSP. Featuring unique controls utilizing the "L" and "R" shoulder buttons, players are tasked with controlling via "tilting or bumping" the landscape of the LocoRoco in order to help them navigate through the level and keep them out of harm's way. With more than 40 stages, players control and guide the LocoRoco through vibrant, thriving and lush worlds filled with slippery slopes, swing ropes , and more. Featuring six different types of LocoRoco that include their own voices and actions, players will be enchanted by captivating music that communicates the joyous world of these LocoRoco. In addition, LocoRoco features the rewarding LocoHouse, three mini-games , and wireless features. The peaceful world of the LocoRoco are under attack by the not-so-nice Moja Corps. These evil outer space creatures want nothing but to capture the blissful LocoRoco and take them from their land of blowing flowers, lively creatures and pastel scenery. As the planet where the LocoRoco inhabit, players must tilt, roll and bounce the LocoRoco to safety.</desc>
		<image>./images/Loco Roco-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Loco Roco-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Loco Roco-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Loco Roco-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Loco Roco-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153453" />
	</game>
	<game id="28439">
		<path>./Ridge Racer 2.iso</path>
		<name>Ridge Racer 2</name>
		<desc>Ridge Racer 2 is not so much a sequel to the early PlayStation Portable title Ridge Racer, but rather an update of the existing game that features several enhancements and a lot of new content. Released about a year after its predecessor, the changes and additions in Ridge Racer 2 include:

1. A new opening and ending CGI movie.
2. Many new tracks and songs from previous Ridge Racer games.
3. New SPECIAL class cars to challenge in duels and win.
 
Survival mode: In a four car race, after each round, the car to be in last place is eliminated from the pack.
4. Duel mode: A race against a single AI car.
5. Single Race mode has been replaced with an Arcade mode in which the player races not only against the pack of 11 cars but also has to reach checkpoints on the track to stay in the game. The options menu features a new setting to adjust the difficulty of Arcade mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ridge Racer 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ridge Racer 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ridge Racer 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ridge Racer 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20060914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Ridge Racer</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153504" />
	</game>
	<game id="28475">
		<path>./Death Jr.ISO</path>
		<name>Death Jr.</name>
		<desc>Take on the role of the Grim Reapers teenage son Death Jr. after he unleashes an unspeakable horror from a box that Pandora herself couldn't open in a school field trip at the museum.

Death Jr. is a 3-D platform game in which you control Death Jr. a.k.a. DJ in an attempt to find his friends that have been taken by the evil necromancer Moloch. DJ's friend souls appear as puzzle pieces throughout the game in which you must find to bring them back.

Warp through 17 levels fighting demons and fiends using DJ's famed scythe along with other weapons like a shotgun, electric gun and even C4 Hamsters. Use DJ's scythe to not only maim and kill but to reach heights not accessible by jumping. Upgrade weapons and learn new moves (scythe combos) by collecting widgets scattered throughout the levels. The ability to destroy the environment is an advantage to DJ as the more successful hits with his scythe be it animate or inanimate his combo meter will rise allowing DJ's friend Pandora to assist in the fight.

Death Jr.'s camera is a free roaming camera that follows DJ around with the ability to snap to the position DJ is looking at the press of a button. You can also free look with the press of a button and lock on to enemies and strafe while shooting with a gun. At the end of each level you receive a report card that tells you your number of kills, how much destruction you caused, the total number of combo points, special items discovered and your final grade.</desc>
		<image>./images/Death Jr-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Death Jr-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Death Jr-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Death Jr-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20050816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Backbone Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153513" />
	</game>
	<game id="28293">
		<path>./Everbodys Golf.iso</path>
		<name>Hot Shots Golf : Open Tee</name>
		<desc>Go golf crazy and take on a cast of colourful characters in the coolest clubhouse around. No need for airs and graces here - just select a golfer from a range of friendly faces, and customize their abilities, attributes and appearance before teeing off across a series of challenging courses and game modes. Go head-to-head with both friends and foes via WiFi compatible Ad Hoc Mode and become a true golfing legend.</desc>
		<image>./images/Everbodys Golf-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Everbodys Golf-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Everbodys Golf-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Everbodys Golf-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clap Hanz</developer>
		<publisher>Clap Hanz</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Golf</genre>
		<family>Everybody's Golf</family>
		<players>8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153523" />
	</game>
	<game id="28626">
		<path>./Frantix.iso</path>
		<name>Frantix</name>
		<desc>Frantix is a puzzle-based adventure game for PSP. It features over 180 different levels. Playing as one of the heroes, the objective of the game is to collect as many gems as possible in order to advance in the world of Frantix. Though there is no story explaining why our hero is venturing through this land of puzzles, it is clear that this must be done as quickly as possible. Each stage has a gem requirement, and you can exit when you have found the required amount. The puzzles are usually based on colored gems that open specific doors.

There are six worlds (including a tutorial) where you get past hazards such as water and quick sands, avoid patrolling creatures, collect gems, manipulate crates, sneak around, build bridges, and plant explosives. There are also power-ups that allow you to walk over certain surfaces, increase speed, or provide invincibility. With short levels, Frantix can be played for five minutes or an hour with the same satisfaction.</desc>
		<image>./images/Frantix-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Frantix-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Frantix-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Frantix-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20050919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Killer Game</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153534" />
	</game>
	<game id="103357">
		<path>./Who Wants To Be A Millionare.iso</path>
		<name>Who Wants To Be A Millionaire - Party Edition</name>
		<desc>It's time to ask once again, Who Wants to be a Millionaire? This 2006 entry in the series (based on the original UK show) reinvents the series with a new cast of crazy characters, new game modes and a more complete multiplayer game. The challenge, as always, is to answer 15 questions to win a million, using your Life Lines to get yourself through the tough questions if you think you need help. Now you get to choose your on-screen contestant from 16 unique and eager contestants in an authentic Millionaire experience hosted by Chris Tarrant. Up to four people can compete in the multiplayer, which is now bursting with options including a quick fire round, Millionaire party and a play or pass mode in which you can pass difficult questions over to another player. There are 4,000 brand new questions in this version, plus there is an added feature where players who bag the big Millionaire pound prize are given a code they can enter on the game's website, so they can brag about their feat with other virtual millionaires.</desc>
		<image>./images/Who Wants To Be A Millionare-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Who Wants To Be A Millionare-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Who Wants To Be A Millionare-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Who Wants To Be A Millionare-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20061201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153540" />
	</game>
	<game id="28258">
		<path>./Transformers.iso</path>
		<name>Transformers: The Game</name>
		<desc>Transformers: The Game is the name of multiple versions of a video game based on the 2007 live action film Transformers, all of which were released in North America in June 2007. Home console and PC versions were developed by Traveller's Tales for the PlayStation 2, Xbox 360, Wii, PlayStation 3 and PC. A different PlayStation Portable version was developed by Savage Entertainment.

Transformers Autobots and Transformers Decepticons are the Nintendo DS versions of Transfomers: The Game. Vicarious Visions, who was tasked with bringing the adaptation to the Nintendo DS, chose to adapt the DS version into two separate games.[1] Autobots follows the heroes' perspective while Decepticons follows the villains'. Unlike games with multiple SKUs such as PokÃ©mon which feature only minor differences between versions, these are two separate games, sharing some basic similarities, but with unique characters, missions and locations.[2]</desc>
		<image>./images/Transformers-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Transformers-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Transformers-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Transformers-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20070619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Savage Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153548" />
	</game>
	<game id="29117">
		<path>./ReelFishing.iso</path>
		<name>Reel Fishing Great Outdoors</name>
		<desc>Reel Fishing: Life &amp; Nature is a return to nature fishing! Whether you're a seasoned veteran or have yet to cast your first line, Reel Fishing: Life &amp; Nature will make it possible to experience fishing as it was meant to be...as it should be...in mother nature. Learn basic and advance fishing techniques from the Fishing Master. Experience a magnificent 3-Dimensional fishing adventure with beautiful environments, life-like fish and soothing environmental sounds!</desc>
		<image>./images/ReelFishing-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/ReelFishing-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/ReelFishing-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/ReelFishing-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Zoo Digital Publishing</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation / Fishing</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153556" />
	</game>
	<game id="28029">
		<path>./Dungeon Siege Thrown Of Agony.iso</path>
		<name>Dungeon Siege : Throne of Agony</name>
		<desc>Dungeon Siege: Throne of Agony is an all-new adventure, created from the ground up specifically for the PSP handheld system. Dungeon Siege: Throne of Agony features all-new playable characters and a freshly designed, non-linear, single player campaign as well as support for Ad Hoc co-operative and competitive multiplayer games. Multiple characters to choose from - Characters can be customized as they level up into different Hero Classes and then even further into Legendary Classes. Player can choose from numerous Pets and Companions to play with. Gameplay will encourage the player to constantly switch between unique Pets and Companions to use their special powers. Face over 100 monsters including well known monsters from the Dungeon Siege world as well as many new creatures. Multiplayer Cooperative Campaign allows you to play with a friend. Each player can bring a Pet or Companion adding up to a four party experience. Multiplayer Battle Arenas allow a concise, fun party experience for players who don't have time for a full campaign. 15 hours of gameplay with 2 different modes Mercenary and Elite.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dungeon Siege Thrown Of Agony-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dungeon Siege Thrown Of Agony-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dungeon Siege Thrown Of Agony-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dungeon Siege Thrown Of Agony-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SuperVillain Studios</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games / Action RPG</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153602" />
	</game>
	<game id="28062">
		<path>./Fifa Street 2.cso</path>
		<name>FIFA Street 2</name>
		<desc>The game is a street football game in which the player can take control of 4-a-side versions of national football teams in matches where the object is to win by scoring a set amount of goals or points via tricks, or within a time limit. In the career mode "Rule the Streets", one creates a player and competes in tournaments around the world to obtain "Skill Bills" to buy clothing and upgrade his rating. As the player improves, he can captain his own street football team and eventually become an international. The best players have special moves often named after their nickname.

Legends of football such as Abedi Pele, Eric Cantona and Paul Gascoigne are unlockable during the game.

The game has its own in-game radio station, presented by Zane Lowe of BBC Radio 1 and featuring music by artists such as Roots Manuva, Sway, Pendulum, The Editors and The Subways.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fifa Street 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Fifa Street 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Fifa Street 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fifa Street 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Fifa Street 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer</genre>
		<family>FIFA</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153614" />
	</game>
	<game id="28358">
		<path>./Micro MachinesV4.iso</path>
		<name>Micro Machines V4</name>
		<desc>Mixing miniature mayhem with maximum multiplayer racing, Micro Machines v4 features knockabout, breakneck racing in the fastest scale miniatures, complete with explosive weapon power-ups. Letting you loose with hundreds of vehicles, each with distinctive performance abilities, you'll be racing your inch-long miniature motors on the wildest tracks where everyday household objects appear immense in size and can become lethal hazards.</desc>
		<image>./images/Micro MachinesV4-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Micro MachinesV4-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Micro MachinesV4-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Micro MachinesV4-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Supersonic Software</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>MicroMachines</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153623" />
	</game>
	<game id="28475">
		<path>./Death Jnr 2.iso</path>
		<name>Death Jr.</name>
		<desc>Take on the role of the Grim Reapers teenage son Death Jr. after he unleashes an unspeakable horror from a box that Pandora herself couldn't open in a school field trip at the museum.

Death Jr. is a 3-D platform game in which you control Death Jr. a.k.a. DJ in an attempt to find his friends that have been taken by the evil necromancer Moloch. DJ's friend souls appear as puzzle pieces throughout the game in which you must find to bring them back.

Warp through 17 levels fighting demons and fiends using DJ's famed scythe along with other weapons like a shotgun, electric gun and even C4 Hamsters. Use DJ's scythe to not only maim and kill but to reach heights not accessible by jumping. Upgrade weapons and learn new moves (scythe combos) by collecting widgets scattered throughout the levels. The ability to destroy the environment is an advantage to DJ as the more successful hits with his scythe be it animate or inanimate his combo meter will rise allowing DJ's friend Pandora to assist in the fight.

Death Jr.'s camera is a free roaming camera that follows DJ around with the ability to snap to the position DJ is looking at the press of a button. You can also free look with the press of a button and lock on to enemies and strafe while shooting with a gun. At the end of each level you receive a report card that tells you your number of kills, how much destruction you caused, the total number of combo points, special items discovered and your final grade.</desc>
		<image>./images/Death Jnr 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Death Jnr 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Death Jnr 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Death Jnr 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20050816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Backbone Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153631" />
	</game>
	<game id="28070">
		<path>./Ghost Recon Warfighter 2.iso</path>
		<name>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2</name>
		<desc>Scott Mitchell, the leader of the ghosts, is sent south of the Panama border to eliminate guerrilla forces believed to be trafficking high-tech weapons to rebel forces. 

â€¢ Exclusively developed for the PSPÂ®: Original story, setting, technology and gameplay for you to engage in. 
â€¢ Advanced Warfighter: Master prototype weapons, use drone technology and call in naval artillery or air strike support. 
â€¢ Co-op multiplayer: Play the entire campaign with a friend over wireless network.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ghost Recon Warfighter 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ghost Recon Warfighter 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ghost Recon Warfighter 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ghost Recon Warfighter 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20070823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153640" />
	</game>
	<game id="142891">
		<path>./The Con.iso</path>
		<name>The Con</name>
		<desc>The Con is a fighting game featuring 20 different characters as well as the ability to create-a-fighter with the ability to use face-mapping from the players photo collection. The player competes in fights and tournaments to earn money and pay off debts to a lone shark, but not only can the player win fights to earn money, but they can take a dive in a fixed fight while trying not to show to the crowd that it was rigged. Players can also bet against their own matches.

Players can also customize their fighters, tweaking their fighting stats with upgrade points acquired through fights, they also can change their appearance with clothing unlocked through the course of the game. There are also fives modes to compete in, Story mode, Survival, Quick Fight, Time Attack mode and a Two-player mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/The Con-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/The Con-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/The Con-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Con-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<developer>Think And Feel Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153648" />
	</game>
	<game id="28716">
		<path>./PQ.Practical.Intelligence.Quotient.iso</path>
		<name>PQ : Practical Intelligence Quotient</name>
		<desc>Based upon psychological research, your PQ score will be determined by how quickly and effectively you solve each life-like situation. Test your wits, bend your brain, and match wits with the minds of users worldwide. A 3D puzzle game that tests players problem solving skills, PQ uses the PSPÂ® system's Infrastructure Mode and allows players to post their PQ score on the worldwide ranking site to see how they rank against other players around the world.</desc>
		<image>./images/PQ.Practical.Intelligence.Quotient-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/PQ.Practical.Intelligence.Quotient-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/PQ.Practical.Intelligence.Quotient-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/PQ.Practical.Intelligence.Quotient-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Now Production</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153703" />
	</game>
	<game id="28518">
		<path>./Ape Academy 2.iso</path>
		<name>Ape Academy 2</name>
		<desc>The primary antagonist, Specter, introduces a new card game which becomes very popular among humans and pipo monkeys alike. Using this card game, he dominates the world through culture manipulation, concurrently introducing a card battle contest for monkeys to complete in. The prize for winning the contest is the rare "Platinum Specter" trading card and a year's supply of bananas.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ape Academy 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ape Academy 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ape Academy 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ape Academy 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153709" />
	</game>
	<game id="28203">
		<path>./Lumines.iso</path>
		<name>Lumines</name>
		<desc>Bust blocks, solve puzzles, and play wirelessly with your friends. In Lumines, your objective is to clear the screen by connecting blocks of like colors together. A timeline wipes away your solid-color creations, which can also initiate combos and link moves. See if you have what it takes to advance through 24 levels, each with its own musical theme and sound effects. Lumines features four gameplay modes, including single-player and multiplayer.</desc>
		<image>./images/Lumines-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Lumines-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Lumines-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Lumines-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>8baed0d2c61683a340e1b0ff6f53d6b3</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153715" />
	</game>
	<game id="28025">
		<path>./Marvel ultimate Alliance.cso</path>
		<name>Marvel : Ultimate Alliance</name>
		<desc>Dr. Doom has united supervillains as the Masters of Evil. Now for the first time ever, over 20 Marvel superheroes including Spider-Man, Captain America, Wolverine, Ghost Rider, Blade and Silver Surfer have come together to stop Doom. Mix and match your choice of Marvel superheroes, in teams of four as you travel across the Marvel Universe to stop this threat. Certain teams such as The Fantastic Four and The New Avengers provide additional bonuses.

Some heroes must be unlocked first. The game also features RPG elements, such as leveling up. When a hero gains a level, they earn points you can use to upgrade their skills. You also collect Shield Coins, which can be spent on boosts for your hero team. 

You explore various legendary Marvel locales, from Asgard, to Prince Namor's Atlantis, where you take on foes with punches, kicks and super powers. Super powers drain energy, however, so use them wisely. Combos can be achieved by combining super powers. Energy is restored by collecting blue orbs from fallen foes. 

Boss battles are like the comics themselves: titanic battles that often not only test brawn but your brain as well. With over 20 playable heroes plus all the cameos, there are over 100 heroes and villains.

The game modes feature either single player, co-op, or online play. In general, Marvel Ultimate Alliance's gameplay can be considered an improved version of 2004's X-Men: Legends. The different versions are fairly identical. The PSP release has three more game modes, while Wii, PS3 and Xbox 360 have additional levels.</desc>
		<image>./images/Marvel ultimate Alliance-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Marvel ultimate Alliance-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Marvel ultimate Alliance-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Marvel ultimate Alliance-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raven Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<family>Marvel</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153718" />
	</game>
	<game id="28281">
		<path>./Ghost in the Shell.iso</path>
		<name>Ghost in the Shell : Stand Alone Complex</name>
		<desc>Based on the series of the same name, Ghost in the Shell: Stand Alone Complex is a fast-action third-person shooter for up to four players. As "Major" Motoko Kusanagi, Batou, and Tachikoma, you can engage enemies in both multiplayer combat and single-player missions. In single-player mode, your missions involve hacking into machines and computers, controlling your enemies' minds from a distance, and using a variety of weapons to eliminate your enemies. Complete the Story mode to unlock more playable characters, costumes, and additional weapons.

The game serves as a sequel to the PS2 game of the same name.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ghost in the Shell-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ghost in the Shell-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ghost in the Shell-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ghost in the Shell-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20051026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>G-Artists</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153725" />
	</game>
	<game id="28153">
		<path>./Metal Gear Acid.ISO</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Ac!d</name>
		<desc>The Metal Gear series comes to the PSP offering a new gameplay system and storyline. In Metal Gear Acid, you'll take on the role of Solid Snake, a top-secret agent who's an expert at infiltration. It's up to you to make calculated decisions to plan out your strategy and accomplish missions in a turn-based style of game. Strategic battle cards give you different abilities and stealth tactics that help you achieve mission objectives. Experience a deeper kind of tactical espionage in the palm of your hand.</desc>
		<image>./images/Metal Gear Acid-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Metal Gear Acid-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Metal Gear Acid-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Metal Gear Acid-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Metal Gear Acid-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Metal Gear</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153729" />
	</game>
	<game id="28827">
		<path>./Puzzle_Bobble.iso</path>
		<name>Puzzle Bobble Pocket</name>
		<desc>Puzzle Bobble, also known as Bust-a-Move, is a 1994 tile-matching arcade puzzle video game for one or two players created by Taito Corporation. It is based on Taito's popular 1986 arcade game Bubble Bobble, featuring characters and themes from that game. Its characteristically cute Japanese animation and music, along with its play mechanics and level designs, made it successful as an arcade title and spawned several sequels and ports to home gaming systems.</desc>
		<image>./images/Puzzle_Bobble-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Puzzle_Bobble-video.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>./images/Puzzle_Bobble-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20041224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<md5>77675b5b922e64571b629f267a7f7783</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153734" />
	</game>
	<game id="28259">
		<path>./Exit.iso</path>
		<name>Exit</name>
		<desc>Exit places you in the role of Mr. ESC, professional escape artist extraordinaire.As Mr. ESC, your job is to guide scores of people from precarious situations. In the midst of situations such as a burning apartment, you will guide and direct those people in an effort to take each and every person in each level out of harm's way. One hundred levels are available in the main quest, with an additional one hundred becoming available through wi-fi downloads.</desc>
		<image>./images/Exit-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Exit-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Exit-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Exit-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Exit-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153741" />
	</game>
	<game id="28438">
		<path>./Rengoku 2.iso</path>
		<name>Rengoku II : The Stairway to H.E.A.V.E.N.</name>
		<desc>The first Rengoku was a surprise hit for many PSPÂ® gamers. Featuring a compelling story about a cyborg yearning to escape its life of never ending battle, Rengoku provided a new and exciting world to battle through on the PSPÂ®. 

Now gamers will return to the world of Rengoku as they battle their way through the towering structure of Purgatory and the Seven Deadly Sins! Rengoku 2 builds upon the first game with improved level design for more strategy, smoother control, exciting new fighting mechanics that allow for attack combos, and deeper customization. With network support for up to four players via AD HOC, more levels, an explosive soundtrack by Hong Kong composer, Chan Kwong Wing, and character designs by legendary manga artist, Jun Suemi, Rengoku 2 is a deep and more challenging action experience.
-- Summary from Gamefaqs.com</desc>
		<image>./images/Rengoku 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Rengoku 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Rengoku 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rengoku 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153752" />
	</game>
	<game id="28109">
		<path>./SSX On Tour.iso</path>
		<name>SSX : On Tour</name>
		<desc>Create your skier or snowboarder and get on the slopes in this version of the SSX franchise. With a different front end interface to previous versions, which looks like a mix between MTV and a doodle book, you select the challenge you want to take part in rather than boarding your way to the event as previous versions.

With improved controls making "Monster Jumps" (Uber Tricks) easier to perform, everyone can look like a professional without learning button combos. As before, if you perform the same trick over and over, you won't get the points to take your skier/snowboarder from a novice to what they have a labeled "black-diamond-dominating rockstar".

The game promises big jumps, fast pace and lots of coloured, detailed slopes.

The GameCube version delivers Mario, Luigi and Peaches on the slopes as special characters. Each has their own moves and is accompanied by Mario-style music.</desc>
		<image>./images/SSX On Tour-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/SSX On Tour-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SSX On Tour-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SSX On Tour-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/SSX On Tour-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20051011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skiing</genre>
		<family>SSX</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153810" />
	</game>
	<game id="28030">
		<path>./Rainbow Six Vegas.iso</path>
		<name>Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas</name>
		<desc>The stakes are high when the world's most elite counter-terrorism unit enters Las Vegas, where over 36.7 million men, women and children visit each year. "Sin City," the home of the famous Las Vegas Strip, flashy hotels, high-rolling casinos and world-famous celebrities, becomes the setting for a terrorist threat of global proportions. What happens when one of the world's most famous cities is held hostage by terrorists?</desc>
		<image>./images/Rainbow Six Vegas-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Rainbow Six Vegas-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Rainbow Six Vegas-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rainbow Six Vegas-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20070612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153817" />
	</game>
	<game id="28131">
		<path>./Sonic Rivals.iso</path>
		<name>Sonic Rivals</name>
		<desc>Sonic Rivals is a platforming/racing game and the first game in the series to feature on the PSP. It has typical Sonic gameplay, but with a twist - players race through 2.5D stages against a CPU character, only progressing when they get to the end of the stage first.

You can choose from five characters: Sonic, Knuckles, Shadow, Silver, and Metal Sonic. There are six zones in the story mode, split into two acts with a boss at the end of the second act. Defeating bosses is not sufficient, players also need to do it before the opponent gets the job done. Next to the story mode, there is also a challenge mode and a cup mode. In the wireless play mode players can challenge other PSP owners. While racing, players can collect power-ups with special attacks. Opponents can also be pushed around during the race.

Players can also collect cards by completing certain tasks in the game and these cards can be traded in the wireless play mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic Rivals-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Sonic Rivals-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Sonic Rivals-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sonic Rivals-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20061116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Backbone Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Sonic</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153820" />
	</game>
	<game id="27960">
		<path>./Harry  Potter Order Of The Phoenix.iso</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix</name>
		<desc>In Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix, Harry returns for his fifth year of study at Hogwarts. The wizarding community is in denial about his recent encounter with the evil Lord Voldemort. The Minister for Magic, Cornelius Fudge, appoints a new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher to keep watch over Dumbledore and the Hogwarts students. The young wizards are woefully unprepared to defend themselves against the dark forces threatening them, leaving Harry, Ron and Hermione to handles thigns themselves. Harry prepares a group of young wizards calling themselves "Dumbledore's Army" for the extraordinary battle against Voldemort and his Death Eaters that lies ahead.</desc>
		<image>./images/Harry  Potter Order Of The Phoenix-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Harry  Potter Order Of The Phoenix-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Harry  Potter Order Of The Phoenix-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Harry  Potter Order Of The Phoenix-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Harry  Potter Order Of The Phoenix-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20070625T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Harry Potter</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153825" />
	</game>
	<game id="29078">
		<path>./Pinball_Fantasies_v2_PSN.iso</path>
		<name>Pinball Fantasies</name>
		<desc>After the success of Pinball Dreams on several systems, a sequel featuring four new tables was created. The gameplay is much the same as the first game, with realistic physics, multi-player options and a high score table to aim for. The tables are Partyland, Speed Devils, Billion Dollar Gameshow and Stones 'n' Bones, taking in a funfair, racing cars, a tacky game-show, and a graveyard. Each one has a range of ramps, combos, light sequences and targets to shoot, as well as general themes which are less influenced by real tables than those in Pinball Dreams.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pinball_Fantasies_v2_PSN-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pinball_Fantasies_v2_PSN-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pinball_Fantasies_v2_PSN-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pinball_Fantasies_v2_PSN-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<developer>Cowboy Rodeo</developer>
		<publisher>Cowboy Rodeo</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201001T001652</lastplayed>
		<md5>c97875589043aa4a2ac586a1f24b5163</md5>
		<gametime>22</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153829" />
	</game>
	<game id="28122">
		<path>./Scarface Money Power Respect.iso</path>
		<name>Scarface : Money. Power. Respect.</name>
		<desc>Scarface: Money. Power. Respect. on PSP lets you reclaim the Cuban baron's drug empire. Combine turn-based strategy gameplay and real-time action to relive the rise of Tony Montana. In a realistic Miami, compete with your enemies for the conquest of territory and control the action in real time during battles in the middle of the street. Up to four players can compete over wi-fi.</desc>
		<image>./images/Scarface Money Power Respect-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Scarface Money Power Respect-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Scarface Money Power Respect-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Scarface Money Power Respect-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<developer>Universal</developer>
		<publisher>FarSight Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153834" />
	</game>
	<game id="28136">
		<path>./Ridge Racer.ISO</path>
		<name>Ridge Racer</name>
		<desc>Ridge Racer is about speed and cool power sliding.
The game features a nice selection of 24 tracks, 58 cars and music from all previous RR-games and in all aspects is faithful to the series' spirit. There are many game modes in the game, like a world tour-mode where player competes on the courses in order to earn new cars and tracks, Time Attack where one races around the tracks against time and also a multiplayer mode, which supports the ad-hoc, meaning that up to eight players can race against each other with only one game disc, with one player hosting, and others joining.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ridge Racer-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ridge Racer-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ridge Racer-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ridge Racer-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Ridge Racer</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153835" />
	</game>
	<game id="28828">
		<path>./World Tour Soccer.ISO</path>
		<name>World Tour Soccer</name>
		<desc>World Tour Soccer: Challenge Edition (WTS; known simply as World Tour Soccer in the United States) is the PlayStation Portable version of the popular PlayStation and PlayStation 2 game This Is Football (TIF), created by SCEE's London Studio and released in 2005.

WTS featured very similar gameplay as TIF but was not a direct port of its forerunner as a number of areas were enhanced - particularly the challenge mode referred to in its title.

WTS has emulated TIF's success by selling over half a million copies in PAL territories.

As a result of its success, a sequel to WTS was developed by SCEE and released as World Tour Soccer 06 in 2006.</desc>
		<image>./images/World Tour Soccer-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/World Tour Soccer-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/World Tour Soccer-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/World Tour Soccer-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Soccer</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153842" />
	</game>
	<game id="28614">
		<path>./The_Impossible_Game_USA.iso</path>
		<name>The Impossible Game</name>
		<desc>The Impossible Game. With a title like that, you know it'll be a tough ride but The Impossible Game takes "difficulty" to a whole new level. It's fast-paced and brutal, but with near-instant respawning, the experience is as smooth as it is deadly.
You play a humble orange square, racing against a serene blue background. The trick is that there are plenty of obstacles on this course: triangles are like deadly spikes, and squares can be jumped on top of but will kill you if you slam into them. Likewise, you can die if you fall through a hole in the floor. Your orange square will hurtle forward regardless of the danger, and your only control is simple tap to jump. Longer taps equal longer jumps, and you?ll need meticulous precision if you want to survive. The music syncs with your music, which is a very nifty effect that adds to the surreal quality of the whole thing.</desc>
		<image>./images/The_Impossible_Game_USA-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/The_Impossible_Game_USA-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/The_Impossible_Game_USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The_Impossible_Game_USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<developer>Grip Games</developer>
		<publisher>Grip Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>cbfbc53c775e593e4bf2ca39267d9d12</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153847" />
	</game>
	<game id="28561">
		<path>./Pimp My Ride.iso</path>
		<name>Pimp My Ride</name>
		<desc>Pimp My Ride is a simulation/racing game published by Activision. This game is based on the popular MTV show. It was released in 2006 for the Wii, Xbox 360, PlayStation Portable and PlayStation 2 consoles. In the game, players are challenged to pimp out their friends' cars by Xzibit, transforming something old and rusty into something worthy of displaying on the streets. Cars can be redesigned from bumper to bumper and it will be playersâ€™ responsibilities to capture the styles, likes and interests of their clients.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pimp My Ride-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pimp My Ride-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pimp My Ride-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pimp My Ride-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>20070410T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eutechnyx</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153855" />
	</game>
	<game id="28424">
		<path>./Thrillville.cso</path>
		<name>Thrillville</name>
		<desc>Thrillville: Off the Rails is an amusement park simulator and is the sequel to the original title Thrillville.

Uncle Mortimer returns to aid you with his brand new Woah Coaster pieces which allow the player to build coasters with massive jumps, ring or fire and spinning blades into their coaster.

The main plot line is that Globo-Joy, the rival park owners and main antagonist from the first game, are trying to destroy the good name of Thrillville by putting saboteurs in your park.

The only way to solve the mystery is to help solve your guests' problems by building new rides and coasters or beat challengers to your games.</desc>
		<image>./images/Thrillville-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Thrillville-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Thrillville-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Thrillville-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Thrillville-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20061121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Frontier Developments</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<family>Thrillville</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153911" />
	</game>
	<game id="28136">
		<path>./Ridge Racer.cso</path>
		<name>Ridge Racer</name>
		<desc>Ridge Racer is about speed and cool power sliding.
The game features a nice selection of 24 tracks, 58 cars and music from all previous RR-games and in all aspects is faithful to the series' spirit. There are many game modes in the game, like a world tour-mode where player competes on the courses in order to earn new cars and tracks, Time Attack where one races around the tracks against time and also a multiplayer mode, which supports the ad-hoc, meaning that up to eight players can race against each other with only one game disc, with one player hosting, and others joining.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ridge Racer-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ridge Racer-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ridge Racer-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ridge Racer-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Ridge Racer</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153912" />
	</game>
	<game id="27971">
		<path>./Prince Of Persia Rival Swords.ISO</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia : Rival Swords</name>
		<desc>In Prince of Persia Rival Swords, the Prince makes his way home to Babylon, bearing with him Kaileena, the enigmatic Empress of Time, and unspeakable scars from the Island of Time. But instead of the peace he longs for, he finds his kingdom ravaged by war and Kaileena the target of a brutal plot. When she is kidnapped, the Prince tracks her to the palace â€“ only to see her murdered by a powerful enemy. Her death unleashes the Sands of Time, which strike the Prince and threaten to destroy everything he holds dear. Cast out on the streets, hunted as a fugitive, the Prince soon discovers that the Sands have tainted him, too. They have given rise to a deadly Dark Prince, whose spirit gradually possesses him.</desc>
		<image>./images/Prince Of Persia Rival Swords-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Prince Of Persia Rival Swords-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Prince Of Persia Rival Swords-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Prince Of Persia Rival Swords-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Prince of Persia</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153925" />
	</game>
	<game id="28284">
		<path>./Marvel Nemesis Rise Of The Imperfects.iso</path>
		<name>Marvel Nemesis : Rise of the Imperfects</name>
		<desc>Marvel Nemesis: Rise of the Imperfects pits fierce Marvel superheroes against each other in a 3D fighting game. You can assume control of heroes such as the Punisher, Spider-Man, and Captain America, and duel with them in interactive and destructible environments. A new team of superheroes called the Imperfects joins the mayhem. You can play in single-player story mode to unlock collectible awards, or you can play against other gamers in multiplayer modes.</desc>
		<image>./images/Marvel Nemesis Rise Of The Imperfects-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Marvel Nemesis Rise Of The Imperfects-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Marvel Nemesis Rise Of The Imperfects-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Marvel Nemesis Rise Of The Imperfects-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Marvel Nemesis Rise Of The Imperfects-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153930" />
	</game>
	<game id="144207">
		<path>./Gundam Battle Tactics.iso</path>
		<name>Gundam Battle Tactics</name>
		<desc>Gundam Battle Tactics, released on September 22, 2005, is a third-person action/mech-combat simulation game for the PlayStation Portable, based on Japan's long-running mecha-based series, Gundam. Tactics, released only in Japan and South Korea, was later followed with a sequel, Gundam Battle Royale, also for the PlayStation Portable, in late 2006. This game follows the events of the One Year War and most scenarios are heavily influenced by animation episodes from One Year War storylines, namely Mobile Suit Gundam, The 08th MS Team, War in the Pocket, and Blue Destiny. This game plays similarly to another Bandai Gundam game for the Sony PlayStation 2, Mobile Suit Gundam: Lost War Chronicles.</desc>
		<image>./images/Gundam Battle Tactics-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Gundam Battle Tactics-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Gundam Battle Tactics-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Gundam Battle Tactics-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050921T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153940" />
	</game>
	<game id="144727">
		<path>./Retro_City_Rampage_DX_USA.iso</path>
		<name>Retro City Rampage DX</name>
		<desc>Retro City Rampage reimagines the open world crime genre in the '80s! Rampage the city, steal cars, or play over 60 story mode missions! 

This remastered pop culture send-up features a full Story Mode of open world missions, along with Arcade Challenges for quick pick-up-and-play action. Explore the city by foot or by car, and discover minigames, customizations, collectibles, special guest stars, and more.</desc>
		<image>./images/Retro_City_Rampage_DX_USA-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Retro_City_Rampage_DX_USA-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Retro_City_Rampage_DX_USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Retro_City_Rampage_DX_USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Retro_City_Rampage_DX_USA-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20160719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vblank Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Vblank Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>1c82a3eabbad3ee09cfe9e1ead54cd7b</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153959" />
	</game>
	<game id="28585">
		<path>./Shrek The Third.iso</path>
		<name>Shrek The Third</name>
		<desc>The Frog King has died and Shrek has inherited the throne. Since Shrek's not a big fan of this idea, he and his friends journey to the Worcestershire academy to recruit Fiona's cousin, Artie, for the job. Unfortunately, while he's away the dastardly Prince Charming has big plans to take over the kingdom.

SHReK the THiRD is an action-platformer with a heavy emphasis on brawling and humor. With plenty of Prince Charming's goons in his path (including black knights, evil gnomes, a crooning Captain Hook, and giant walking trees), Shrek will have to use all of his abilities to defeat them, find his way home, and pick up some souvenir mugs along the way.

Each level features several quests, lots of collectibles, and funny situations. While most of the levels feature Shrek himself, there are six playable characters in total (Donkey, Puss in Boots, Fiona, Artie, and Sleeping Beauty feature as well), over 20 levels, three big boss battles, and several multiplayer minigames.</desc>
		<image>./images/Shrek The Third-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Shrek The Third-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Shrek The Third-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shrek The Third-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Shrek The Third-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20070605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<family>Shrek</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154004" />
	</game>
	<game id="28026">
		<path>./Need For Speed Carbon.iso</path>
		<name>Need for Speed Carbon : Own the City</name>
		<desc>Need for Speed Carbon: Own the City is a handheld released based off of Need for Speed: Carbon. It was released for the PlayStation Portable, Nintendo DS, Gameboy Advance, and Zeebo.

Compared to Need for Speed: Carbon, the title greatly differs from gameplay and graphics.</desc>
		<image>./images/Need For Speed Carbon-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Need For Speed Carbon-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Need For Speed Carbon-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Need For Speed Carbon-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20061031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Black Box</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Need for Speed</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154009" />
	</game>
	<game id="28319">
		<path>./Bleach 2 - Heat Of The Soul.iso</path>
		<name>Bleach - Heat The Soul 2</name>
		<desc>Bleach: Heat the Soul 2 is the second installment in the Heat the Soul series, released on September 1, 2005.[6] The theme song for this game is Chance! by Uverworld, and the music was composed by Kazuo Hanzawa, under the alias "NON", and Hitoshi Sakimoto. Continuing where Heat the Soul left off, the story mode of Heat the Soul 2 ranges from the Soul Society: The Sneak Entry arc to the end of the Soul Society: The Rescue arc[2] and features 12 playable characters. As opposed to Heat the Soul's story mode, however, this game allows you to follow the story of the selected character rather than a single, designated plot. For example, if you were to choose Ichigo Kurosaki, you would fight all his battles with the shinigami, whereas if you chose to play as Byakuya Kuchiki, you must stop Ichigo and his friends from saving Rukia Kuchiki.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bleach 2 - Heat Of The Soul-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bleach 2 - Heat Of The Soul-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bleach 2 - Heat Of The Soul-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bleach 2 - Heat Of The Soul-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20050901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154018" />
	</game>
	<game id="28069">
		<path>./SpiderMan 2.ISO</path>
		<name>Spider-Man 2</name>
		<desc>Based off the sequel to the popular 2002 movie of the same name, Spider-Man 2 once again places the player in the Web-Swinger's tights as he goes up against Dr. Octopus in this 3D adventure game.  

Unlike the first game, however, the sequel is much more open-ended (a la Grand Theft Auto: Vice City), allowing Spider-Man free reign to explore New York City, and doing everyday tasks from stopping muggers, bank robberies and car-jackers, to delivering pizzas and snapping photos for the Daily Bugle.  

However, the action becomes even more intense as not only does Spidey have to keep the streets safe in general for the citizens of Manhattan, he also has to face up against such super villains as Rhino, Shocker, Mysterio and Calypso, as well as a few entanglements with the Black Cat along the way to square off against Dr. Octopus and save New York in the process!</desc>
		<image>./images/SpiderMan 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/SpiderMan 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SpiderMan 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SpiderMan 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Vicarious Vision</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Spider-Man</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154023" />
	</game>
	<game id="28699">
		<path>./Darius Burst (Japan).iso</path>
		<name>Darius Burst</name>
		<desc>Darius Burst for PSP is the first new entry in the Darius-series since G-Darius (released in 2002). The plot is set in Darius year 1904. Belser has attacked Darius, which had been revived by immigrants from planet Vadis. The game is now in 3D although it's still a left-to-right scroll-shooter . 

Darius Burst features a few elements new to the series: first of all, you don’t loose any weapon upgrades when you die. Second, there’s a 3-mode burst laser which is basically a revised version of the giant laser weapon featured in G-Darius. This time you don’t need to capture and sacrifice enemy units to use it and you may even absorb certain types of bullets with it.

There are 3 silverhawks: “Legend” (the Darius Gaiden ship) piloted by two terminals referred as TI2 and two unlockables: “Next” (a next generation model) piloted by Riga Practica and “Origin” ship which is the original silverhawk, pilot unknown. Darius Burst is shorter than previous games in the series: there are 11 levels and 8 bosses total. The game features a number of unlockable trials ("Mission mode") and a “Burst mode” which challenges the player to complete the game with a single life.

The soundtrack is composed by Zuntata, Taito’s in-house music band.</desc>
		<image>./images/Darius Burst (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Darius Burst (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Darius Burst (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Darius Burst (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20091224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201001T000209</lastplayed>
		<gametime>203</gametime>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154025" />
	</game>
	<game id="28391">
		<path>./BattleZone.iso</path>
		<name>BattleZone</name>
		<desc>BattleZone for PSP is a fast-paced action game where players pilot agile hover tanks fighting other contestants in arena battles. Select one of six game types (DM, TDM, CTF and three others) in one of eight arenas (e.g. Russian Silo, New Mexico canyon, Arctic Tundra) for the right to wear the BattleZone championship crown. 

Fight the way you want to fight choosing a light, medium, or heavy tank chassis and improving it with your favorite weapons and customizing it with your favorite tweak tune-ups. It's all about personality and choice while beating down AI in single-player, and your friends over WiFi multiplayer. 

The single player campaign simulates a 20-match season on the semi-futuristic BattleZone circuit. Represent one of eight NATO countries and battle for pride against the others in their home arenas across the globe. Each country has a special weapon representing their style of play. Configure your tank by hot-swapping between fifteen weapons that are fully automatic, self-guided, or totally exotic.</desc>
		<image>./images/BattleZone-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/BattleZone-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/BattleZone-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/BattleZone-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Paradigm Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154034" />
	</game>
	<game id="28685">
		<path>./World Series Of Poker.iso</path>
		<name>World Series of Poker</name>
		<desc>The official game of the premier poker tournament, World Series Of Poker allows you to take on some of the greatest poker players in 26 different poker games, earn WSOP bracelets and earn a place in the "WSOP Hall of Fame".

During tournaments, you take part in several tables en route to the final table. Each table consists of 8 players that are automatically replenished with new players when numbers dwindle.
Once the tournament is down to the last 16, you move onto the "featured table", and once down to the last 8, you move onto the final table, where the winner will be decided.

Several famous poker players make an appearance in game including Chris "Jesus" Ferguson, Men the Master and Jennifer Tilly.</desc>
		<image>./images/World Series Of Poker-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/World Series Of Poker-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/World Series Of Poker-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/World Series Of Poker-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Left Field Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Playing cards</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154044" />
	</game>
	<game id="28085">
		<path>./CrashTagTeamRacing.ISO</path>
		<name>Crash Tag Team Racing</name>
		<desc>When Ebeneezer von Clutch, the owner of the famed racetrack amusement park MotorWorld, has the Black Power Gem that maintains his life force stolen, he charges Crash and friends (and foes) to recover the gem and catch the culprit.

Similar to previous racing games in the Crash Bandicoot series, players are able to choose from a variety of characters from the series, including both notable allies and enemies, along with several notable new characters. In addition, Crash Tag Team Racing introduces the ability to 'clash' with another racer, allowing the two to create a hybrid vehicle to cooperatively destroy their opponents.</desc>
		<image>./images/CrashTagTeamRacing-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/CrashTagTeamRacing-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/CrashTagTeamRacing-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/CrashTagTeamRacing-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Radical Software</developer>
		<publisher>Universal</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Crash Bandicoot</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154047" />
	</game>
	<game id="142931">
		<path>./Sims2.iso</path>
		<name>The Sims 2</name>
		<desc>A world created, customized and controlled by you is in your hands now that the Sims 2 is coming to the PSP! Explore Strangetown and uncover the secrets of this classic Sims destination as you work to build out your mansion. Keep your Sanity Meter high by fulfilling your wants and fears so that you don't have a nervous breakdown.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sims2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Sims2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Sims2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sims2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation / Life</genre>
		<family>The Sims</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154055" />
	</game>
	<game id="28463">
		<path>./Tokobot.iso</path>
		<name>Tokobot</name>
		<desc>Tokobot is a puzzle-solving game in which the player takes control of Bolt, a 16-year girl who has been sent to a set of ancient ruins to decipher its clues in order to save the world.  However, Bolt is not alone. She gets help from the Tokobots, a bunch a mechanized men who help Bolt out by forming certain objects such as bridges and ladders to avoid pitfalls and help move objects as well.

The gameplay is similar to Pikmin for the Gamecube, the player controls the Tokobots by highlighting them and sending them to certain areas and complete certain tasks.  The game will start you out with six, but as the levels progress, more Tokobots will be available, the more that can be obtained, the more bigger and powerful machines that can be used.  Likewise, the puzzles get harder as the game progresses as well.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tokobot-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Tokobot-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Tokobot-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tokobot-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154105" />
	</game>
	<game id="28666">
		<path>./Fired Up.ISO</path>
		<name>Fired Up</name>
		<desc>In Fired Up, you take on the role of various members of a resistance cell in an attempt to stop the forces invading your home country using various buggies tricked out with big guns and power ups.

It starts when a country, known only as The Republic, led by a leader known only as "The Iron Lady", invades your homeland. 
From here, you take the roles of the resistance fighters Isabel, Viktoria, Erik and Tim in an effort to stop her plans.

Fired up also includes 8 player ad-hoc multiplayer for getting together with your friends in standard deathmatch games with the vehicles featured during the single player campaign.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fired Up-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Fired Up-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Fired Up-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fired Up-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154113" />
	</game>
	<game id="28377">
		<path>./Alien Syndrome.iso</path>
		<name>Alien Syndrome</name>
		<desc>Alien Syndrome is a top down shooter inspired by Sega's original Alien Syndrome action game. The games story takes place thousands of years in the future; by this point in time mankind has explored many parts of the galaxy and established numerous colonies. One such colony, Seti-Alpha 5 (SAT5), has ceased communications for some reason and it is your job to head to SAT5 and investigate what went wrong. Upon arrival, you encounter the alien syndrome, a force which can mutate man and machine into deadly aliens. These events take place roughly 100 years after those in the original Alien Syndrome game.

When you begin the game you can select one of several characters as well as choose a character specialty (such as demolitions expert, firebug,  seal, tank, and sharpshooter). The specialty you select will determine your initial character stats; as you play through the game you earn levels which provide you points to allocate towards improving your stats. The character stats help determine your characters accuracy in ranged  or close attacks, speed, healing power, resistance to fire/radiation, armor strength, and so on.

Similar to the original game, the action is viewed top down. You'll need to explore the numerous corridors and rooms found on SAT5 and eliminate the numerous alien invaders found there. Mission objectives are often provided to you which need to be completed. Additional weapons, ammo, and other useful items can be found throughout the levels. Your character has a limited amount of energy, and if all energy is lost then you will need to begin again at the last checkpoint crossed.</desc>
		<image>./images/Alien Syndrome-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Alien Syndrome-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Alien Syndrome-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Alien Syndrome-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20070624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Totally Games</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154122" />
	</game>
	<game id="28704">
		<path>./MindQuiz.iso</path>
		<name>Mind Quiz</name>
		<desc>Mind Quiz is brain training game very similar to the Brain Age: Train Your Brain in Minutes a Day! DS title, as both are based on the book; Train Your Brain: 60 Days to a Better Brain by Prof. Ryuta Kawashima.

Like the DS game, your calculations, reflexes, judgment and memory are tested, and there is an option to try and solve a daily series of problems, from which the age of the brain is then computed. It includes 49 exercises in 4 genres of calculation, reflex, judgment, and memory. Mind Quiz was supervised by Dr. Kawashima, the Japanese authority on Functional Brain Imaging.

It also has online gameplay to play against family and friends, and a mock exam, which evaluates comprehensive strength. By establishing new records, a Healing gallery is opened, with images of animals.</desc>
		<image>./images/MindQuiz-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/MindQuiz-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/MindQuiz-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/MindQuiz-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<family>Naruhodo</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>b9f688569021f61b01ae3cbceefe33bd</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154130" />
	</game>
	<game id="28132">
		<path>./Wipeout Pure.iso</path>
		<name>WipEout Pure</name>
		<desc>WipEout Pure is the first adaptation for the PSP of the long-running Wipeout series. Players take part in a futuristic racing league known as the FX300 Racing League and control a fast hovercrafts on tight, cornering tracks, vying for first place in one of many tournaments. There are ten anti-gravity vehicles available to use (two need to be unlocked), each with their own characteristics in speed, handling and acceleration. Vehicles are further divided into classes that are unlocked gradually. In later classes most of the vehicles become much faster and require more precise steering at fast speeds. In the same vein, players can unlock new tournaments.

There are a total of sixteen tracks to race on: twelve designed from the ground up for the PSP, as well as four classic Wipeout tracks. Each track has its own obstacles, as well as weapon pick-ups (both offensive and defensive) and speed boosters. The different game modes include single races, tournaments of sets of races, time trial and zone races. In the zone races the player goes through a number of increasingly difficult zones on his own without the ability to slow down until the vehicle explodes because of collision damage. New game elements are unlocked through the Tournament mode.

The game features wireless play over ad-hoc mode (PSP-to-PSP). It was also the first PSP game to support downloadable content with extra teams, tracks and PSP skins. Some of these packs are only available for specific regional versions. The European version of the game supports game sharing.</desc>
		<image>./images/Wipeout Pure-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Wipeout Pure-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Wipeout Pure-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Wipeout Pure-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Wipeout Pure-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio Liverpool</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Wipeout</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201001T001040</lastplayed>
		<gametime>117</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154132" />
	</game>
	<game id="29174">
		<path>./Passport To London.iso</path>
		<name>Passport To... London</name>
		<desc>An interactive street map application for the PlayStation Portable. The UMD release features city maps of metropolitan districts (one for each European city released separately on disc for the EUR version), with streets, detailed building location markers, hotspot locations (including dining, shops, sight-seeing areas, plus more) and many other details for easy city running. Maps can be zoomed and rotated in any direction. You can mark your own My Spot locations, dotting your map with up to 400 spots, and can trade My Spots with other PSPs via wireless link (ad-hoc). Users can also connect online to download updated info and extensive markings for different locations.</desc>
		<image>./images/Passport To London-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Passport To London-video.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>./images/Passport To London-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<developer>London Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154137" />
	</game>
	<game id="27975">
		<path>./Tekken Dark Resurrection.iso</path>
		<name>Tekken : Dark Resurrection</name>
		<desc>The power of the greatest fighting dynasty... in the pal of your hands.

Tekken: Dark Resurrection has arrived on the PSP system. Fight with new characters Lili and Dragunov or other favorites including Jin, Heihachi, and Armor King.

-Wireless ad hoc battle with up to 2 players to prove who is the real champion.
-Customize your character with twice the items and share your creation using the Ghost feature.
-Play mini-games in ad hoc mode or individually for a change in the action.
-Stunning graphics on 19 stages of pain.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tekken Dark Resurrection-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Tekken Dark Resurrection-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Tekken Dark Resurrection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tekken Dark Resurrection-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Tekken Dark Resurrection-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20060725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thunder Mountain</developer>
		<publisher>Thunder Mountain</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Tekken</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154142" />
	</game>
	<game id="28245">
		<path>./Rocky Balboa.iso</path>
		<name>Rocky Balboa</name>
		<desc>Rocky Balboa is a 2007 video game based on the movie of the same name for the PlayStation Portable, which is similar in style and content to Rocky Legends. The game includes footage from each Rocky film, showing the buildup to the major fights of the film series. There are also some flashback videos of the training footage from the films (this is used in the Mickey's Corner section of the game, which is a tutorial aimed to teach new players how to play).</desc>
		<image>./images/Rocky Balboa-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Rocky Balboa-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Rocky Balboa-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rocky Balboa-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Fiction</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154150" />
	</game>
	<game id="28012">
		<path>./Need For Speed Underground Rivals.ISO</path>
		<name>Need for Speed : Underground Rivals</name>
		<desc>Customize 20 tuner cars and race on 10 new circuit tracks.

Eight modes including Drift Attack, and Rally Relay

Tune your ride performance and style

Special Features: 
   Wireless and Party Play Multiplayer Modes
   EAâ„¢ Pocket TRAX Music Visualization Player</desc>
		<image>./images/Need For Speed Underground Rivals-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Need For Speed Underground Rivals-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Need For Speed Underground Rivals-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Need For Speed Underground Rivals-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Need For Speed Underground Rivals-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Need for Speed</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154154" />
	</game>
	<game id="28228">
		<path>./Twisted Metal Head On.iso</path>
		<name>Twisted Metal : Head On</name>
		<desc>Get ready for the next installment in the Twisted Metal car combat series. Twisted Metal: Head-On puts you behind the wheel of one of 14 destructive vehicles, each equipped with machine guns, turbo boost, and a unique special attack. Once you select a vehicle, you can take out your road rage on opponents in 12 wild arenas. The game also offers multiplayer modes for up to eight players through a wireless connection.</desc>
		<image>./images/Twisted Metal Head On-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Twisted Metal Head On-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Twisted Metal Head On-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Twisted Metal Head On-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Twisted Metal Head On-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incognito Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vehicle, 3rd person</genre>
		<family>Twisted Metal</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154157" />
	</game>
	<game id="28492">
		<path>./Lumines 2.iso</path>
		<name>Lumines II</name>
		<desc>The sequel to the Lumines stays close the original puzzle game, but add some twists. The gameplay is identical: you arrange blocks, made of four smaller block pieces with two colours in total, to form shapes with an identical colour, as a square of four pieces or more. The blocks can be rotated and are stacked with the other blocks on the board. A vertical line crosses the screen and when it hits the right side, all combinations are removed, causing chain combos and clearing the board. You have to prevent the blocks from piling up and reaching the top of the screen. There are also special blocks you can use to remove many blocks at once. Games are played against colorful backgrounds and the speed of the timeline matches the music of the level, while the falling speed of the blocks increases as you get further in the game.

The game modes are either new or have been remixed. In the single-player Challenge mode, there are three difficulty classes. By clearing levels you unlock new music, skins and game modes. One of these are the Endurance challenge runs, where you have to play through all skins in the game. Next to games with regular skins, some backgrounds now have 3D animations or show music videos of popular artists. The sound effects and the design of blocks is often adapted to fit the music. For levels with music video skins, you cannot play through them at a quicker pace to clear the level as you have to keep going until the song ends.

The other single-player modes are Time Attack mode (get a high score with limited time, you can even record your session) and Puzzle mode where you need to create shapes. You can also challenge the computer in the VS CPU Mode. Here, you need to score more than your opponent to make his playing field smaller until he gets stuck. This game type is also available as the Duel mode against a human player through Wi-Fi. The order of the skins can be defined in the new Skin Edit mode. The Single Lap section allows you to make your own playlists for a set run, while the Endless Lap allows you to choose or exclude skins to keep playing as long as you like. There are 60 levels and 100 skins in total.

Another new feature is the Mission mode where more strategy is required. You are given specific tasks to clear boards with a limited amount of blocks or time. In the new Sequencer mode, you can compose your own songs. The game provides options to define the speed and 8 separate music sheets to place notes and effects on. The high scores, playlists from the Skin Edit mode, songs from the Sequencer mode and replays of the Time Attack mode can be exchanged with other players through Wi-Fi. Your performance is tracked in the Database mode where statistics of your playing sessions are available. The game also includes a demo of Every Extend Extra, another puzzle game by Q ENTERTAINMENT, Inc.</desc>
		<image>./images/Lumines 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Lumines 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Lumines 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Lumines 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Buena Vista Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154204" />
	</game>
	<game id="28229">
		<path>./ATV Off Road Fury.iso</path>
		<name>ATV Offroad Fury Pro</name>
		<desc>ATV Offroad Fury Pro is an offroad racing game which was released alongside with ATV Offroad Fury 4. Besides the expected ATV (all-terrain vehicles) there are also a variety of other vehicles to race with, e.g. trucks or bikes, which is the foundation of the career mode: participating in a string of championships which are divided in vehicle type and difficulty. Upgrades and additional vehicles are purchased with credits which can be earned in a number of ways: besides price money for winning races, credits are also awarded for performing stunts. There are also three sponsors which offer free upgrades and/or credits for fulfilling their demands regarding performance and stunt rating, but they should be hired with caution because a big penalty is assigned for missed goals. The available types of races are Supercross, Rallycross, National, Freestyle, Circuit, Endurcross, Rally and Snowcross.

Besides a basic course editor and multiplayer for up to four players (which is also the maximum number of racers in single-player) there are also connectivity features with ATV Offroad Fury 4 which allow to exchange courses/vehicles and access a shared online community.</desc>
		<image>./images/ATV Off Road Fury-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/ATV Off Road Fury-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/ATV Off Road Fury-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/ATV Off Road Fury-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20061026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154211" />
	</game>
	<game id="144546">
		<path>./Namco Museum.iso</path>
		<name>Namco Museum</name>
		<desc>All your favorite Namco classics are now in one package. Namco Museum 1 includes Pac-Man, Ms. Pac-Man, Galaga, Galaxian, Dig Dug, and Pole Position. But the fun doesn't stop there, since Namco has added all new arrangement modes plus other hidden games. Whether it's eating ghosts, shooting aliens, digging a hole, or racing toward the finish line, the addictive gameplay of Namco Museum has proven it can stand the test of time</desc>
		<image>./images/Namco Museum-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Namco Museum-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Namco Museum-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050224T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154215" />
	</game>
	<game id="28036">
		<path>./Star Wars Lethal Alliance.iso</path>
		<name>Star Wars : Lethal Alliance</name>
		<desc>To capture the plans for the Death Star and make it back home safely, players must guide Rianna Saren and her trusty droid Zeeo through a variety of Star Wars environments while avoiding or attacking Imperial soldiers and their allies. Rianna is gifted in combat and Zeeo comes in handy for unlocking security doors, reaching high places, and bypassing dangerous areas. The story of Star Wars: Lethal Alliance unfolds between Episode III and Episode IV, when Princess Leia recruits the duo to steal the plans so the Rebels may learn any weaknesses in the massive weapon. Players will explore such areas as Tatooine, Despayre, Alderaan, and Danuta while interacting with characters including Boba Fett, Darth Vader, and Kyle Katarn. The PSP features various mini-games and multiplayer Twil'lek vs. Twi'lek combat over a wireless network.</desc>
		<image>./images/Star Wars Lethal Alliance-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Star Wars Lethal Alliance-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Star Wars Lethal Alliance-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Star Wars Lethal Alliance-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<family>Star Wars</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154221" />
	</game>
	<game id="28553">
		<path>./Grip shift.iso</path>
		<name>Gripshift</name>
		<desc>Gripshift is a driving game with a twist. It combines racing with puzzles and even some platform action. 

The game is built around a tour mode where the player must complete the stages one by one. Clear these stages by driving fast to the finish or try to top the times required to obtain bronze, silver, and gold medals. There are also stars to collect and a hidden item on every stage to discover. All of the levels are afloat in the air, so if the player happens to drift off the course, the car drops into nothingness.

There are many multiplayer modes, including bonus games such as soccer, ice hockey and a Snake game played with cars. In the track editor, players can construct their own gravity-defying tracks and share them through a wireless connection.</desc>
		<image>./images/Grip shift-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Grip shift-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Grip shift-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Grip shift-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Sidhe Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154228" />
	</game>
	<game id="27964">
		<path>./Killzone Liberation.iso</path>
		<name>Killzone : Liberation</name>
		<desc>In Killzone: Liberation, two months after the events of "Killzone," (PS2) most of southern Vekta is still under Helghast control. The rules of war have been cast aside with the Helghast General, Metrac, employing brutal measures in order to seize the initiative and strengthen his position further. Returning as Templar, players will be sent on a mission to undertake a covert operation to save hostages captured by Metrac, while ISA troops continue the fight for liberty. Featuring an intelligent third person camera system, Killzone: Liberation allows players a more tactical surveillance viewpoint to view their action and read the enemy's behavior during gameplay. Set in an intense postmodern war reminiscent of the previous PS2 title, Killzone: Liberation features the unique graphical style to showcase pure grit and realism. During gameplay, players will have access to variety of weapons that are unique and innovative, inspired by modern military equipment.</desc>
		<image>./images/Killzone Liberation-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Killzone Liberation-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Killzone Liberation-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Killzone Liberation-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Guerrilla</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Killzone</family>
		<players>2-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154234" />
	</game>
	<game id="27938">
		<path>./Daxter.iso</path>
		<name>Daxter</name>
		<desc>Daxter stars for the first time on his own in this action-platformer that reveals how he became a hero and freed Jak at the beginning of Jak II. Finally able to explore past the secure boundaries of Haven City, Daxter inadvertently takes on a job as a pest exterminator, a task the Old Sage intuitively knew he was proficient at since the first Jak and Daxter. Armed with a fly swatter and soon afterwards a spray canister that allows him to not only stun bugs but to hover in the air, Daxter unravels to the player the introduction of the upcoming invasion that occurred in Jak II into Haven City. The invasion is led by the Metal Heads who are using bug-like variations called Metal Bugs to permeate the city. Later upgrades include a flame thrower attachment as well as a detonator weapon.

Daxter's path towards freeing Jak involves a series of platforming and combat challenges through a wide variety of environments ranging from a high speed transit system to a fish cannery, and all the way to the Krimson Guard fortress where Daxter has to sneak past the guards to eventually save Jak.

Daxter features a variety of vehicle levels, minigames typical of the Jak series, as well as a series of dream level sequences that take Daxter into a realm where he is the hero. The dream minigames spoof cinematic moments from The Matrix, Indiana Jones, Braveheart and Lord of the Rings. Wi-fi multiplayer mode of Bug combat is included, where players can use their trained collected bugs to fight each other.</desc>
		<image>./images/Daxter-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Daxter-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Daxter-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Daxter-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Daxter-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ready At Dawn Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Jak And Daxter</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154242" />
	</game>
	<game id="28298">
		<path>./GunShowdown.iso</path>
		<name>GUN Showdown</name>
		<desc>GUN Showdown puts players in the role of Colton White, a vengeful gunslinger making his way through the untamed West of the late-1800s where the lines between good and evil are blurred and greed, lust and brutality were a way of life. The game features all of the action contained in the console versions, as well as all-new side missions, quick-play modes, multiplayer modes and gameplay features that are unique to the PSP system.</desc>
		<image>./images/GunShowdown-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/GunShowdown-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/GunShowdown-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/GunShowdown-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/GunShowdown-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Gun</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154250" />
	</game>
	<game id="144206">
		<path>./Guilty gear X.iso</path>
		<name>Guilty Gear Xx Reload</name>
		<image>./images/Guilty gear X-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Guilty gear X-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Guilty gear X-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Guilty gear X-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc System Works</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / 2D</genre>
		<family>Guilty Gear</family>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154302" />
	</game>
	<game id="28362">
		<path>./Miami Vice.iso</path>
		<name>Miami Vice : The Game</name>
		<desc>Miami Vice is a third-person shooter for the PlayStation Portable. It was released as a tie-in with the movie of the same name. Therefore, the likeness of the narcotics officers Crockett and Tubbs are based on that of Colin Farrell and Jamie Foxx, respectively.

While going through levels, the majority of the gameplay is combat, with enemies who must be killed to advance the level. Emphasis is put on taking cover, with health running out quite fast if player remains in the open during a shoot-out. All fire-arms have laser sightings, which acts as an aiming reticule.

The player may also deal drugs amongst other suppliers, both buying and selling. Drugs can be bought at one point and kept for several days, in which they may increase in value, thus making a profit for the player. Additionally, varying drugs can be obtained throughout each of the levels, and sold for a profit once the level is complete. Drugs can also be sold to informants for information.</desc>
		<image>./images/Miami Vice-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Miami Vice-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Miami Vice-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Miami Vice-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Universal</developer>
		<publisher>Rebellion</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154309" />
	</game>
	<game id="28156">
		<path>./Key Of Heaven.iso</path>
		<name>Kingdom of Paradise</name>
		<desc>Five great gates of Ouka be,

Name them here for all to see;
Sieryu, Byakko and Genbu
Kirin and Suzaku be there too;
At Heavenâ€™s gate twin keys you need;
At Earthâ€™s gates, bows the Divine Steed;
The soul is born as the Yang moon whirls
The body is born as the Yin moon twirls
The twin moons make a mighty hum
From the watery moon, it doth come.</desc>
		<image>./images/Key Of Heaven-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Key Of Heaven-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Key Of Heaven-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Key Of Heaven-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20051115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154317" />
	</game>
	<game id="29034">
		<path>./World Snooker Challenge 2005.ISO</path>
		<name>World Snooker Challenge 2005</name>
		<desc>World Snooker Championship 2005 on PSP is a very exhaustive billiards simulation offering you the possibility to indulge in the various variants that are the 8-pool, the Snooker Plus but also the Billiard Bar or the Carambola. Whether it is forging a career in the most prestigious tournaments of this small world or partly relaxed, come and try the tail.</desc>
		<image>./images/World Snooker Challenge 2005-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/World Snooker Challenge 2005-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/World Snooker Challenge 2005-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/World Snooker Challenge 2005-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<developer>Blade Interactive Studios</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154322" />
	</game>
	<game id="28759">
		<path>./PAC-MAN_Championship_Edition_USA.iso</path>
		<name>Pac-man Championship Edition</name>
		<desc>Pac-Man Championship Edition is similar in basic gameplay to the original 1980 Pac-Man: players have to eat dots, while avoiding the four ghosts that roam around the maze. Championship Edition, however, also brings many gameplay differences.

The game was designed by the creator of the classic original 1980 arcade game Pac-Man, and it was Iwatani's final game before his retirement.</desc>
		<image>./images/PAC-MAN_Championship_Edition_USA-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/PAC-MAN_Championship_Edition_USA-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/PAC-MAN_Championship_Edition_USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/PAC-MAN_Championship_Edition_USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<family>Pac-Man</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154328" />
	</game>
	<game id="28200">
		<path>./Metal_Slug_XX_USA.iso</path>
		<name>Metal Slug XX</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug XX is an entry in the long-running series of side-scrolling shooters. It is a revised version of Metal Slug 7. The Peregrine Falcons, Marco, Eri, Clark, Tarma, Fio and Ralf, are once again running-and-gunning in colorfully hand-drawn levels, throwing grenades, driving vehicles and slashing enemies.

Metal Slug XX includes various single-player features in the form of a Combat School that lets players return to previously completed missions while executing various objectives; a POW List that shows how many POWs were rescued in each level; and single-player Rankings. Players can also cooperate in Ad-Hoc while gunning down hordes of humorous foes using familiar weapons in seven distinct levels that will see our heroes traverse deserts, mountains, caves and lava pits to finally put an end to their longtime enemy.

This revised version includes additional content including co-op multiplayer and downloadable content, as well as the character Leona Heidern.</desc>
		<image>./images/Metal_Slug_XX_USA-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Metal_Slug_XX_USA-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Metal_Slug_XX_USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Metal_Slug_XX_USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Metal_Slug_XX_USA-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20100223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DHM Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Run and Gun</genre>
		<family>Metal Slug</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201001T000620</lastplayed>
		<gametime>72</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154338" />
	</game>
	<game id="28821">
		<path>./Solitaire_USA.iso</path>
		<name>Solitaire</name>
		<desc>So you thought you were the king of solitaire? Swot up on your classics!
Take the first and most popular of all card games with you wherever you go, whether you're on public transport or in a waiting room, with a spare 5 minutes or an hour to kill! You're never alone when you've got solitaire.</desc>
		<image>./images/Solitaire_USA-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Solitaire_USA-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Solitaire_USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Solitaire_USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20100804T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bigben Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Bigben Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Playing cards</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>b53b82360661740cccd609ba9983fd30</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154345" />
	</game>
	<game id="28493">
		<path>./Activision Hits Remixed.iso</path>
		<name>Activision Hits Remixed</name>
		<desc>Activision Hits Remixed lets PSP system gamers relive the dawn of home console gaming while on the go by delivering over 40 of the biggest Atari 2600 titles, such as Pitfall, Kaboom!, Chopper Command, Stampede, Keystone Kapers, to the PSP. With the game's multi-player supported classics, players can choose whether they want to game together utilizing a Game Share feature that allows two friends to play together using only one copy of the game or take turns on one PSP system or play via the game's wireless functionality. Activision Hits Remixed also features a rockin' 80's themed soundtrack, modernized front-end graphics, classic game manuals which include tips and photographs, and a host of retro unlockables.</desc>
		<image>./images/Activision Hits Remixed-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Activision Hits Remixed-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Activision Hits Remixed-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Activision Hits Remixed-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154353" />
	</game>
	<game id="28623">
		<path>./Star Trek Tactical Assault.iso</path>
		<name>Star Trek : Tactical Assault</name>
		<desc>Star Trek: Tactical Assault is a Star Trek video game for the Nintendo DS and PlayStation Portable that was developed by Quicksilver Software, also the creators of Star Trek: Starfleet Command</desc>
		<image>./images/Star Trek Tactical Assault-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Star Trek Tactical Assault-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Star Trek Tactical Assault-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Star Trek Tactical Assault-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>QuickSilver</developer>
		<publisher>Bethesda Softworks</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Star Trek</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154400" />
	</game>
	<game id="28352">
		<path>./Moto GP.iso</path>
		<name>Moto GP</name>
		<desc>MotoGP is a motorcycle racing game based on the 2005 MotoGP season. It features all the riders from that 2005 season, but only eight of the seventeen circuits. There are two main modes of play, arcade and season. Arcade allows the player to select any rider and track to race on. Season mode allows the player to take part in a complete season with one 'real-life' rider, or alternatively to compete over multiple seasons with a fictional rider, with the ability to move teams at the end of the season depending on the performance during the season. Different levels of difficulty relating to the realism of the bikes handling and performance are offered to cater for both novice and more experienced players. All the usual setup options are available to tune the bikes for each track.</desc>
		<image>./images/Moto GP-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Moto GP-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Moto GP-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Moto GP-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving / Motorcycle</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154408" />
	</game>
	<game id="28378">
		<path>./Outrun 2006 Coast 2 Coast.iso</path>
		<name>OutRun 2006 : Coast 2 Coast</name>
		<desc>OutRun 2006: Coast to Coast features a choice of 15 fully licensed Ferrari models, featuring the all-new F430 and F430 Spider, as well as the dazzling Superamerica and the stunning 550 Barchetta. Power your way across 15 new American themed environments from the "OutRun2 SP" arcade experience. Race from coast to glorious coast with a fresh new mission structure, a license mode and online play, with up to 6 players for a thrilling head-to-head journey.</desc>
		<video>./videos/Outrun 2006 Coast 2 Coast-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Outrun 2006 Coast 2 Coast-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Outrun 2006 Coast 2 Coast-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Outrun 2006 Coast 2 Coast-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>OutRun</family>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154419" />
	</game>
	<game id="142887">
		<path>./Scooby Doo Whos Watching Who.iso</path>
		<name>Scooby-Doo! : Who's Watching Who</name>
		<desc>The gang from Mystery Inc. are the stars of a hit reality TV show about ghost hunting. However, when rival show team GSI (Ghost Scene Investigators) question Mystery Inc's unscientific methods of ghost detection, the challenge is on to see who can debunk the most ghosts! Scooby, Shaggy and the gang will travel cross-country visiting spooky locations and unmasking classic ghosts. Are their old-fashioned methods up to the challenge?</desc>
		<image>./images/Scooby Doo Whos Watching Who-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Scooby Doo Whos Watching Who-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Scooby Doo Whos Watching Who-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Scooby Doo Whos Watching Who-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20061016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Savage Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Scooby-doo</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154427" />
	</game>
	<game id="28857">
		<path>./Ford Bold Moves Street.ISO</path>
		<name>Ford Bold Moves Street Racing</name>
		<desc>(Known in the UK/EU as "Ford Street Racing: LA Duel") Now featuring 24 officially licensed Ford vehicles, classics such as the 1971 Mustang Mach 1 join the already prestigious roster, as well as scorching hot supercars like the 2005 Shelby GR-1 Concept. The Maximum Team Control Racing features have been expanded to 11 different modes, each designed to exploit different aspects of team racings such as blocking, drafting, and switching. Multiplayer has also been enhanced to include both team and solo racing options, utilizing the wireless capabilities of the PSP system for high velocity head-to-head racing battles</desc>
		<image>./images/Ford Bold Moves Street-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ford Bold Moves Street-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ford Bold Moves Street-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ford Bold Moves Street-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<developer>RazorWorks</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Ford Racing</family>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154438" />
	</game>
	<game id="88707">
		<path>./Champ Manager 2006.iso</path>
		<name>Championship Manager</name>
		<desc>This first portable edition of the most famous brand of football management simulation Championship Manager arrives on PSP. It's based on Championship Manager 5, the first game developed after original developers SI left Eidos and the CM brand behind.

Players can manage teams in any of 55 leagues from 12 countries, and watch their matches play out in a 2D engine. Exclusive content for the PSP include a new Challenge mode and a quick play 3 season mode. Also, by hooking up your PSP to your PC over USB, you can update the game roster and stats throughout the season.</desc>
		<image>./images/Champ Manager 2006-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Champ Manager 2006-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Champ Manager 2006-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Champ Manager 2006-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20051209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gusto Games</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation / Build And Management</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154444" />
	</game>
	<game id="28223">
		<path>./Field Commander.cso</path>
		<name>Field Commander</name>
		<desc>Field Commander is a turn-based strategy game where players take to the field and guide their division to victory by outsmarting, outmaneuvering and outgunning their opponents. You have been recruited by ATLAS (Advanced Tactical Legion for Allied Security) to defend the world against different cover organizations. As a field commander, you are give a selection of allied troops and technology to complete your tasks. Jump into the singleplayer game with your choice of 15 different divisions while you combat your enemy through 30 missions. Rise to the top of the leaderboards with 36 different units while you play against others across the street or across the world with it's online capabilities. You can even create your own missions and share them with your friends.

Multiplayer supports Ad-Hoc, Infrastructure, Hotswap (two players on a single PSP) and Transmission Mode (similar to Play by Email)</desc>
		<image>./images/Field Commander-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Field Commander-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Field Commander-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Field Commander-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Field Commander-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20060523T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Daybreak Game Company</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154458" />
	</game>
	<game id="78586">
		<path>./Kameleon.iso</path>
		<name>Chameleon: To Dye For!</name>
		<desc>Chameleon: To Dye For! is a 2006 puzzle video game released for the PlayStation Portable (PSP) and the Nintendo DS. In Japan, the game is called Kuru Kuru Chameleon. In North America, the game is titled simply Chameleon on the PSP, while it goes under the name Kameleon for all systems in Europe. This game offers players simple controls and competitive play in the attempt to match colours on the playfield. The game features several playable characters along with a bonus character. Each character has her own special power, which can be used to hinder the opponent. Wireless play is also available.</desc>
		<image>./images/Kameleon-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Kameleon-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Kameleon-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kameleon-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20080505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Starfish</developer>
		<publisher>UFO Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>961b1ffb7adc0e563f7a791c7ebcaba1</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154511" />
	</game>
	<game id="28417">
		<path>./Coded Arms.iso</path>
		<name>Coded Arms</name>
		<desc>Coded Arms is a first-person shooter game for the PSP. You play as a future hacker, who uses technologies to jack his brain into computer networks. The entire game takes place in a virtual reality world inside a computer network. This world was created as a combat simulator for an alien invasion. Even though the program was canceled, it kept running and growing inside the network. You infiltrate the world to neutralize it.

The game offers six sectors to explore, each containing several sub-sections. Each of them has a good selection of different types of weapons you can collect during the levels. Coded Arms also uses “The Matrix”-style effects. There are three multiplayer types with support up to four players: Deathmatch, Keep the Mark and Last Man Standing.</desc>
		<image>./images/Coded Arms-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Coded Arms-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Coded Arms-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Coded Arms-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Coded Arms-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050706T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154523" />
	</game>
	<game id="27884">
		<path>./MediEvil Resurrection.ISO</path>
		<name>MediEvil : Resurrection</name>
		<desc>The PSP installment in this series takes place 100 years after the evil sorcerer Zarok was defeated at the Battle of Gallowmere. Now Zarok has returned with his undead army to conquer the land. It's up to you, as Sir Daniel Fortesque, to defeat Zarok and his minions with your varied combat moves and weapons. Seek out the voodoo witch to learn more about your abilities and environments. In addition to a single-player campaign, MediEval features several multiplayer minigames.</desc>
		<image>./images/MediEvil Resurrection-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/MediEvil Resurrection-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/MediEvil Resurrection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/MediEvil Resurrection-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/MediEvil Resurrection-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>SCEE Studio Cambridge</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154538" />
	</game>
	<game id="28289">
		<path>./Toca Race Driver 2.iso</path>
		<name>Toca Race Driver 2 - Ultimate Racing Simulator</name>
		<desc>TOCA Race Driver 2: The Ultimate Racing Simulator (V8 Supercars 2 in Australia, DTM Race Driver 2 in Germany) is a racing video game installment of the racing video game TOCA Touring Car series, released on Xbox and Microsoft Windows in April 2004, with a PlayStation 2 version following six months later.</desc>
		<image>./images/Toca Race Driver 2-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Toca Race Driver 2-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Toca Race Driver 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Toca Race Driver 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Toca Race Driver 2-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20050901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154601" />
	</game>
	<game id="27903">
		<path>./Valkyrie.iso</path>
		<name>Valkyrie Profile : Lenneth</name>
		<desc>Asgard, the realm of the gods, remains locked in an eternal struggle between the benevolent Aesir and the demonic Vanir. With the end of the world approaching, Odin, Lord of Asgard, summons Lenneth Valkyrie to his side. Possessing the ability to hear the thoughts and feelings of men and women in their dying moments, he charges Valkyrie to search Midgard, the world of mortals, to recruit and train the souls of worthy warriors to join the ranks of the Aesir in the Sacred War. Valkyrie Profile: Lenneth brings the classic PlayStationÂ® game console title, originally released in 2000, to the PSP system with completely new CG cut scenes. tri-Ace, the developers behind the acclaimed Star Ocean series and "Radiata Stories", introduce new fans to the spectacular combo attacks, unique side-scrolling environment, and gripping storyline that first captivated players six years ago. To give players a deeper understanding of the plot and to complement the game's dramatic storyline, additional CG cutscenes have been incorporated. Some of these new scenes contain links to the story of "Valkyrie Profile 2: Silmeria".</desc>
		<image>./images/Valkyrie-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Valkyrie-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Valkyrie-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Valkyrie-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060718T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tri-Ace</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154627" />
	</game>
	<game id="27975">
		<path>./Tekken - Dark Resurrection.iso</path>
		<name>Tekken : Dark Resurrection</name>
		<desc>The power of the greatest fighting dynasty... in the pal of your hands.

Tekken: Dark Resurrection has arrived on the PSP system. Fight with new characters Lili and Dragunov or other favorites including Jin, Heihachi, and Armor King.

-Wireless ad hoc battle with up to 2 players to prove who is the real champion.
-Customize your character with twice the items and share your creation using the Ghost feature.
-Play mini-games in ad hoc mode or individually for a change in the action.
-Stunning graphics on 19 stages of pain.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tekken - Dark Resurrection-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Tekken - Dark Resurrection-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Tekken - Dark Resurrection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tekken - Dark Resurrection-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Tekken - Dark Resurrection-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20060725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thunder Mountain</developer>
		<publisher>Thunder Mountain</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Tekken</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200927T112441</lastplayed>
		<gametime>535</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154628" />
	</game>
	<game id="29108">
		<path>./Star Soldier.iso</path>
		<name>Star Soldier</name>
		<desc>Star Soldier is a budget remake of the classic top-down shooter which puts you behind the cockpit of a lone starfighter as you attempt to stop an alien invasion.

This PSP remake features a completely new polygonal engine with new stages, enemies and weapons. Additionally the game has been specifically redesigned for the PSP's 16:9 screen, meaning you have to turn the console on its side to play the game in a vertical orientation.</desc>
		<image>./images/Star Soldier-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Star Soldier-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Star Soldier-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Star Soldier-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Star Soldier-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050721T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>6f803a4dd371681c2034851c30178d79</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154643" />
	</game>
	<game id="28146">
		<path>./Fight NightRound 3.iso</path>
		<name>Fight Night Round 3</name>
		<desc>Fight Night Round 3 was developed by EA Chicago, formerly NuFX. It is the third boxing title in the Fight Night franchise. It features the usual improvements such as better graphics and gameplay. "Impact Punches" are one of the most drastic changes, along with ESPN Classic fights and a new career mode, in which the player fights to gain popularity in order to reach sponsored fights, or to be featured on ESPN. Unlike in older versions, Round 3 defaults without a heads-up display (HUD), allowing a player to judge the status of their stamina and energy based on their stance, movements, and facial features, instead of the usual stamina meter.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fight NightRound 3-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Fight NightRound 3-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Fight NightRound 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fight NightRound 3-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Fight NightRound 3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Boxing</genre>
		<family>Fight Night</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154656" />
	</game>
	<game id="27979">
		<path>./The Godfather Mob Wars.iso</path>
		<name>The Godfather : Mob Wars</name>
		<desc>Based on the 1972 film of the same name, The Godfather immerses you in the dangerous world of the Mafia. The game features GTA-style gameplay, a new storyline, and voice-acting by original cast members. Take control of the Corleone Family and make New York City your own. Intimidate and earn the loyalty of your peers as you battle the Tattaglia, Cuneo, Barzini and Stracci families. Engage in a turf war as you take over territory in the strategic Mob Wars mode unique to PSP.</desc>
		<image>./images/The Godfather Mob Wars-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/The Godfather Mob Wars-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/The Godfather Mob Wars-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Godfather Mob Wars-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154715" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman USA.cso</path>
		<name>Bomberman</name>
		<desc>Bomberman arrives on the PSP with nostalgic gameplay and a new twist for the next generation of wireless, mobile gaming. An ominous black shadow is creeping towards Bomberman's planet, and sudden attacks by a mysterious robot army have brain-washed the inhabitants of surrounding planets, causing mass chaos. Bomberman must embark on a new adventure through the galaxy to restore peace and order. Normal Mode: the latest Bomberman complete with a new story and 100 levels featuring a new Item Stock system allowing for the collection and strategic use of more items. Classic Mode: based on original classic Bomberman featuring over 50 different levels. Multiplayer Battle Mode: up to 4 players can fight for survival in a variety of highly customizable games across 20 different stages via wireless ad hoc mode. Game Sharing: Up to 4 players can battle from 1 UMD game disc.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bomberman USA-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Bomberman USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bomberman USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060720T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200930T235808</lastplayed>
		<md5>45ac12bcc89ae9272e5cf1fc466d0de7</md5>
		<gametime>95</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154716" />
	</game>
	<game id="28061">
		<path>./Patapon.cso</path>
		<name>Patapon</name>
		<desc>Set among a variety of colorful 2D backgrounds, Patapon unfolds through more than 30 missions with more than 20 different environments, where players are tasked with outfitting the Patapon army, collecting resources, and using strategy to grow the tribe into a devastating fighting force. Incorporating various button-timed drumbeats in real-time to control the Patapons, players will strategically traverse through each environment, battling enemies each step of the way. The game presents a variety of warrior types such as archers, infantry, cavalry, and more that players can unlock, along with a wide selection of more than 100 weapon and shield upgrades, allowing players to customize their forces throughout the funky adventure.</desc>
		<image>./images/Patapon-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Patapon-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Patapon-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Patapon-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Patapon-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20080226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pyramid</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154718" />
	</game>
	<game id="28965">
		<path>./NFL Street 2 Unleashed.ISO</path>
		<name>NFL Street 2 Unleashed</name>
		<desc>Get ready for more fancy moves, new modes, and wireless gameplay in the PSP version of NFL Street 2. Now you can jump 15 feet high to make catches off the wall, dive into the end zone, or pull off wild jukes. You can master these new abilities in seven new game modes, including "crush the carrier" and "own the city." Create your own player, master new skills, and then hit the streets.</desc>
		<image>./images/NFL Street 2 Unleashed-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/NFL Street 2 Unleashed-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/NFL Street 2 Unleashed-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/NFL Street 2 Unleashed-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>EA Sports</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154738" />
	</game>
	<game id="27935">
		<path>./Test Drive Unlimited.ISO</path>
		<name>Test Drive Unlimited</name>
		<desc>Test Drive Unlimited lets the player choose one of several characters, both male and female, waiting at an airport to check in for their flight to the Caribbean dream island O'ahu located in Hawaii. The characters do not have different statistics, that only applies to the extravagant, licensed cars.

The whole island is accessible from the beginning and after the player has bought his first home and car, he can either drive around and look for events or load up the map and jump directly to a location of a race, a car salesman or other locations - similar to Need for Speed Underground. Every bought car has a built-in navigation system, guided by a woman's voice to get the player to his destination, either pre-programmed in the game or decided by the player.

There are over 125 different cars and motorcycles in different price ranges to choose from. From the Audi TT over the Jaguar XJ200 to the McLaren F1 and Kawasaki Z1000, there is everything the character needs as a young man or girl with too much money on their hands. Each car has its own, realistic set of characteristics such as speed or handling, but they all have a highly detailed exterior and interior in common.

The character starts with $200.000 dollars in his pocket, but there will not be anything left after buying a first car and home. Additional cash needs to be earned in different kinds of races from checkpoint challenges to time trials. The money cannot only be used to buy new homes and new cars (and a little tuning for those), but also to buy new outfits for the avatar.

The heart of Test Drive Unlimited is the online mode. Using a GameSpy account, players connect to the official TDU server immediately after loading the game. New options become available online, such as a meeting lounge where the statistics and looks of other players can be looked up. It also provides access to player-created matches shown on the map screen. Creating a race  here also works in the singleplayer modes. At any location, the start and finish can be defined, as well as the type of the race, which type/classes of cars or bikes are allowed and how many people can participate. If not all slots have been filled up by other players, the AI will take control of the rest.

The PSP and PS2 versions have a lower visual quality and lack a few features, such as manual transmission, avatar customization, certain cars and all motorcycles, dealership and tuning shop NPCs, the vehicle interior camera angle and certain missions. They do include Master Points and Auto GPS, and certain default vehicles only available for the 360 version through download packs.</desc>
		<image>./images/Test Drive Unlimited-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Test Drive Unlimited-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Test Drive Unlimited-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Test Drive Unlimited-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20070321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Test Drive</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154753" />
	</game>
	<game id="28244">
		<path>./F1 Grand Prix.ISO</path>
		<name>F1 Grand Prix</name>
		<desc>FIA licensed Formula 1 racing game including the 2005 season teams, drivers, cars, and circuits.  The player controls the car on the track and tries to either complete a lap in fastest possible time, or race against either computer controlled drivers (or in multiplayer mode, against other players) and finish in top position.

Game can be played in Quick Grand Prix, Event, World Championship, and Multiplayer modes.  Quick Grand Prix selects a random car and circuit to race.  Event modes are Time Attack (race against ghost car), Single Grand Prix, and Scenario Mode in which the player needs to complete different kinds of racing tasks such as completing a lap with failed brakes and pitting in to fix them.  Each successfully completed scenario unlocks the next one.  Additional scenarios are available for download to PSP.

World Championship mode lets the player to choose the team to race in and the championship season difficulty.  All 19 circuits of the 2005 F1 season are raced in order and points for finishing in positions 1-8 are awarded.  Driver with most points at the end of the season wins the championship.  Before each race the player can drive practice laps to get familiar with the track and the car setup.  Player can also drive a single lap qualifying run which will determine the grid position at the race start.

The difficulty levels (easy, medium, hard) define the total number of laps, weather conditions, pit stops, and tyre wear.  Initially only the easy level is selectable and must be completed successfully in top three in order to unlock the medium level.  In same manner, the medium level must be completed in top three to unlock the hard level.  Also the Single Grand Prix Event is unlocked by successfully completing the easy level.

In Multiplayer mode, up to 8 players can play in three different race types.  As in singleplayer Time Attack, each car races against top time ghost car.  Both Head to Head and Single Grand Prix modes allow players to race a single grand prix, the difference being that in the latter mode, computer controlled AI drivers are entered to fill the grid if less than eight players enter.

F1 Grand Prix also includes a TV Mode Race where AI cars race each other and the player has no control, except selecting the camera view.

All 2005 season cars are initially available but the game has unlockable F1 cars from past years, such as Lotus-Climax 25, turbo powered Williams FW11, and Cosworth classics Lotus-Ford 79 and Williams FW08.  Overall game style is more arcade than simulation, eg. collisions do not cause any noticeable damage, after a spin-out the car is automatically pointed to the right direction, and driving off-track slows the car down.  A simple car setup system has three presets: Defensive, Balanced, and Aggressive.  Player can also enable Brake Assist which automatically applies brakes in corners if the speed is too high.</desc>
		<image>./images/F1 Grand Prix-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/F1 Grand Prix-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/F1 Grand Prix-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/F1 Grand Prix-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20050922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Traveller's Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154757" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MOHH.iso</path>
		<name>MOHH</name>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154759" />
	</game>
	<game id="28534">
		<path>./Hotbrain.iso</path>
		<name>Hot Brain</name>
		<desc>Fire up your mind with Hot Brainâ„¢, a game that engages the mind through a series of puzzles and challenges designed to raise your brain activity. Hot Brainâ„¢ presents challenging and fun mental activities that help ignite your mind in areas like logic, memory, math, language and concentration. 

Hot Brain Â© 2009 Warner Bros. Entertainment Inc. All other trademarks and copyrights are the property of their respective owners. All rights reserved. 
HOT BRAIN and all related characters and elements are trademarks of and Â© Warner Bros. Entertainment Inc. 
WB GAMES LOGO, WB SHIELD: â„¢ &amp; Â© Warner Bros. Entertainment Inc.
(s09) 

Purchase or use of this item is subject to the PlayStationÂ®Network Terms of Service and User Agreement. If you do not wish to accept all these terms, do not purchase or use this item. This item has been sublicensed to you by Sony Computer Entertainment America. One-time license fee for downloads to up to 2 portable systems that are associated with the purchasing account.</desc>
		<image>./images/Hotbrain-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Hotbrain-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Hotbrain-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hotbrain-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154811" />
	</game>
	<game id="144661">
		<path>./Pinball.ISO</path>
		<name>Pinball</name>
		<image>./images/Pinball-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pinball-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pinball-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pinball-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>62cd00779febd3f67ab5358c19c7bd5f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154822" />
	</game>
	<game id="28262">
		<path>./Fat Princess Fistful of Cake (K).ISO</path>
		<name>Fat Princess : Fistful of Cake</name>
		<desc>Fast-paced and strategic, Fat Princess: Fistful of Cake pits two hordes of players against each other in a comic medieval battle on the PSP. The player's goal is to rescue a beloved princess from the enemy castle. There is a catch, though; the adversary has been feeding her magical cake to make her heavier to carry. Therefore, it will take much of the army working together to carry her across the battlefield. Team balance and strategy is crucial in Fat Princess: Fistful of Cake because players can switch between five different character classes, literally, at the drop of a hat. The name of the game is cooperation, whether it is flinging another player over the enemy's walls with a teeterboard, healing him while he charges into battle, or adding muscle to carry the hearty princess to safety. The comical, quirky, and loveable cast of characters in Fat Princess: Fistful of Cake has been developed specifically for optimization on the PSP. Now players can have their cake and take it on the go, too.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fat Princess Fistful of Cake (K)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Fat Princess Fistful of Cake (K)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Fat Princess Fistful of Cake (K)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fat Princess Fistful of Cake (K)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Fat Princess</family>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201001T001244</lastplayed>
		<gametime>94</gametime>
		<lang>kr</lang>
		<region>kr</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154823" />
	</game>
	<game id="28703">
		<path>./Street Supremacy.cso</path>
		<name>Street Supremacy</name>
		<desc>Street Supremacy, is a hand-held take of the Tokyo Xtreme Racer universe, with races on 15 different courses on the streets of Tokyo as well as 25 authentic high-end model cars, fully customizable with the ability to tweak anything from the engine to the muffler.

The main mode of the game is called "Team Rumble", where the player joins a clique, once doing must race in a series of events, winning these events will earn the player's team that "territory", taking control of that area.  Players can also recruit rival racers to their clique by draining their "Spirit Points", by smashing them into walls, guardrails and other cars, once depleted they will join the player's "clique".

Not only do players race against rival teams, but also against their own in "ranking battles", where a five car race will determine the rankings of the "clique".  The player can climb through the rankings by winning these races, eventually leading to the team leader and if he/she is beaten, they will become team leader of their group.

There is also a "Time-Attack" mode where players must complete a race in an allotted amount of time and there is also the ability for players to battle online utilizing the Ad-Hoc as well.</desc>
		<image>./images/Street Supremacy-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Street Supremacy-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Street Supremacy-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Street Supremacy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genki</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154837" />
	</game>
	<game id="28470">
		<path>./Rengoku.iso</path>
		<name>Rengoku : The Tower of Purgatory</name>
		<desc>Set in a dark and distant future, Rengoku: The Tower of Purgatory lets you play as a well-armed android that must fight its way to the pinnacle of a great tower to confront a mysterious foe. As you progress to higher levels, you'll improve your skills and acquire new weapons and technologies. You must strategically manage your resources to tackle the missions at hand. With the PSP's wireless capabilities, you can trade equipment and materials or battle with up to three other players in the multiplayer mode.
-- Summary provided by Gamefaqs.com</desc>
		<image>./images/Rengoku-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Rengoku-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Rengoku-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rengoku-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154854" />
	</game>
	<game id="28543">
		<path>./Kao Challengers.iso</path>
		<name>Kao Challengers</name>
		<desc>This is a conversion of the platform game Kao the Kangaroo Round 2 ported to PSP. There is one more world, 26 levels in total, and 5 bonus levels. 

There are 2 different multiplayer modes. The first mode is a deathmatch. The player can choose one of 4 characters (Kao, Parrot, Hunter and Pirate). The fight can be fought on one of ten arenas. Players can use 10 different weapons like rockets, bombs, scorpions, flamethrowers etc. to kill each other. 
The second mode is a race. There are 3 vehicles to choose from (snowboard, motorboat and bobsleigh). Players can race over 5 different tracks.</desc>
		<image>./images/Kao Challengers-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Kao Challengers-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Kao Challengers-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kao Challengers-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<developer>Tate Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154904" />
	</game>
	<game id="28658">
		<path>./Shift_Extended_USA.iso</path>
		<name>Shift Extended</name>
		<desc>As a subject of a science experiment, you have to escape the 120 levels of the game and avoid all the carefully crafted traps. Fortunately you have a unique power called 'SHIFT': floor, ceiling, walls...everything is reversed by pressing a single button!</desc>
		<image>./images/Shift_Extended_USA-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Shift_Extended_USA-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Shift_Extended_USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shift_Extended_USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Fishing Cactus</developer>
		<publisher>Zallag</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>dd8a930793025bd55790dd4c278139ee</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154907" />
	</game>
	<game id="28054">
		<path>./Midnight Club 3 Dub Edition.ISO</path>
		<name>Midnight Club 3 : DUB Edition</name>
		<desc>The series that took racing from the tracks to the open urban streets is raising the stakes even higher.  Midnight Club 3: DUB Edition is the definitive portable racing experience for the PSPâ„¢ Portable Entertainment System, delivering an unparalleled level of speed, customization and style.  Trick your ride out with the latest customization and upgrades and take on street racing's elite.  Midnight Club 3: DUB Edition puts the fastest ride ever in the palm of your hand.</desc>
		<image>./images/Midnight Club 3 Dub Edition-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Midnight Club 3 Dub Edition-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Midnight Club 3 Dub Edition-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Midnight Club 3 Dub Edition-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Rockstar Games</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Midnight Club Racing</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154916" />
	</game>
	<game id="144143">
		<path>./Fish Eyes Portable.iso</path>
		<name>Fish Eyes Portable</name>
		<desc>A portable fishing sim, based on the PlayStation fishing franchise. The PSP version retains the beautiful views of lakes, streams, waterfalls and rivers, with natural time-of-day changes in the environment. Drop line for utilizing an extensive variety of lures, tackle and other implements (over 150 tacklebox items) to hook any of 22 varieties of fish.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fish Eyes Portable-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fish Eyes Portable-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154920" />
	</game>
	<game id="27969">
		<path>./Eragon.iso</path>
		<name>Eragon</name>
		<desc>In Eragon, based on the movie of the same name, which is in turn based on the book Eragon, by Christopher Paolini, the player controls Saphira, Eragon's dragon companion and friend, and her task is to help him along 9 different levels in which you will be killing enemies, protecting allies, racing through narrow corridors and clearing pathways. Saphira can attack, brake, reverse course and use boost to cross long distances. The main means of attack are her talons, used to grab enemies or larger objects to bomb everything on the ground below. There is also a selection of offensive and defensive spells. Health is replenished by eating livestock.

There are 6 arena levels unlocked by playing through the singleplayer campaign. These are multiplayer stages where you can fight versus as many as three bots or human players in 12 different game modes. The PSP version is completely different game than those for the other platforms, focusing only on Saphira the dragon while the others prominently feature the hero Eragon.</desc>
		<image>./images/Eragon-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Eragon-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Eragon-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Eragon-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Eragon-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Sierra</developer>
		<publisher>Amaze Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154933" />
	</game>
	<game id="28297">
		<path>./Infected.iso</path>
		<name>Infected</name>
		<desc>Infected is a fast-paced third person comedy zombie shooter.  The focus is on a humorous plot and combo-based zombie killing.

It's Christmas time in New York and Zombies have come to ruin the festivities.  As New York Cop Agent Stevens, you find out that not only are you immune to the zombie virus, but your blood is actually so powerful, it will make a zombie explode.

The main focus of the gameplay is shooting holes in the zombies until they are weak enough for you to fire a vial of your own blood into them, causing an explosion.  Weaken enough zombies, fire a blood vial into one, and watch the chain reaction as exploding zombies send your anti-zombie blood onto other zombies.

The game was one of the first online PSP games, and featured a mode where defeating an opponent would give them your virus, and force their avatar online to look like your avatar.  If they in turn defeated someone, your virus would be passed onto them as well.  At any time you could look at a world map to see where on earth your strain of virus had travelled.</desc>
		<image>./images/Infected-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Infected-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Infected-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Infected-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Majesco</developer>
		<publisher>Planet Moon</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154941" />
	</game>
	<game id="144051">
		<path>./Bleach 1.ISO</path>
		<name>Bleach - Heat The Soul</name>
		<desc>Bleach: Heat the Soul is the first installment in the Heat the Soul fighting game series, released on March 24, 2005. The theme song for the game is *: Asterisk by Orange Range, which also happens to be the original opening theme for the anime. The game has a total of six characters, all of which derived from the Agent of the Shinigami arc.</desc>
		<image>./images/Bleach 1-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bleach 1-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bleach 1-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bleach 1-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154950" />
	</game>
	<game id="28596">
		<path>./Frogger Helmet Chaos.iso</path>
		<name>Frogger : Helmet Chaos</name>
		<desc>Frogger returns in an all-new platform game, Frogger Helmet Havoc. In the amphibious hero's latest adventure, Frogger must stop an evil force that threatens his home, Firefly Swamp, and the nearby kingdom of Bunnington Hollow. To stop Dr. Wani and his destructive mining efforts, you must help Frogger hop and dodge his way to the mastermind's lair. Frogger has unique abilities that allow him to climb walls, double-jump, tongue-grab, and more.</desc>
		<image>./images/Frogger Helmet Chaos-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Frogger Helmet Chaos-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Frogger Helmet Chaos-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Frogger Helmet Chaos-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154957" />
	</game>
	<game id="28184">
		<path>./Cars.iso</path>
		<name>Cars</name>
		<desc>Race to the finish line as you live all the fun and excitement of the Walt Disney Pictures &amp; Pixar Animation Studios film, "Cars." Play as all your favorite characters as you help Lightning McQueen capture the coveted Piston Cup Championship. Fans will discover unique characters and environments inspired by the film with more than 10 playable characters and 30 races and minigames to choose from. The game features a fully immersive re-creation of all major environments introduced in the movie, including Radiator Springs and Ornament Valley, which will offer distinctive racing experiences to players while maintaining the artistic style of the film.</desc>
		<image>./images/Cars-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Cars-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Cars-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cars-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Locomotive Games</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Cars</family>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T155003" />
	</game>
	<game id="142923">
		<path>./Open Season.iso</path>
		<name>Open Season</name>
		<desc>Open Season is a video game, based on the movie of the same name. It was released for Wii, PlayStation 2, PlayStation Portable, Microsoft Windows, Game Boy Advance, Xbox 360, Xbox, Nintendo DS, and Nintendo GameCube. The Nintendo DS version supports the Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection.

While Patrick Warburton, Matthew W. Taylor, Nika Futterman and Danny Mann reprise their roles from the movie, most of the original people were replaced (for example, Chris Williams and Matthew W. Taylor are the voices of Boog and Elliot in this game).</desc>
		<image>./images/Open Season-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Open Season-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Open Season-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Open Season-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Open Season-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T155011" />
	</game>
	<game id="27895">
		<path>./Ratchet  And Clank Size Matters.iso</path>
		<name>Ratchet &amp; Clank - Size Matters</name>
		<desc>Ratchet &amp; Clank: Size Matters (known as Ratchet &amp; Clank 5 in Japan) is a 2007 platformer video game developed by High Impact Games and published by Sony Computer Entertainment for the PlayStation Portable and PlayStation 2. The game is the first Ratchet &amp; Clank title on the PSP handheld. Development company High Impact Games was spawned from the original Ratchet &amp; Clank developer, Insomniac Games. The story is about Ratchet and Clank as they are interrupted from their vacation to search for a kidnapped girl and encounter a forgotten race known as the Technomites</desc>
		<image>./images/Ratchet  And Clank Size Matters-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ratchet  And Clank Size Matters-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ratchet  And Clank Size Matters-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ratchet  And Clank Size Matters-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Ratchet  And Clank Size Matters-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Impact Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<family>Ratchet &amp; Clank</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T155019" />
	</game>
	<game id="28103">
		<path>./Tony Hawks Underground 2 Remix.ISO</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Underground 2 Remix</name>
		<desc>Tony Hawk's Underground 2 Remix takes players on an all new skating blitzkrieg where they embark on the ultimate road trip from Tony Hawk's Underground 2 in addition to wreaking havoc in four never-before-seen city-levels - Las Vegas, Atlanta, Kyoto and Santa Cruz -- that feature original goals, level changing events and unlockable characters. For the first time, players can live the Tony Hawk console gaming experience on a handheld device as they join either Tony Hawk or Bam Margera on a World Destruction Tour where they nail insane tricks with lightning speed or slow motion focus control, pull off mischievous pranks, and conquer sick terrain through 13 single-player levels, or face off against up to three friends in 10 wireless multiplayer games.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tony Hawks Underground 2 Remix-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Tony Hawks Underground 2 Remix-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Tony Hawks Underground 2 Remix-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tony Hawks Underground 2 Remix-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Tony Hawks Underground 2 Remix-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<developer>Shaba Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<family>Tony Hawk</family>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T155030" />
	</game>
	<game id="28270">
		<path>./BBoy.iso</path>
		<name>B-Boy</name>
		<desc>B-Boy is a dance battle game based around the Hip Hop element of b-boying (AKA break-dancing). The game has taken care to be true to the culture, featuring real b-boys such as Crazy Legs and recent UK Break-dancing Championship winner Mouse. Music is a mixture of classic b-boy themes such as The Mexican by Babe Ruth.

The gameplay is a combination of fighting game mechanics with a music rhythm game. The player pulls off different combinations to accrue points and defeat opponents (human and cpu). In deference to the global popularity of B-Boying, the game takes place at global locations from Japan to Europe to New York. There are 21 venues in total. In the B-Boy Life mode, you have to gather a crew and battle against superstars. You can also create your own character and define the moves.</desc>
		<image>./images/BBoy-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/BBoy-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/BBoy-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/BBoy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20080923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Freestyle Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T155037" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2008.iso</path>
		<name>Tiger Woods PGA Tour 08</name>
		<desc>CONFIDENCE IS EVERYTHING

-ALL-NEW SHOT CONFIDENCE
Now track your performance on every hole. Analyze past performances to identify strengths and weaknesses before every shot to build confidence and improve your game. 

-UNIQUE MENTAL GAMES
Manage your emotions on the course and regain your composure by playing one of the new confidence-building Mental Games. Easy to pick up , hard to put down.

-14 AUTHENTIC CHAMPIONSHIP COURSES
Experience the new PGA TOUR FedExCup championship format by playing dream rounds at Westchester Country Club, TPC Boston, Cog Hill, and East Lake.

-CHOOSE FROM 11 PROFESSIONAL GOLFERS
Take on the golfing world's best, including Tiger Woods, John Daly, and Vijay Singh, plush Annika Sorenstam.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2008-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20070828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Tiburon, Exient Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>EA Sports</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153417" />
		<scrap name="TheGamesDB" date="20221011T164235" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Taitsujin Portable.ISO</path>
		<name>Taiko no Tatsujin Portable</name>
		<thumbnail>./images/Taitsujin Portable-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20050805T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Music</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T164335</lastplayed>
		<gametime>29</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153435" />
		<scrap name="TheGamesDB" date="20221011T164354" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jetpack_Joyride_v2_150K_Coins_USA.iso</path>
		<name>Jetpack Joyride</name>
		<image>./images/Jetpack_Joyride_v2_150K_Coins_USA-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Jetpack_Joyride_v2_150K_Coins_USA-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Jetpack_Joyride_v2_150K_Coins_USA-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beatshapers</developer>
		<publisher>Beatshapers</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201001T001549</lastplayed>
		<gametime>43</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153541" />
	</game>
	<game id="28711">
		<path>./Gundam Battle Royal.ISO</path>
		<name>Gundam Battle Royale</name>
		<desc>Gundam Battle Royale is a game released for the PlayStation Portable. The game was released only in Japan and South Korea on October 5, 2006. The game features many mobile suits and mobile armors from the Universal Century up to and including Zeta Gundam. It is the sequel to Gundam Battle Tactics. A sequel called Gundam Battle Chronicles has been released on 25 October 2007.</desc>
		<image>./images/Gundam Battle Royal-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Gundam Battle Royal-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Gundam Battle Royal-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Gundam Battle Royal-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20061005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T163616" />
	</game>
	<game id="142897">
		<path>./Call of Duty 3.iso</path>
		<name>Call of Duty : Roads to Victory</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty: Roads to Victory is a 2007 World War II first-person shooter for the PlayStation Portable. It was released on March 13, 2007. It is the third portable installment of the franchise, first being on the N-Gage and the second on the Pocket PC.</desc>
		<image>./images/Call of Duty 3-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Call of Duty 3-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Call of Duty 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Call of Duty 3-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20070313T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<family>Call Of Duty</family>
		<players>2-6</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T162436</lastplayed>
		<gametime>289</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T161944" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Series Of Poker Champions 2007.ISO</path>
		<name>World Series of Poker - Tournament of Champions - 2007 Edition</name>
		<video>./videos/World Series Of Poker Champions 2007-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/World Series Of Poker Champions 2007-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/World Series Of Poker Champions 2007-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Divers</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153632" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20221011T163935" />
	</game>
	<game id="15387">
		<path>./WWE vs Raw.iso</path>
		<name>WWF Raw</name>
		<desc>The game offers the players a wrestling experience with various matches like singles match, tag team match, triple threat, fatal 4 way, battle royal and handicap matches. It has a weak/strong grapple system. There are two types of grapples: one which is done with normal opponents and other with groggy opponents. The normal grapples do little harm when compared to grapples done when the opponent is stunned. There is a voltage meter which shows the momentum of the wrestlers. Special move, high flying attacks and taunting boost the momentum while repeated attacks cost loss in momentum. Finishers can only be applied when the opponent is stunned and the voltage meter is flashing. Excessive use of finishers also cause loss in momentum.</desc>
		<image>./images/WWE vs Raw-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/WWE vs Raw-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/WWE vs Raw-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/WWE vs Raw-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/WWE vs Raw-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20020211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Anchor</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<family>WWF</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T163919" />
	</game>
	<game id="28236">
		<path>./50 Cents Bulletproof.cso</path>
		<name>50 Cent : Bulletproof, G-Unit Edition</name>
		<desc>After getting shot nine times and left for dead, 50 takes revenge on his enemies. Working with his G-Unit soldiers ? Lloyd Banks, Tony Yayo, and Young Buck ? 50 takes on the most powerful gangs and crime syndicates in the city, uncovering a criminal conspiracy with international implications.</desc>
		<image>./images/50 Cents Bulletproof-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/50 Cents Bulletproof-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/50 Cents Bulletproof-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/50 Cents Bulletproof-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/50 Cents Bulletproof-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<developer>Universal</developer>
		<publisher>High Voltage</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T161224</lastplayed>
		<gametime>41</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T161257" />
	</game>
	<game id="28065">
		<path>./300 March To Glory.iso</path>
		<name>300 : March to Glory</name>
		<desc>In the action packed 300: March to Glory, players take on the role of King Leonidas, who leads the brave 300 Spartans against Xerxes and his massive Persian army. The player, as Leonidas, uses his sword, spear and shield and the power of the soldiers in a battle to determine the very fate of western civilization. 300: March to Glory is a visceral experience focused on action and combat, allowing the player to fight both solo and in a phalanx alongside his fellow Spartans</desc>
		<image>./images/300 March To Glory-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/300 March To Glory-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/300 March To Glory-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/300 March To Glory-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Collision Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T161140</lastplayed>
		<gametime>338</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153657" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ace Combat Skies Of Deception.iso</path>
		<name>Ace Combat X Skies of Deception</name>
		<desc>With licensed aircraft such as the F-14D and Tornado F3, and a strategic AI system where the course of the player's actions directly affect their mission objectives, Ace Combat X: Skies of Deception allows the player to take on the role of an ace pilot trying to liberate his home country of Aurelia from its neighbor, Leasath. A country filled with secretive motives veiled behind long-internal conflicts, Leasath, has invaded and taken over Aurelia. Defending the invaded country, the player's mission is to take them to the battle-filled skies in order to take down the enemy and restore freedom and peace to his homeland. Rounding out the list of features, Ace Combat X: Skies of Deception allows players to tune their original aircrafts with parts unlocked in Campaign Mode to further enhance their flying experience.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ace Combat Skies Of Deception-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ace Combat Skies Of Deception-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Ace Combat Skies Of Deception-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20061023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Access Games, Project Aces</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Flight Simulator</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153718" />
		<scrap name="TheGamesDB" date="20221011T161320" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Live 2006.iso</path>
		<name>NBA Live 06</name>
		<desc>NBA Live 06 continues the NBA live franchise and boasts a set of new features. Improved transition play captures the speed and feel of a NBA fast break, and increased attention to interior defense delivers the physicality of an NBA game. NBA Live 06 allows you to play as players in the NBA who can exhibit superstar styles like 'Playmaker' or 'Stopper'. These stars have their own controls and visual modes allowing them to dominate lesser players.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/NBA Live 2006-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20051004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Canada</developer>
		<publisher>EA Sports</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153725" />
		<scrap name="TheGamesDB" date="20221011T165039" />
	</game>
	<game id="28187">
		<path>./Vampire Chronicle.ISO</path>
		<name>Darkstalkers Chronicles : The Tower of Chaos</name>
		<desc>Once again, the monster warriors from the Darkstalkers series return to battle for control of the night. From vampires to mummies, Darkstalkers Chronicle: The Chaos Tower includes all 18 characters from previous installments in the franchise. Choose your favorite character, and master his or her unique moves to gain victory in various gameplay modes, such as arcade, training, tower, and network. Use the wireless network capabilities of the PSP to challenge your friend to a one-on-one match.</desc>
		<image>./images/Vampire Chronicle-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Vampire Chronicle-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Vampire Chronicle-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Vampire Chronicle-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Vampire Chronicle-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<family>Darkstalkers</family>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T164142</lastplayed>
		<gametime>15</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164123" />
	</game>
	<game id="28170">
		<path>./Burnout Legends.iso</path>
		<name>Burnout Legends</name>
		<desc>First installation of the Burnout-series on handheld consoles combines the best features of the first three games: Burnout, Burnout 2: Point of Impact, and Burnout 3: Takedown.  Aggressive racing is still the centerpiece attraction of Burnout Legends and the player's task is not only to win the races but also crash opponent cars as much as possible.  Opponent takedowns, drifts, and other stunts award Burnout Points which in turn unlock new cars and other awards.

One player games can be played as single events or as a World Tour where the player needs to compete in different races and succeed in them in order to advance through five car classes (Compact, Muscle, Coupe, Sport, and Super).  In addition there is the Crash mode, where the goal is to create as much wreckage as possible by ploughing the player car into the traffic.  The different race types include Race, Time Attack, Road Rage, Pursuit, Face Off, Eliminator, Burning Lap, and Grand Prix.  Multiplayer game modes include Race, Road Rage, Pursuit, special Crash modes Double Impact and Party Crash (all these can can be played as single events or as a tournament), and Collector Challenge where the player has the opportunity to win other player's Collector cars.

PSP version game sharing feature allows others to play multiplayer events or single player demo without their own Burnout Legends UMD.

DS version Multi-Pak support allows two player games without additional game cards.  More than two player games require multiple game cards.</desc>
		<image>./images/Burnout Legends-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Burnout Legends-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Burnout Legends-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Burnout Legends-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Burnout Legends-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<family>Burnout</family>
		<players>6</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T162812</lastplayed>
		<gametime>212</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153802" />
	</game>
	<game id="144066">
		<path>./Panic_Bomber.iso</path>
		<name>Bomberman - Panic Bomber</name>
		<desc>It is a "falling blocks" puzzle game based on the Bomberman franchise. The goal of the game is essentially to cause your opponent to lose by causing their gameplay field to fill to the top with objects. You do this by causing chains of bombs to explode, sending useless rubble over to your opponent's field, which they must then remove themselves. Bombs are earned by causing chains of three identical blocks to disappear. Bombs can only be blown up with an explosion from a lit bomb, which falls from the top of the screen every so often. If the player causes enough damage, they can eventually earn a giant bomb, which will remove a large amount of debris from the playing field, and cause their opponent a good deal of trouble.

The game's regular story mode revolves around Bomberman's hunt for the Golden Bomber statue. During his trek, he fights against several different odd characters, like Drifty the balloon, or Cecil the tiger. However, all that can really be earned from playing through this mode is a harder difficulty level, earned by finishing the entire story at the "hard" difficulty level. The player's progress is saved by a password system.</desc>
		<image>./images/Panic_Bomber-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Panic_Bomber-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Panic_Bomber-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Panic_Bomber-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20050623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<family>Bomberman</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>155296c8c0e06cd25fb92cbc858a6086</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164901" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pro Evo Soccer 2007.iso</path>
		<name>Winning Eleven - Pro Evolution Soccer 2007</name>
		<video>./videos/Pro Evo Soccer 2007-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pro Evo Soccer 2007-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pro Evo Soccer 2007-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<genre>Sport</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153843" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20221011T164837" />
	</game>
	<game id="144770">
		<path>./Kazook.iso</path>
		<name>Kazook</name>
		<image>./images/Kazook-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Kazook-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Kazook-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kazook-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<developer>Monte Cristo Multimédia</developer>
		<publisher>Monte Cristo Multimédia</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T163654" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0567 - Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Ultimate Ghosts'n Goblins</name>
		<desc>Once again, the brave knight Arthur is called into action to face the Dark Lord in order to rescue the princess.

The fourth title in the series, Arthur must make numerous ghouls and monsters on his quest to save Princess Prin Prin before her life is taken by the newest Dark Lord's evil plan.

Possessing the familiar moves that Arthur is known for, he must go throughout numerous levels in this latest 2D quest with new 3D rendered elements.  New abilities and upgrades allow Arthur a new set of moves to face this difficult platformer, and Warp Keys allow Arthur to go back and revisit completed worlds in order to find more secrets and weapons.  Ever present are the classic cast of zombies, the shape-changing magicians, and the infamous Red Devil.</desc>
		<image>./images/0567 - Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins (USA)-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/0567 - Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins (USA)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/0567 - Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins (USA)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20200926T144954</lastplayed>
		<gametime>92</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T153926" />
	</game>
	<game id="28210">
		<path>./Virtua Tennis.iso</path>
		<name>Virtua Tennis : World Tour</name>
		<desc>Virtua Tennis: World Tour is the PSP incarnation of Sega's Virtua Tennis series. You can play as one of many professional tennis players, such as Roger Federer or Maria Sharapova, on courts around the world. In addition to Exhibition and Tournament modes, you can create a custom player and play through World Tour mode. Virtua Tennis: World Tour also lets you play stat-building minigames and challenge up to four other players in Versus mode.</desc>
		<image>./images/Virtua Tennis-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Virtua Tennis-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Virtua Tennis-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Virtua Tennis-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20051007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Tennis</genre>
		<family>Virtua Tennis</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164049" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Snoopy Red Baron.iso</path>
		<name>Snoopy vs the Red Baron</name>
		<video>./videos/Snoopy Red Baron-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Snoopy Red Baron-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Snoopy Red Baron-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154005" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20221011T164731" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fifa 0607.cso</path>
		<name>FIFA 07</name>
		<desc>FIFA 07 throws you into the rollercoaster ride of a football season. Employ real world tactics, make realistic decisions, and think like a player in order to win matches.</desc>
		<image>./images/Fifa 0607-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/Fifa 0607-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fifa 0607-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20061017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Canada</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T163527</lastplayed>
		<gametime>330</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154010" />
		<scrap name="TheGamesDB" date="20221011T162941" />
	</game>
	<game id="28693">
		<path>./Space Invaders.iso</path>
		<name>Space Invaders Evolution</name>
		<desc>Space Invaders makes a return to the gaming scene with both old and new versions of the classic arcade experience. A classic mode includes the original color game and a port of the 1978 match-up mode. While playing the screen can be rotated 90 degrees to have two players compete on a single PSP. It also future a wireless mode with support of up to four players.

In the new Future Mode the game takes place in 13 stages from Pluto to Earth in full 3D. You have to shoot down the mothership, which spawns small invaders over time. This mode supports three viewpoints. In addition to the normal shots there is also Beat Attack accessed by triangle button. If you time your shots with the music using Beat Attack, they will become more powerful. You can also wipe out all aliens on the screen by holding down the triangle button until the fourth beat and then letting go.</desc>
		<image>./images/Space Invaders-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Space Invaders-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Space Invaders-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Space Invaders-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20050922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Whip</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<family>Space Invaders</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T164651</lastplayed>
		<gametime>13</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164706" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Free Runing.cso</path>
		<name>Free Running</name>
		<desc>Parkour, the art of movement, is less a sport and more a way of life. Its participants, known as Free Runners or Traceurs, view the environment and its obstacles, urban or natural, as a series of challenges to be overcome. To the Traceurs, parkour has a philosophical appeal: they feel transformed by the experience, free from the grind of city life. Since its inception in Paris during the mid-1980s, it has spread across the globe and now has an international army of exponents and enthusiasts. In Free Running, the concrete jungle becomes your urban playground as you run, vault, jump or climb over obstacles in the most fluid and flowing manner possible. Test the boundaries of human ability as you perform death-defying leaps and jaw-dropping trips across inner-city rooftops. To be crowned King of Parkour, you must master over 50 moves, tricks and stunts including 'Kong Vaults', 'Pharaoh Climbs', 'Rail Split Vaults' and 'Vertical Wall Runs' in a variety of game modes while racing against human or computer-controlled competitors.</desc>
		<thumbnail>./images/Free Runing-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20070405T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154019" />
		<scrap name="TheGamesDB" date="20221011T163541" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NFL Madden 2006.iso</path>
		<name>Madden NFL 06</name>
		<video>./videos/NFL Madden 2006-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/NFL Madden 2006-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/NFL Madden 2006-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<publisher>EA</publisher>
		<genre>Sport</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154020" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20221011T165140" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Winning Eleven 9.ISO</path>
		<name>World Soccer Winning Eleven 9</name>
		<image>./images/Winning Eleven 9-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Winning Eleven 9-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Winning Eleven 9-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Winning Eleven 9-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<genre>Sport</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T164750</lastplayed>
		<gametime>12</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164002" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20221011T164815" />
	</game>
	<game id="28092">
		<path>./Mega Man Power Up.iso</path>
		<name>Mega Man : Powered Up</name>
		<desc>Dr. Light had an idea: He would build a bunch of good and handy robots to help him and others to make the world a better place. One of these robots is named "Mega" and is designed to help Light around the lab in various tasks. One day, evil Dr. Wily attacks the lab and turn all of the robots evil too. All except Mega. Dr. Light sends Mega to stop these robots and thus, Mega Man is born.

Mega Man: Powered Up is a semi-remake of the original Mega Man.
There is an "Old Mode", where one tackles the adventure just like it was in the olden days, with the exception of an added feature to save game. The graphics are souped up, but the level layout is basically the same than in the original with a few minor changes here and there.
Then there's the "New Mode" which also features the original level themes and bosses but the levels themselves are boosted with various hidden areas and features which are mostly impossible to get to with Megaman only. The Player must defeat the bosses after which they'll be available as playable characters and use their special abilities to find everything in every level.

The third mode is the Challenge Mode where there is 100 different challenges to tackle and in which one has to dispatch as many enemies as possible in a given amount of time, get to the specific goal in a given amount of time and so on.

In addition to these two main game modes, there is a level editor that can be used to build the Megaman level of one's dreams and play it or send it to the internet where other gamers can download and play it.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mega Man Power Up-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Mega Man Power Up-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mega Man Power Up-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mega Man Power Up-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Mega Man Power Up-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Mega Man</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T163852" />
	</game>
	<game id="143810">
		<path>./Ape Academy 1.iso</path>
		<name>Ape Escape Academy</name>
		<desc>Ape Escape Academy sees you taking on the role of one of the cheeky monkeys from the Ape Escape series. Choose your chimp, then prepare to tackle various classes in Academy Mode. Each 'class' is actually a mini-game. Your goal is to complete as many mini-games as possible from the 9x9 grid, and score as many lines as you can (sort of like Noughts and Crosses). Mini-games range from mind-bending quizzes to wacky sports games, to the just plain silly, like protecting a roast banana from oncoming apes, or flying through the sky delivering parachutes to plummeting primates.</desc>
		<image>./images/Ape Academy 1-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ape Academy 1-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ape Academy 1-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ape Academy 1-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Run Jump</genre>
		<family>Ape Escape</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T161902</lastplayed>
		<gametime>226</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T161513" />
	</game>
	<game id="28673">
		<path>./Nascar 07.cso</path>
		<name>NASCAR</name>
		<desc>Take risks, be rewarded, and become a champion with NASCAR® on the PSP® system as you challenge the greatest drivers in four authentic racing series. Fight to the finish against a full field of 43 drivers in Season mode to stay atop the leaderboard, or become a superstar owner or driver by developing essential racing skills and increasing fan support in Fight to the Top mode. Improve your skills with a host of mini-games and experience the all-out drama and intensity of 190-mph racing with NASCAR.</desc>
		<image>./images/Nascar 07-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Nascar 07-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Nascar 07-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Nascar 07-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20080906T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TBC</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<family>NASCAR (EA)</family>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T165026" />
	</game>
	<game id="28509">
		<path>./Dave Mirra bmx.iso</path>
		<name>Dave Mirra BMX Challenge</name>
		<desc>Dave Mirra is to BMX what Edison was to electricity. What the Wright Brothers were to flight. Like them, he rewrote the rules of what's possible. On the ground or above it, the Miracle Boy has redefined the boundaries of the sport and then promptly surpassed them. Now, the legend of the winningnest X Games competitor of all time is on the PSP system, letting you defy gravity wherever you go. With ad hoc wireless play for 1-4 players, you can challenge your friends to racing and freestyle competition and see who's got what it takes to ride with the greatest. 17 levels across 9 different environments. Customizable player characters, with tricked out clothes and gear. 10 Bikes to choose from and customize as you win.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dave Mirra bmx-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dave Mirra bmx-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dave Mirra bmx-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dave Mirra bmx-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Oxygen Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Cycling</genre>
		<family>Dave Mirra BMX</family>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T162827" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sponge Bob Square Pants.cso</path>
		<name>SpongeBob SquarePants - The Yellow Avenger</name>
		<video>./videos/Sponge Bob Square Pants-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Sponge Bob Square Pants-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sponge Bob Square Pants-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<md5>eb989ac4fb2d8a3a44099dfcebf17cce</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154341" />
		<scrap name="HfsDB" date="20221011T164624" />
	</game>
	<game id="28257">
		<path>./Dynastey Warriors.ISO</path>
		<name>Dynasty Warriors</name>
		<desc>Koei's Dynasty Warriors series hits the handheld market in it's first fully 3D form on the PSP. As an officer in a Chinese army, you fight and kill thousands of soldiers in massive battles stretched over numerous battlefields - either in the campaign "Musou" modes or the single battle "Free" mode which can be used to train.

New to this PSP version is a bodyguard system where your selected second officer can give you certain items or abilities, for example one ensures you always have a horse when entering an area.and others can give you special powered up Musou attacks.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dynastey Warriors-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dynastey Warriors-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dynastey Warriors-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dynastey Warriors-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Koei</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<family>Dynasty Warriors</family>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T162902" />
	</game>
	<game id="28539">
		<path>./Mercury.iso</path>
		<name>Archer Maclean's Mercury</name>
		<desc>In Archer Maclean's Mercury, your job is to guide a blob of mercury, or several blobs, along various mazes, by tilting the game world.  En route, you are required to run over color markers, which will change the color of your blob to the color required to win the level. Some areas of the game will require you to split your mercury into two, roll each blob over two different colored switches, and then combine the two blobs to form a third, different color.

Each level has different elements to it, some of which will help you and some of which will hinder you.  There are conveyor belts, moving platforms, launch pads, and jagged corners that when hit, will cause your blob to split into two, even three.

There are 83 different mazes, each one progressively harder than the last.</desc>
		<image>./images/Mercury-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Mercury-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mercury-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mercury-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050406T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T164926</lastplayed>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164937" />
	</game>
	<game id="103359">
		<path>./Work Time Fun.cso</path>
		<name>WTF : Work Time Fun</name>
		<desc>Created specifically for the PSP system, WTF is a crazy collection of fun and addictive mini-games that drive the player to perform sometimes trivial, sometimes mind-bending, but always fun jobs in pursuit of the almighty dollar. The latest in a long line of unique Japanese games that have gained popularity in the United States, WTF delivers gamers compelling, bite-sized morsels of frenzied arcade-style action unlike anything ever seen on the PSP system.</desc>
		<image>./images/Work Time Fun-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Work Time Fun-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Work Time Fun-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Work Time Fun-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20061017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCEJ</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164104" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GTAvcs.iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto: Vice City Stories</name>
		<desc>Vice City, 1984. Opportunity abounds in a city emerging from the swamps, its growth fueled by the violent power struggle in a lucrative drug trade. Construction is everywhere as a shining metropolis rises from foundations of crime and betrayal.

As a soldier, Vic Vance has always protected his dysfunctional family, his country, and himself. One bad decision later and that job is about to get much harder. Kicked out onto the streets of a city torn between glamor and gluttony, Vic is faced with a stark choice: build an empire or be crushed.

GTA: VCS is the PlayStation Portable follow-up to Rockstar's monumental handheld entry in the series, Grand Theft Auto: Liberty City Stories. As in Liberty City Stories, this game ventures back to the location of the second PS2 game.</desc>
		<image>./images/GTAvcs-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/GTAvcs-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/GTAvcs-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/GTAvcs-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<releasedate>20061031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Leeds, Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Sandbox</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154657" />
		<scrap name="TheGamesDB" date="20221011T163602" />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2007.iso</path>
		<name>Tiger Woods PGA Tour 07</name>
		<desc>Take the road to the PGA Championship with Tiger Woods PGA Tour 07. At home or on the go, challenge the world’s top golfers in all-new PGA Tour Mode, featuring training sessions, practice, and The FedEx Cup, the new PGA Tour championship playoff system. Hone your skills in the all-new Shooting Gallery, then play as or against 11 players, including John Daly, on 12 championship courses. An enhanced Game Face features dramatic visual improvements, including player and course lighting, in addition to improved camera movements. From the plush fairways of Pebble Beach to the dunes of Fancourt Links, feed off the intensity and rise above the competition to become the next golf legend.</desc>
		<image>./images/Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2007-image.jpg</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2007-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20060922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T154658" />
		<scrap name="TheGamesDB" date="20221011T164221" />
	</game>
	<game id="103340">
		<path>./Luxor.iso</path>
		<name>Luxor : The Wrath of Set</name>
		<desc>LUXOR: Wrath of Set is any easily accessible title that features an addictive style of gameplay combined with slick graphics and detailed levels that continue to challenge you as you go. Luxor is an action/puzzler that takes the player on a thrilling adventure across Ancient Egypt. Isis has enlisted you to battle Set and his evil minions. Use your scarab to shoot and destroy the approaching spheres before they reach the pyramids. Use Isis' magic by catching talismans, gems, and Ankh coins. Featuring a rousing soundtrack and full of exhilarating action, the only question is: Can you thwart Set's diabolical plans?</desc>
		<image>./images/Luxor-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Luxor-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Luxor-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Luxor-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20061117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MumboJumbo</developer>
		<publisher>MumboJumbo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T163825</lastplayed>
		<gametime>56</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T163839" />
	</game>
	<game id="28002">
		<path>./Street Fighter Turbo Alpha 3.iso</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 3 Max</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 3 MAX is a conversion of the 2D arcade fighter Street Fighter Alpha 3. Featuring a roster of 37 characters, including 3 (Maki, Yun, Eagle) never seen outside of the GBA version, and 1 brand-new character (Ingrid) to the game, all with their own storyline, you can spend a very long time learning the intricacies of all the fighters.

It includes all the novelties introduced in the Alpha series, including finite defenses, the ability to recover and isms to customize special attacks. To help avoid the typical repetitiveness of the game, all the modes available in the previous home versions of Alpha 3, such as Arcade Mode, Training Mode, Edit Mode, World Tour, Dramatic Battle and Survival modes are all available in this version, along with the brand-new 100-man kumite (survival) and tag-team battle modes.

The PSP version also has network games (Ad-Hoc only) for up to 8 players, with four additional modes: VS Mode, Team Mode, Variable Battle (take three players into battle of which you control two, and the computer one), and the Dramatic Battle with multiple fighters going at it simultaneously.</desc>
		<image>./images/Street Fighter Turbo Alpha 3-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Street Fighter Turbo Alpha 3-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Street Fighter Turbo Alpha 3-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Street Fighter Turbo Alpha 3-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Street Fighter Turbo Alpha 3-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Street Fighter</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164605" />
	</game>
	<game id="28493">
		<path>./Atari Hits Remixed.iso</path>
		<name>Activision Hits Remixed</name>
		<desc>Activision Hits Remixed lets PSP system gamers relive the dawn of home console gaming while on the go by delivering over 40 of the biggest Atari 2600 titles, such as Pitfall, Kaboom!, Chopper Command, Stampede, Keystone Kapers, to the PSP. With the game's multi-player supported classics, players can choose whether they want to game together utilizing a Game Share feature that allows two friends to play together using only one copy of the game or take turns on one PSP system or play via the game's wireless functionality. Activision Hits Remixed also features a rockin' 80's themed soundtrack, modernized front-end graphics, classic game manuals which include tips and photographs, and a host of retro unlockables.</desc>
		<image>./images/Atari Hits Remixed-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Atari Hits Remixed-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Atari Hits Remixed-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Atari Hits Remixed-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T161430</lastplayed>
		<gametime>18</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T161408" />
	</game>
	<game id="28540">
		<path>./Super Moneky Ball Adventures.cso</path>
		<name>Super Monkey Ball Adventure</name>
		<desc>Our four heroes from Super Monkey Ball - Aiai, Meemee, Baby and Gongon - were enjoying a typical day, when they saw a flying machine crash down on a nearby island.  Soon, they discovered that the mysterious Naysayers have appeared, spreading discord and unhappiness all over the island.  And to top it all off, the prince and princess of the neighboring islands have gone missing on Jungle Island - if they aren't found and returned, there's sure to be trouble!  Can our heroes restore order to Monearth?

Super Monkey Ball Adventure takes the monkey rolling madness of the previous games and puts a story-based spin on it.  Choosing from one of the four monkeys, Players roll their way around the various islands of Monearth, talking to citizens and performing the tasks they request (such as delivering sandwiches, finding a missing baby, rescuing rare flowers, and more) to cheer them up.

Certain parts of the island are locked by 'Puzzle Gates' - these can only be unlocked by solving the puzzle stages which can be accessed in front of the gate.  Each pad transports you to a different Puzzle Realm.  The Puzzle Realm stages are the more familiar gameplay of Super Monkey Ball - simple looking stages where players must carefully (but quickly) roll their monkey to the finish line within the time limit.

Bananas can also be collected throughout the game - these are used as currency, and can be used to unlock new playable characters and puzzle stages.  They can also be given to particular unhappy citizens.  The monkeys will also learn magical chants as they progress through the game - these allow you to climb walls, set your monkey's ball on fire, use a boxing glove to attack, and more.

Also included in Super Monkey Ball Adventure are the famous Party Games - favorites like Monkey Race, Monkey Target and Monkey fight return.  There's also three new games: 'Monkey Cannon' - fire monkeys at enemy towers to steal their bricks for your own tower.  'Monkey Bounce' - bounce on a trampoline-like platform with your opponents, and try to claim as many squares as possible.  'Monkey Tag' - roll around a globe and try to collect as many balloons as possible.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Moneky Ball Adventures-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Moneky Ball Adventures-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Moneky Ball Adventures-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Moneky Ball Adventures-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164448" />
	</game>
	<game id="28081">
		<path>./Syphon Filter.cso</path>
		<name>Syphon Filter : Dark Mirror</name>
		<desc>Assume the role of Gabe Logan, a highly-trained Precision Strike Operative, commanding a black box United States Agency that legally doesn't exist. Gabe finds himself dealing with a beautiful woman from his past who harbors a shocking secret while he battles the Red Section, a para-military group in possession of Project Dark Mirror, a next-generation weapon of mass destruction. Using Precision Strike Tactics, advanced vision technology, and the latest in high-tech weaponry, Logan and his team perform surgical strike missions - too sensitive for a military response, too dangerous for civilian intelligence forces. Through the role of Gabe, players will have to be quick to strategize, as he is responsible to infiltrate, recon and execute decisively. Once inserted, Logan is his own authority - he must make life and death decisions, quickly choosing which course of action to take.</desc>
		<image>./images/Syphon Filter-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Syphon Filter-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Syphon Filter-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Syphon Filter-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<fanart>./images/Syphon Filter-fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<family>Syphon Filter</family>
		<players>2-8</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20221011T164516</lastplayed>
		<gametime>14</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164534" />
	</game>
	<game id="28562">
		<path>./Taito Legends.iso</path>
		<name>Taito Legends Power-Up</name>
		<desc>Alpine Ski
Balloon Bomber
Cameltry
Chack'n Pop
Crazy Balloon
Elevator Action
The Fairyland Story
KiKi KaiKai
Kuri Kinton
The Legend of Kage
Lunar Rescue
New Zealand Story
Phoenix
Qix
Raimais
Rastan Saga
Return of the Invaders
Space Chaser
Space Dungeon
Space Invaders
Space Invaders Part 2</desc>
		<image>./images/Taito Legends-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Taito Legends-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Taito Legends-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Taito Legends-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>KOCH Media</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T164408" />
	</game>
	<game id="27932">
		<path>./Lego Star Wars II.cso</path>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars II : The Original Trilogy</name>
		<desc>Lego Star Wars II: The Original Trilogy is a multi-platform action-adventure video game developed by Traveller's Tales and published by LucasArts and TT Games. It was released on September 11, 2006. Part of the Lego Star Wars series, it is based on the Star Wars science fiction media franchise and Lego Group's Star Wars-themed toy line. It follows the events of the Star Wars films Star Wars, The Empire Strikes Back and Return of the Jedi. The game allows players to assume the roles of over 50 Lego versions of characters from the film series; customized characters can also be created. Camera movement was improved from its predecessorâ€”Lego Star Wars: The Video Game; and the concept of "vehicle levels" was explored more thoroughly. The game was revealed at American International Toy Fair 2006. Promotions for the game were set up at chain stores across the United States.

Lego Star Wars II was critically and commercially successful; it has sold over 8.2 million copies worldwide as of May 2009. Critics praised the game for its comedic and "adorable"[2][3] portrayal of the film series and for their preference of the original trilogy to the prequel trilogy. However, the game's low difficulty, and its Game Boy Advance and Nintendo DS versions in general, were received more poorly. The game received awards from the British Academy of Film and Television Arts and Spike TV, among others. A mobile phone adaptation was later developed by Universomo, published by THQ, and released on December 19, 2006. Lego Star Wars and Lego Star Wars II were compiled in Lego Star Wars: The Complete Saga, released on November 6, 2007. The OS X version of the game was released in April 2007 by Feral Interactive.[4]</desc>
		<image>./images/Lego Star Wars II-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Lego Star Wars II-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Lego Star Wars II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Lego Star Wars II-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20060912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<family>Star Wars</family>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20221011T163712" />
	</game>
</gameList>
