<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="47073">
		<path>./Amidar (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Amidar</name>
		<desc>As a paintbush, run over the borders of each rectangle to color them in in order to complete the level, while avoiding enemies. You can force them to jump to help you if they get in your way.</desc>
		<image>./images/Amidar (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Amidar (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Amidar (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Amidar (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Bros</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>ee4e2d5b4617c3bf9f11016e1fe1c94e</md5>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T094206" />
	</game>
	<game id="47074">
		<path>./Excite Mahjong (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Excite Mahjong</name>
		<desc>Excite Mahjong is a Strategy game where you will play ... mahjong. Have fun !</desc>
		<image>./images/Excite Mahjong (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Excite Mahjong (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Excite Mahjong (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Excite Mahjong (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Casio</developer>
		<publisher>Casio</publisher>
		<genre>Board game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>b0ef3b9523fb276772fa4433136bc5db</md5>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T094218" />
	</game>
	<game id="47075">
		<path>./Pachinko-UFO (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Pachinko-Ufo</name>
		<desc>Pachinko UFO is a simulator of the popular Japanese gambling pastime of pachinko with added computerised action elements. The main screen resembles a typical pachinko unit with pins for balls to bounce on, spinners for balls to put in motion, and baskets for them to land in. The baskets open and close, and so does the big feature in the middle of the screen, an airplane or spaceship with an integrated fruit-machine like counter. When a score specified by the counters is reached, the game changes to a shooter sequence, where the pachinko balls must be used to shoot down aliens. After that, the game continues to the next table.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pachinko-UFO (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pachinko-UFO (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pachinko-UFO (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pachinko-UFO (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Casio</developer>
		<publisher>Casio</publisher>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>aefafc42cabc5c6ee40defe9ec09b488</md5>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T094226" />
	</game>
	<game id="47076">
		<path>./Pooyan (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Pooyan</name>
		<desc>In Pooyan, you play the role of a pig, protecting its piglets from wolves. The first screen takes place near the pigs' home. Mrs. Pig rides up and down in a cable car, shooting at wolves, who are riding balloons downward, towards the ground. If the wolves land safely on the ground, then they can climb a ladder, near the cable-car, and catch Mrs. Pig. But if she shoots their balloons, they splat on the ground instead. The wolves shoot acorns at the pig. But Mrs. Pig has a food based weapon too. If she gets to the top, she can get meat, to toss at the wolves and make them jump off their balloons in pursuit. Each wolf taken out this way is worth bonus points (on a doubling scheme: 400, 800 1600...) The second scene takes place at the wolves lair. Here the wolves have reinforced balloons--it takes multiple hits to make them fall. Here they float upwards toward a big rock, which they push on top of Mrs. Pig, when seven wolves are present. Additionally, an alpha wolf (wolf leader) appears and summons wolves in packs.</desc>
		<image>./images/Pooyan (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pooyan (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pooyan (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pooyan (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Casio</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>e43b200c31cec2dd1ebe3331c4bd2bf3</md5>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T094147" />
	</game>
	<game id="47077">
		<path>./Super Cobra (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Cobra</name>
		<desc>Super Cobra is a side-scrolling shooter based on the arcade game. You're a chopper pilot on a surveillance mission in enemy territory; your goal is to make it through the various obstacle courses alive and score as many points as possible. Tall buildings, mountains, narrow tunnels, and various enemies (such as tanks, rockets, mines, and more) can all get in the way and destroy your chopper if you aren't careful. To help defend yourself, the chopper is armed with a machine gun and bombs which can be used to destroy the enemy tanks and rockets. To make the task more difficult, your chopper has a limited amount of fuel. Throughout the landscapes are fuel tanks; if one of these is shot or bombed, you will be awarded extra fuel. As the levels progress, the enemies become more aggressive, fuel becomes more scarce, and the landscape becomes trickier to navigate.</desc>
		<image>./images/Super Cobra (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Super Cobra (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Super Cobra (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Super Cobra (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Casio</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>01e70f498b2e104b4714434014943e1a</md5>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
		<scrap name="ScreenScraper" date="20220928T094158" />
	</game>
</gameList>
